## The Simpsons ##
Ahh.
Why, you little..!
[ Raiders ofThe Lost Ark
Theme Playing ]
What the..? D'oh!
Bart, look at this.
My dad took me to
Circus of Values last night
and said I could get
anything I wanted.
Cool-- An oversize
novelty billiard ball.
You shake it up
and it tells the future.
Really?
Uh-huh.
Will I pass my English test?
''Outlook not so good.''
Wow, it does work!
Let me try.
Will... I get
beat up today?
''All signs point to yes.''
That ball knows everything.
I got one.
Will Milhouse and I
be friends till we're
toothless old men
with hair in our ears?
Will Milhouse and I be friends
when we're high school dropouts
living off Uncle Sucker?
Will Milhouse and I
be friends at the end
of the day?
What could come between
two bestest buddies like us?
Samantha, I've always
been suspicious
of transfer students.
Other principals unload
problem cases that way.
Lord knows I do.
I'm a good student.
Yeah, sure, and they told me
I'd get a big parade
when I got back from 'Nam.
Instead, they spat on me.
I can still feel it searing.
So, let's just see
what the permanent record
has to say.
No detention,
fairly good attendance...
I see you beat
that bed-wetting problem.
Don't worry.
They'll forget...
just like they forgot about me
in that tiger cage
for 1 8 agonizing months.
Every night I wake up screaming.
Well, let's meet
your classmates.
Bart, was this thing
right about your test?
To those who doubt
the Magic Eight Ball's power
I say, behold my ''F.''
Attention, class.
I have a new student for you.
Great.Just keep
packing them in, Seymour.
We should discuss
this later.
It's never easy
to come to a new school.
Let's make her feel
right at home.
Please say a big
elementary school hello
to Samantha Stinky.
Stanky.
Oh, right.
How embarrassing for you.
Well, good-bye.
I'm sure this is
a little scary for you...
Uh-huh.
So why don't you
tell us about yourself?
I'll be grading you
on grammar and poise.
We just moved here from Phoenix.
My dad's
in home security.
He came here because of
the high crime rate
and lackluster police force.
All my friends
are back in Phoenix
and this town has a weird smell
that you're all probably used to
but I'm not.
It takes about six weeks.
Hey, Milhouse, would you
like a wet willie?
Sure.
Eww!
Victim number four.
Louis, can I interest you
in a wet willie?
Sure... aah!
When I find out who
hit me with ball
I'm going to tear them a new..!
Whoa!
In order to explain
why your hormones
will soon make you
an easy target
for every smooth-talking
lothario
with a car and tight jeans
I will now show
a short sex education film.
Ezekiel and Ishmael
in accordance with
your parents' wishes
you may step out
into the hall
and pray for our souls.
Hello. I'm actor Troy McClure.
You kids might remember me
from such educational films
as Lead Paint::
Delicious But Deadly
and Here Comes
The Metric System.
I'm here to provide
the facts about sex
in a frank
and straightforward manner.
And now, here's...
This is Fuzzy Bunny.
About a year ago
he noticed
his voice was changing
he had terrible acne
and had fur
where there was no fur before.
He also noticed Fluffy Bunny.
Boring.
Fluffy and Fuzzy
went to the park
the ice cream social
the boat show
and other wholesome activities
and they never ruined their fun
by giving in to their throbbing
biological urges.
Then came the big day.
Fluffy and Fuzzy got married.
That night came the honeymoon.
Eww!
She's faking it.
The most satisfying part
was knowing that they waited.
Nine months later
Fluffy gave birth
to 1 4 beautiful bunnies.
Eight survive.
And now that you know
how it's done...
don't do it.
Any questions?
Mrs. Krabappel
how come you don't live
with Mr. Krabappel?
Because Mr. Krabappel
chased something fluffy
down a rabbit hole.
How do we know
when we fall in love?
Oh, don't you worry.
Most of you
will never fall in love
and marry out of fear
of dying alone.
How do I create a half man,
half monkey-type creature?
I'm sorry,
that would be playing God.
God, shmod--
I want my monkey man.
Uh... that's a nice dress.
My dad makes me wear it.
I hate it.
I hate it too.
Uh... can I walk you home?
Okay.
Everybody on.
No shoving.
Just kidding.
You can shove all you want.
Hey, Otto Man,
you can't leave.
Milhouse isn't here yet.
No time, Bart Dude.
My girlfriend's dancing topless
at the airport bar
from 4:1 5 to 4:20.
Hey, Bart.
Milhouse, what
a pleasant surprise.
Hi.
What's with the skirt?
I've brought friends
to this tree house before.
But never a girl.
What if I want
to strut around nude?
Maybe I should go.
No, you can stay.
You can read comics with us.
Let's see,
something for the lady...
ah-- Radioactive Man
vs. The Swamp Hag.
Got any girl comics
like Bonnie Crane,
Girl Attorney
Punkin and Dunkin,
the Twinkle Twins
or Li'l Knee Socks?
No, but my sister's
got a wide selection
of crappy comics.
Eww!
You guys want to see
something gross?
[ Announcer]
Tonight on Smartline::
''I'm okay. You're too fat.''
Here's your host,
Kent Brockman.
Good evening.
Did you know that 34 million
american adults are obese?
That excess blubber
could fill two-fifths
of the Grand Canyon.
That may not sound impressive
but keep in mind,
it is a very big canyon.
This sucks. Where's
that channel changer?
Oh.
I'll give it a chance.
Americans have grown up
with the image
of the jolly fat man--
Dom DeLuise
Alfred Hitchcock, and, of course
Santa Claus.
But in real life
Santa would be suffering
from gall stones
hypertension, impotence,
and diabetes.
I wish they had never
invented fried cheese.
We got to widen
the hole.
Hurry-- The chain's
starting to give.
We take 1 8 ounces
of sizzling ground beef
and soak it
in rich creamery butter.
Then we top it off with bacon,
ham, and a fried egg.
We call it
the Good Morning Burger.
I've got to help him.
Okay, Milhouse
I'll trade your Carl Yastrzemski
baseball card
for my Omar Vizquel.
Deal.
Next, your Mickey Mantle
for my picture
of Homer on the couch.
Milhouse, I've got to go.
My dad thinks I'm having
my braces examined.
Well, you kind of
sort of are.
Milhouse, we're living
in the age of cooties.
I can't believe
the risk you're running.
Besides, what's so great
about kissing?
It's not just
the kissing.
A lot of it is
waiting to kiss.
You know, like when you open
an Eskimo Pie
and you wait just a little
for it to melt?
But she doesn't melt.
Oh, yes, she does.
We start with pure
milk chocolate...
Chocolate...
...add a layer
of farm-fresh honey...
Oh, sweet.
...then we sprinkle on
four kinds of sugar...
...and dip it
in rich creamery butter.
What if I told you
you could lose weight
without dieting
or lifting a finger?
I'd say you're
a lying scumbag.
Why, sweetie?
According to Eternity magazine
you can lose weight
subliminally.
An idea is subtly implanted
in your head
without your knowing it.
That's a load
of rich creamery butter.
You listen to tapes
while you sleep.
As you hear New Age music
a powerful message
goes to your brain
telling you to eat less.
Lose weight and listen
to New Age music? Wow.
What do you think, Marge?
Oh, Homer, I love you
just the way you are.
Lisa, what's that number?
I'd like to place an order
for my husband.
Would he like to lose weight,
stop smoking
learn the state capitals,
master hostage negotiations..?
Hmm... hostage negotiations.
Listen, Tabbouleh, we're
ignoring all your demands.
What do you say to that?
Give me
the weight loss tape.
We're out of
''Subliminally Slim.''
Uh... send them
the vocabulary builder.
Here you go, fatso.
So long, stomach.
We've had a lot
of great memories.
Hello. This is
Dr. Marvin Monroe.
Let's build your vocabulary.
Abattoir: Slaughterhouse.
''The cow was slaughtered
in the abattoir.''
Has the weight loss tape
reduced your appetite?
Lamentably, no.
My gastronomic rapacity
knows no satiety.
Don't you usually
play with Milhouse?
He has a girlfriend.
Milhouse?
Yeah. All they do is kiss.
How cute.
They don't open
their mouths, do they?
No.
How cute.
Hey, Martin.
No one has sat next to me
since I successfully lobbied
to have the school day
extended by 20 minutes.
I'm looking for a friend
who won't leave me
for a girl.
I'm as unpopular
with the ladies
as I am with the chaps.
Yeah, right.
Do you want to do something
after school?
It's a date.
Everyone, Bart and I
would like to announce
that we friends.
Bart, would you care
to listen to me play the lute?
Uh... sure.
Is that tape working?
You ate three desserts
tonight.
Forbearance is the watchword.
That triumvirate of twinkies
overwhelmed my resolve.
There's another thing
I want to talk about.
Tut, tut, gentle Marge.
Here in the boudoir
the gourmand
metamorphosizes into...
the voluptuary!
What in God's name
are you talking about?
Oh.
Mmm...
Heh...
Hey, guys.
Wow, that really took my mind
off those awful,
transforming space mutants.
Good.
Man, I could sure go
for a snack.
Me too.
D'oh!
Hey, I've got an idea.
Why don't we go spit
on the principal's car?
Listen, Bart, there's
such a thing
as spending
too much time together.
Oh, fine.
I'm tired of watching
you two lip wrestle.
There's plenty of other ways
to be grossed out.
Bart, wait.
Yeah?
Uh...
could we still use
your tree house?
What? Get bent.
If her father catches us,
he'll kill her.
All right, Milhouse.
You can use my tree house.
Thanks, Bart.
# Samantha and Milhouse
sitting in a tree #
#About to lose their privacy ##
Now there's
a Machiavellian
countenance.
Ooh, a sextet of ale!
Hello, Mr. Stanky?
I have shocking news
about Samantha.
Who am I?
Let's just say I'm
concerned prude
with lot of time on his hands.
I bet you had peanut butter
for breakfast.
Yeah.
Samantha!
Dad!
Noooooo!
Samantha, you're my little girl
and sometimes my imagination
runs away with me.
Just tell me
what happened.
Milhouse and I...
That's enough!
I'm putting you in
an all-girl school.
You're never going to see
that boy again.
Milhouse!
Samantha!
Well, 'tis better
to have loved and lost...
yatta, yatta, yatta.
Let's go to the arcade.
How could this happen?
We started out
like Romeo and Juliet
but it ended up
in tragedy.
Hierospacy:
Predicting the future
through the study
of animal entrails.
Dad! Do you know
what today is?
The vernal equinox?
No, it's two weeks
since you got
that weight-loss tape.
Let's get you on the scale.
You've gained 1 3 pounds.
Disingenuous mountebanks with
their subliminal chicanery--
A pox on them!
There stands
a broken man.
It's recess everywhere
but in his heart.
Hey, Bart, according
to this magazine
in another million years
man will have
an extra finger.
Five fingers?
Ooh-- Freak show!
Lise, I need some advice
and mom's not here.
What about dad?
I couldn't understand
what he was saying.
I feel terrible.
I ratted on my best friend
and he doesn't even know.
According to
Eternity magazine
the feeling of guilt
has been linked
to gamephenomene.
Dow Chemical is developing
a minty gel
to eliminate excess guilt
but it won't be on the market
for six months
so I guess you'll have
to confess to Milhouse.
Bart, I'm glad you're here.
Milhouse could use
a friend like you.
Milhouse?
Bart, I don't want you
to see me cry.
Oh, come on.
You cry when they're out
of chocolate milk.
You cry when you're doing
long division
and you have
a remainder left over.
Well, I didn't want you
to see me cry this time.
Milhouse, I got
a confession to make.
I'm the one who narc'ed
on your kissing.
What?!
Milhouse is out bed
and full beans.
Whoa, it's a miracle!
I bet the eight ball
didn't see that one coming.
Yeah.
Marge...
where's that...
metal dealie...
you use to...
dig... food?
You mean, a spoon?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh, this is good.
Are you sure
you want to do this?
I can't stop thinking
about her.
Even these gates remind me
of her braces.
How are we going
to find her?
She's wearing a plaid jumper.
Milhouse!
Samantha!
I went to Circus of Values
and bought you a ten-gallon tub
of gummi bears.
I'm sorry about
getting you thrown
in the penguin house.
That's all right, Bart.
I love Saint Sebastian's.
It's run by a group
of French Canadian nuns.
They're very nice
except they never let me out.
Samantha, ne pas des boys.
I have to go now,
Milhouse.
I'd better not.
It's 50 rosaries
a kiss.
Oh, okay.
Oh, what the heck.
Bart
think I can ever find
another one like her?
You're asking
the wrong guy, Milhouse.
They all look alike to me.
Now, let's go whip donuts
at old people.
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net