##Ahhh, the Simpsons ##
D'oh!
Ooh!
Ooh, ooh, ooh, what?
Hello?
Dad, the school talent show--
I know, it's tonight.
I broke my last saxophone reed.
I need a new one.
Isn't this something
your mother's better at?
I called her.
She's not home.
I also tried Mr. Flanders, Aunt Patty,
Aunt Selma, Dr. Hibbert, Reverend Lovejoy...
and that nice man who caught
the snake in our basement.
Wow. And after them...
out of all the people in the world...
you chose me.
Uh-huh.
Number 4½/ reed. Got it.
You're in for
a whale of a show tonight.
The doors are now locked,
so you parents can't sneak out...
after your own child has performed.
Let me caution the people
in the first five rows--
You will get wet.
Just in the nick of--
Mmm. Beer.
I've only got five minutes
till the music store closes.
Go there first.
Do I tell you what to do?
Sorry, Homer.
Tip the glass.
This is a whole lot of nothing.
I'd rather watch the boilers.
Make sure you return
those chairs to the cafeteria.
I'm not kidding.
Ah... finished,
with 1 5 seconds to spare.
Ah!
D'oh! D'oh!
What's the matter, buddy?
The moron next door closed early.
I happen to be that moron.
Oh, me and my
trenchant mouth!
Oh, terrible,just terrible.
They seem to get worse every year.
Ha, ha, ha!
Wonderful!
This is the best batch
we've ever had.
And now, here's Bart Simpson...
the boy of a thousand voices.
I'd like to open
with my impression of...
Principal Skinner.
Duh, look at me.
I'm Principal Skinner.
That young man just became...
the boy of a thousand days detention.
I wonder what lunch lady Doris
has for us today.
Today's special is refried...
dog poop.
Please! You've got
to open that store.
Let me think about it.
Uh... no.
Okay, but I want you
to see a picture...
of the little girl
you're disappointing.
Well, I don't have one.
Come on,Jer.
Open up.
I pulled you
out of that burning car.
Okay, but now we're even.
What does your daughter need?
I wrote it down.
''Number... Number 4½/--''
Stupid gum!
''Number 4½/ reed.''
Whoo-hoo!
Mm-hmm. What instrument
does she play?
I don't know.
Mom, where is he?
If I don't get that reed,
I'll sound terrible.
Don't worry, honey.
I'm sure your father is...
maybe--
No.
That's a long shot.
Bingo.
Don't worry.
He'll be here.
- Clarinet? Oboe?
- No.
- Saxophone?
What was that last one?
Saxophone.
Hmm...
Lisa, stop playing that stupid--
Saxophone! That's it!
Alto or tenor?
D'oh!
This act is over!
Well, ladies and gentlemen...
I'd like to put this filth behind us...
and let's all enjoy...
Lisa Simpson's rendition...
of''Stormy Leather.''
Uh, ''Weather.''
Sounds like that gopher
I caught in me lawn mower.
Ew, I'd hate to be
that kid's father.
Uh-oh.
That will do.
It's not my fault.
It's the reed.
Oh, yes, of course.
Let's hear it for Lisa Simpson...
and her wacky sax.
Yeah!
Whoo!
Must be her father.
Whoo, yeah...
Who ordered a Mount Bellyache?
I ordered it for my little girl.
I'm done.
Oh! That cost $88!
I don't feel much like eating.
Look, I let you down
and I apologize.
I know that doesn't make it right.
I hope you can forgive me.
I forgive you.
D'oh! You didn't mean that.
No, I didn't.
Look, Homer...
Lisa's taking her first steps.
You're taping it?
Yes.
I'll watch it later.
The plane,
the plane!
No, my freakish little friend.
Hmm.
Da-da.
Did you hear that, Homer?
Marge, please-- I'm busy.
No wonder she hates me.
Oh, I never even noticed
she was alive.
If you want to make up with Lisa...
spend some time with her.
Ohh! Okay!
Ahh!
Maybe I should give up on Lisa...
and make a fresh start
with Maggie.
Stop looking for the quick fix.
If you keep spending time
with Lisa, she'll forgive you.
If I spend any more time
doing girl things...
I'm going to, you know, go fruity.
No, you were right the first time...
with that quick fix idea.
Let's see-- quick fix, quick fix.
I'll buy her that pony
she's always bugging me for.
We can't afford it.
With today's gasoline prices,
we can't afford not to.
Ridiculous.
When I look in Lisa's eyes...
I don't see love.
That's no reason to buy a pony.
When you yell at me,
I see love in your eyes.
Stick to the subject.
# Uh-huh
you love me #
Let's be realistic.
A pony is expensive.
We have enough trouble
paying bills as it is.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Promise me you won't buy a pony.
Hmm.
Was that a yes or a no?
Baa.
Those aren't even words.
Sna.
Oh, my, what's that smell?
Oh, it's you.
Excuse me.
Do you sell ponies?
Sure, pal. Right here.
''Scottish Deer Hound.''
Hey, this is a dog!
My friend, you're smarter
than I gave you credit for.
I suggest you try the pony farm
on Route 401 .
Merely take a left
at the rendering plant.
Lady, I'm buying a pony
for my little girl...
and I don't care what it costs.
Very good.
That stunning creature over there...
is half a million dollars.
Half a million dollars?!
He was sired by Seattle Slew.
His mother won
the Kentucky Derby.
His likeness
graces a stamp in Tanzania.
Sold.
Mr. Simpson, do you have...
half a million dollars?
Sure, let me write you a check.
Mr. Simpson...
this check is dated
January 1 , 2054.
Is there a problem with that?
Our ponies start at $5,000... cash.
Isn't there like a pound...
where you can pick up cheap ponies...
that ran away from home?
I sincerely hope not.
I'd like...
to borrow $5,000.
Sorry.
I can't approve
a loan that size myself.
Hello.
''Simpson.''
How can I help you?
Mr. Burns,
you do this personally?
It's a hobby.
I'm not in this for personal gain.
Are you acquainted with our
state's stringent usury laws?
Usury?
Silly me.
I made up a word
that doesn't exist.
What is the purpose of this loan?
I want to buy a pony.
Isn't that cute?
He's planning on joining
the horsey set.
That is it, isn't it?
You're not planning to eat it?
It's for my little girl
because she doesn't love me.
Shut up, Simpson.
You have any collateral?
Smithers, let's not be so cold.
His spirit is my collateral.
Just sign this form
and the money will be yours.
Sorry, I was just thinking...
of something funny
Smithers did today.
I didn't do anything funny, sir.
Shut up.
Mr. Simpson...
are you quite sure you know
how to take care of a pony?
Of course.
Simpson, you've done it again.
Oh!
I love you, Dad!
Mmmmm.
I am very upset with you.
Sounds like someone's angling...
for a pony of her own.
How come Lisa gets a pony?
She stopped loving me.
So get me a moped.
I know you love me,
so you don't get squat.
Snowball II,
Santa's Little Helper--
This is Princess.
Please don't exclude her
because she's different.
Where were you planning
to keep this horse?
I've got it figured out.
By day, it will roam free
around the neighborhood...
and at night,
it will nestle snugly...
between the cars in our garage.
Dad, no!
That's illegal.
That's for the courts to decide.
Marge, she loves me.
Dad, I think Princess
belongs in a stable.
Stable?
That sounds expensive.
This is what love costs a month?
These are standard fees, Mr. Simpson.
Plus, I'm teaching your daughter
riding, grooming...
and at no extra charge,
pronunciation.
You've made me
the happiest girl who ever lived.
Oh, nuts.
What do I do? What do I do?
If you want to go right...
move the joystick left.
Yes. Move the--
What's a joystick?
Oh, oh!
Here comes a Xylon cruiser!
Go into hyperspace!
Wait! Where's the hyperspace?
Grandpa, you're the spaceship.
I thought I was this guy.
- Oh!
Game's over.
I got down on the floor for this?!
Wait, Dad.
I've got something for you.
I was hoping...
it would be money.
Hmm, dear. We're
in serious trouble here.
We're just going to have
to cut down on luxuries.
Well, we're always buying Maggie...
vaccinations for diseases
she doesn't even have.
We could cut down on beer.
We're not going to do that.
Then there's no choice
but to give up the pony.
First you didn't
want the pony.
Now you want me
to take it back.
Make up your mind.
Homer!
Lisa loves me.
The pony stays.
You got us into this.
You get us out.
There's plenty of money out there...
for a guy who's willing to work.
Do you have any jewelry
you don't need?
Mmmmm.
You're so beautiful.
Oh, you haven't touched
your salt lick.
Num-num. Good salt lick.
Need money. Need money.
One scratch-for-cash.
Here you go.
Liberty bell.
Two liberty bells.
Come on,
come on, come on--
Oh.
Yes!
Whoo-whoo!
Three liberty bells!
That will be $1 0,000, Apu.
Congratulations, Mr. Homer.
Thank you.
If I could see the ticket--
There it is.
Please to be removing your thumb.
No.
Yes, please. I must insist.
No. No.
You can't see--
Yes, I must--
No! Let go!
You're ripping it.
A cherry.
Oh, Mr. Homer...
what has reduced you
to such cheap chicanery?
Oh... I need money.
If you need money...
you should have
jammed a gun in my ribs...
or inquire
about my help wanted sign.
You need help?
Someone for the demanding...
high profile
midnight to 8:00 a.m. shift.
I'm your man.
You're hired.
I dreamed of the day...
one of you would work for me.
She certainly tamed that horse.
But what man can tame her?
I won't lie to you.
On this job,
you will be shot at.
Each bullet wound
is a badge of honor.
''Badge of honor''--
Here's a pointer.
Try taking it in the shoulder.
These hot dogs have been here
for three years.
They are strictly ornamental.
There is only one bozo
who comes in and buys them.
But I eat-- Oh.
The perfect crime.
Homer, where have you been
all night?
I was so worried.
Let's go in the other room.
I did something I'm ashamed of.
The kids can't hear it.
Busted.
I'll work midnight to 8:00.
Come home, sleep five minutes...
eat breakfast,
sleep six minutes, shower.
I have ten minutes
to bask in Lisa's love...
Then I'm off to the power plant,
fresh as a daisy.
Oh, my God, she killed him.
Mmm. Salty.
Homer!
Are you stealing Squishies?
No, sir.
This next song is also...
about a girl and her pony.
It's called ''Wildfire.''
Come on, Apu, honey, loosen up.
Ohh!
I'm sorry, baby.
While I'm here with you...
my store is going down the tubes.
Three dollars
and 51 ... 52... 53 cents.
Homer, you are asleep
at your post!
Go change the expiration dates...
on the dairy products.
Yes, sir.
Sorry, baby. Date's over.
Homie, how long do you
plan to do this?
I don't know.
How long do horses live?
30 years.
D'oh.
Mustn't sleep.
Must monitor core.
Hello?
I called to say I love you.
Thanks.
When is she going
to stop loving me?
I heard Milli Vanilli was arrested...
for impersonating a McNugget.
Well, it's still fun to be up late.
Hey, Homer, where you going?
Going for...
eight-hour walk.
Homer. Homer.
Homer sleep now.
What's wrong with Dad?
He's just exhausted.
Lisa, do you know what
it costs to keep a pony?
No.
Well, it's a lot.
Your father had
to take a second job.
Poor guy.
Where's he working?
The Kwik-E mart.
I hope you realize...
that your father can't keep this up.
You're making me
give up Princess?
We can't make you.
I can make her.
Give me five minutes
alone with her.
No, Bart.
No one's making her.
Lisa has to decide for herself.
All the years I've lobbied
to be treated like an adult...
have blown up in my face.
Hey!
When I ordered...
that blueberry Squishy,
I meant today.
Coming right up, sir.
And fill it to the top time.
Yes, sir.
She likes a little carrot
after her oats...
and she likes it...
when you scratch her
behind the ear.
She likes contemporary
adult radio in the morning...
and easy listening at night.
Please take good care
of my Princess.
Although there is no change
in my patrician facade...
my heart is breaking.
I'll never forget you.
What the?
You call this melted cheese
receptacle clean?
The young man you replaced
is rolling over in his grave.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
You see, Lisa...
grown-ups have
a thing called money.
Dad, I understand the sacrifice
you've made for me.
That's why I gave up the pony.
You did?
There's a big dumb animal...
I love more than that horse.
What is it, a hippopotamus?
I mean you, you dummy.
Oh.
Apu, you can take this job
and restaff it.
Giddy-up, Dad!
He slept, he stole...
he was rude to the customers.
Still, there goes
the best damned employee...
a convenience store ever had.
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net