## The Simpsons ##
D'oh!
Hello, I'm Kent Brockman,
and this is Eye on Springfield.
[ Rock And Roll
Instrumental Theme Playing ]
Wow. Info-tainment.
Tonight
we salute the silver anniversary
of the Great Springfield
Tire Yard Fire.
25 years
and still burning strong.
We watch
Springfield's oldest man
meet Springfield's fattest man.
He's not so fat.
And we visit
with heavyweight champion
Dredrick Tatum
who reminisces about growing up
in Springfield.
It was a dump.
If you see me there,
you know I up bad.
But first, part seven
of our eye-opening look
at the bikini.
Whoa-- T and A!
Why are you still up?
- Lisa's slumber party.
Who can sleep with those five evil hens
cackling and plotting against me?
They've got better things
to talk about than you.
Sheesh, what an ego.
Lisa, your brother
is so gross.
You should smell
his room.
Now remember, Wanda,
whatever shape the wax takes
that's what your
husband's job will be.
It's a mop.
My husband will be a janitor.
That looks like
an Olympic torch to me.
He could be an athlete
and go on to have
a great acting career.
It's a dustpan.
The wax never lies.
Let's play truth or dare.
Truth or dare! Truth or dare!
I'll take... dare.
I dare you to...
kiss Lisa's brother.
Eww!!
What the..?
Aaaaahh!
I'm telling mom and dad.
Who?
Mom and dad.
Jinx!
#You can't talk till somebody
says your name #
Coming up next:
An elephant who never forgets...
to brush!
What is it, boy?
Is anything the matter,
my son?
Talk to me, young man.
Say your name?
Why should I do that,
my lad?
Because I'm jinxed,
damn it!... Ow!
What was that for?
You spoke
while you were jinxed
so I get to punch you.
Sorry, it's the law.
There he is.
Let's give him
a makeover.
Run for it, boy!
Get him! Get him! Get him!
Aaaaahh!
Oof!.
Come here, Maggie.
Huh?!
That's it, I'm out of here.
Hiya, Homer.
What's the matter, Moe?
Oh, business is slow.
People are healthier
and drinking less.
If it wasn't for
the junior high school next door
no one would even use
the cigarette machine.
Yeah, things are tough.
Increased job satisfaction
and family togetherness
are poison for a purveyor
of mind-numbing intoxicants.
Got a beer?
Yeah, sure.
Oh, sorry.
I forgot
we're out of beer.
Aahh!
I got behind
on my beer payments.
The distributor
cut me off
and I spent my last ten grand
on the love tester.
You're too late,
Homer.
Barney sucked it dry.
Cut his gums up
pretty bad.
Ohh!
Take it easy, Homer.
I learned how to make other
drinks at bartender's school.
Gin and... tonic?
Do they mix?
Hey, I know a good drink.
Really hits the spot.
I invented it myself.
One night,
Marge's beastly sisters
were showing slides
from their vacation.
And this is Patty
trying to plug her razor
into those ungodly
Czechoslovakian outlets.
As you can see, we
never got the hang of it.
Ay, caramba!
As I stared
at that hairy drumstick
I knew I needed a drink.
Patty, Selma, would you
excuse me for a moment?
If you're going for a beer,
this is the last one.
D'oh!
I decided to mix
the little bits that were left
in every liquor bottle.
In my haste
I had grabbed a bottle
of the kids'cough syrup.
It passed the first test--
I didn't go blind.
They say everyone can float
in the Dead Sea
but Selma sank
right to the bottom.
Huh?!
I don't know the scientific
explanation
but fire made it good.
Sounds like one hell
of a drink.
What do you call it?
A Flaming Homer.
Why don't you
make us up a couple
of Flaming Homers?
You got any
cough syrup?
Let me check
the lost and found.
Bowie knife, troll doll...
glass eye...
Oh, here we are.
It's not without it's charm.
Try lighting it on fire.
Hmm?!
Wow!
Homer, it's like there's
a party in my mouth
and everyone's invited.
Hey,
your love tester's busted.
I want my nickel back.
Hey, buddy,
have one on the house.
Hey, this drink is delicious
and my phlegm feels looser.
What do you call it?
It's called a Flaming...
...Moe!
It's called a Flaming Moe.
That's right, a Flaming Moe.
My name is Moe,
and I invented it.
What are you looking at,
Homer?
It's a Flaming Moe.
- Oh!
Hey, what's this?
A sneeze guard.
Wow, it really works!
It hasn't been this crowded
since the government
cracked down on you
for accepting food stamps.
Think my drink had something
to do with it?
Who can say?
It's probably a combination of things.
Another pitcher
of Flaming Moes.
I hate this joint,
but I love that drink.
Ohhh.
I couldn't help
noticing your sign.
You mean, '' Bartenders
Do It 'Til You Barf''?
Above that store-bought
drollery.
Why don't we fill out
an application.
I'll need your name,
measurements, and turn-ons.
You expect me to tell you that?
You could,
but I find this way
is much more accurate,
and fun.
Ugh! What salary do you offer?
Minimum wage and tips.
Of course,
there are fringe benefits.
Such as?
An unforgettable weekend
at Club Moe.
I'd prefer to vacation
someplace hot.
- Whoo!
- Ha-ha!
- Ow!
- Whoo!
I like your moxie, kid.
You're hired.
You shan't regret this.
Methinks I shan't.
Are you the genius
behind the Flaming Moe?
- Yes, I...
- I'm your man.
I work for Tipsy McStagger's
good time drinking
and eating emporium.
Oh, yeah? Hey, what's
Mr. McStagger really like?
Tipsy McStagger
is just a composite
of other successful logos.
You tell him for me
that he makes
one great mozzarella stick.
Yes, I will.
I've got a proposition
for you.
Your Flaming Moe
is perfect for our chain.
We want to buy the recipe.
It's not for sale.
Do you know how much
of my blood and sweat
are in this drink?
Uh... figure of speech.
Sorry, Harv.
I'll be back.
Good for you, Moe.
Only an idiot
would give away
a million-dollar idea
like that.
Ohhh.
The next time you use
a gas chromatograph
remember to thank
Mr. A.J.P. Martin.
Brilliant, Martin.
Once again you've wrecked
the grading curve.
I pity the student
who has to follow you.
Bart Simpson,
you're next.
''The Inventor I Admire''
by Bart Simpson.
The inventor I admire
is not a rich man
or a famous man,
or even a smart man.
He's my father, Homer Simpson
creator of...
# Dun-da-da-dah #
The Flaming Homer!
The Flaming Homer?
You mean the Flaming Moe
and your dad
didn't invent it, you wuss.
Moe the bartender did.
Everyone knows that.
It's not true.
My father invented it.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Are those liquor bottles?
I brought plenty.
Take those to
the teachers' lounge.
Hey, Bernard!
Good evening,
Krusty.
Nice to see you,
Bernard.
Thank you very much.
- Krusty, over here!
- Krusty, one more!
Henceforth, this date
shall forever be known
as Flaming Moe's Day.
Sir, this is Veteran's Day.
It can be two things.
Mom, instead of milk,
can I have a virgin Moe?
Honey, what's wrong?
I'll tell you what.
That rotten Moe is getting rich
off a recipe I gave him.
Take that off
this second.
Okay.
Homey, why don't you go
to Moe's
and talk to him?
I bet he'd share some
of his success with you.
Nah.
Marge, I'm too upset to eat.
I think I'll go to Moe's.
D'oh!
Oh!
Hey!
Can I help you?
I need to see Moe.
Your name's
not on the list.
I never gave it.
What is it?
Homer Simpson.
Not on the list.
We're all filled up.
File off!.
Some new buddies of mine
stopped by tonight.
Maybe we can get them
to come up here.
How about a warm
Flaming Moe's welcome for...
Aerosmith!
Nah. We're just
hanging out.
Come on. Free pickled eggs.
- All right!
- Yeah!
Hello, St. Louis!
That's Springfield,
Steven.
Oh, yeah. Right.
Are you ready to rock?
Yeah!
I said, are you ready to rock!
Hit it!
Barney?
Hi, Homer.
I want you
to meet my friends
Armando and Raffi.
Hey, Moe, come on.
Get up here.
Do you want to ignite
my drink?
You're my kid's teacher.
Single parent, are we?
No.
Let's pretend you are.
Get away from me.
Hey, Moe!
Homer, how about a beer?
I'd rather have
a Flaming Homer.
A what?
Oh, I get it.
How could you
do this to me?
This bar was going under,
and my drink saved it.
My face should be on
that crappy merchandise.
Morris, is what
this man says true?
It's hard to say.
He may have come up
with the recipe
but I came up
with the idea
of charging 6.95.
Uhp-- telephone.
Flaming Moe's.
I'm looking for a friend.
Last name:Jazz.
First name: Hugh.
Hold on. I'll check.
Huge ass?
Somebody check the men's room
for a huge ass.
I'm Hugh Jazz.
Telephone.
This is Hugh Jazz.
Uh... hi.
Who's this?
Bart Simpson.
What can I do for you?
This is a crank call
that backfired
and I'd like to bail out
right now.
Better luck next time.
Hmm, what a nice young man.
I'm sorry you're mad,
but this isn't personal.
This is business.
Business, eh?
Well, you just lost yourself
a customer.
What? I couldn't hear you.
I said,
you just lost a customer!
- What?
- You just lost a customer!
You'll have to speak up.
You lost yourself
a customer, Moe!
I forced myself to what?
You just lost
a customer!
We'll talk tomorrow.
You just lost yourself
a customer!
Yeah, you can use it.
Barney!
How's the world treating you?
Hey, there!
What can I do
for you, Harv?
Tipsy McStagger would like
to buy your drink.
He's here?
No. My company is willing
to do what it takes
to get that recipe.
We're prepared
to offer you $1 million.
Sorry, Harv,
but like I told you before
it ain't for sale.
Don't be stupid!
We have a lab for this.
We've figured it out,
except for one ingredient.
Brace yourselves, gentlemen.
According
to the gas chromatograph
the secret ingredient is...
love?!
Who's been screwing
with this thing?
I'm sorry, but the secret
ingredient dies with me.
30 cases of cough syrup.
- Sign here.
I got hooked on this
in the service.
Ah! My new watering hole.
Yeah, what do you want?!
A beer.
Okay, then.
Can I have a clean glass?
Here you go,
Your Majesty.
Next on Eye on Springfield
a toast to Moe,
wizard of Walnut Street.
The Flaming Moe
dates back to my forefathers
who were bartenders to the czar.
So, Mr. Hutz,
does my husband have a case?
I'm sorry,
Mrs. Simpson
but you can't
copyright a drink.
Ohh!
This goes back to the '7 8
Frank Wallbanger case.
How about that?
I looked something up.
These books don't just make
the office look good.
They're filled
with useful legal tidbits.
Stupid Moe.
Non-inventing,
recipe-stealing, pug-nosed...
maybe you can take consolation
in that something you created
I'm the magical man
from happy land
in a gumdrop house
on lollipop lane.
Oh, by the way,
I was being sarcastic.
Well, duh!
Now, that's what I call
a happy hour.
Morris, something troubles me.
My mother won't be home
for another 20 minutes.
No. I was thinking
about Homer Simpson.
That's okay.
I was thinking
about Sybil Danning.
I meant, I think you
should sell your drink
and give half the money
to Homer.
But, honey...
He's your friend, Morris
and you took advantage
of him.
All right.
I'll split the million
with Homer.
Jeepers, Mary and Joseph!
I sleep with a chick once
it costs me
half a million bananas.
Moe, Moe, Moe...
Bart, are you going
to mow the lawn today?
Okay, but you promised me
Moe money.
I Moe, I Moe.
Moe, Moe, Moe...
When Bart's done,
can we Moe
to the Moevies
for the Moetinee?
Of course. All work and Moe play
makes Moe a Moe Moe.
Moe Moe Moe Moe Moe?
Moe Moe Moe.
Moe Moe Moe Moe Moe.
Moe Moe Moe Moe.
Moe.
Moe, Moe...
Moe...
Moe....
Moe, Moe...
Hey, Homer.
- Hey, Homer.
Aaaaahh!
Hiya, Homer!
What's the matter?
Aaaaaaahhh!
Hey, where's Joey?
[Joey ]
Mrs. Krabappel
I really need
my drumsticks.
Come and get 'em!
You're going to be
a rich man, Moe.
The way we usually work
is to steal the recipe
and run the inventor
out of business.
Ah, c'est la vie.
What the..?
Fools!
You poor, pathetic
misguided creatures
choking down Flaming Moes
all the time wondering,
'' How does he do it?''
Well, I'm going to tell you.
Hee-hee-hee-hee-hee!
The secret ingredient is...
Homer, no!
...Cough syrup.
Nothing but plain, ordinary,
over-the-counter
children's cough syrup.
Shoot.
Thank you, Mr. Nutball.
Got to go, Moe.
Tough luck.
Aaaaaaaahhh!
Holy cow,
you just fell
on Aerosmith!
Hey, Homer.
Come in here.
Hi, Moe.
Where's your waitress?
She left to pursue
a movie career.
Frankly, I think she
was better off here.
Moe, sorry I lost you hundreds
of thousands of dollars.
Oh, hey, hey.
Maybe some things are too good
to be kept a secret.
I guess so.
Compliments of the house--
One Flaming... Homer.
Aw, thanks, Moe.
You're the greatest friend
a guy could ever have.
Hey, do you think Aerosmith
will be in tonight?
I doubt it.
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net