##Ahh, the Simpsons ##
D'oh!
Oh, ain't that cute?
Hey! Where in God's name
did you learn that kind of...
dancing?
Whoa.
Ooh.
Oh, yeah.
Can I have money...
to buy Bart
a birthday present?
Money.
- Dad, this is $1 1 0.
- Oh. Sorry.
That's righteous.
Funky See, Funky Do will be back
to lip-synch one of their hits...
right after this.
Hey, kids,
why sit in front of the TV...
when you can be on the radio?
#We're gonna roll
this truckin' convoy #
#Across the U.S.A. #
# Convoy #
That could be Bart.
Throw away
your bulky transmitters...
and broadcasting towers.
The superstar
celebrity microphone...
lets you hear your voice
through any A.M. radio.
Hey, good-looking...
we'll be back
to pick you up later.
He's in for some loving.
It's the perfect gift
for birthdays, graduations...
board meetings.
You're fired.
Bart's birthday's coming up.
But order now,
supply is limited.
Limited!
Do you have
any of those microphones left?
Yeah, a couple.
Bart's really going to like
my birthday present this year.
It won't be like
those shoe trees...
I got him last year...
or the shelf paper
I bought him for Christmas.
I'll buy his love yet.
Mmm, yeah.
Okay, Sideshow Mel...
bring out the birthday cake.
Hey, kids...
while Sideshow Mel mops up...
let's see the names...
of our Krusty birthday pals
for today.
All right,
here comes my name.
Wow.
Best eight bucks I ever spent.
Bart, your grandpa's on the phone.
He wants
to wish you a happy birthday.
Isn't that nice?
Take a message.
Right now, I'm off
to hit 46 local merchants...
for free birthday...
goods and services.
I'm here for
my free birthday sundae.
Eat it and get out.
Digital audiotape, my butt.
When I was a kid,
we had compact discs...
and I don't recall
no one complaining.
Damn right.
Sorry, Rosarita.
I got to get
to my birthday party.
Farewell, Señor Bart.
Hey, good to see you.
Glad you could make it.
Toby, have you lost weight?
Uh-oh, here comes trouble.
It's Wally!
Hey, Wally,
do something funny.
Hey, later, okay?
Hey, why don't you
go bug your parents?
Cool, Larry the Looter.
All right, stick it to the man.
Hey there.
I hear it's your birthday.
How old are you?
Well, I'm--
That's great.
Would you like us to
sing you a special song?
- Hell, no.
- You got it.
Ready, Señor Beaveratti?
I'm a-ready.
And a-one, and a-two...
#You're the birthday #
#You're the birthday boy
or girl... #
What the...?
It's a label maker.
We have one at home.
Before we got it...
I was always
finding Patty's stubble...
in my leg razor.
Bart, I'll bet you think...
nothing's going
to top that cactus.
Well, check out my present.
Next.
Bart, be polite.
Next, please.
Bart, I've noticed...
your birthday presents
are a poor crop at best.
I hope this turns the tide.
Ooh,just gorgeous.
Now we can be twins.
There's only one beer left,
and it's Bart's.
Hey, boy,
how's the microphone working?
Fine.
Bart! I would love
to get a present like that.
Here you go.
Enjoy.
D'oh!
This is a great invention.
Watch.
#We got a great big convoy #
# Rocking through the night #
#We got a great big convoy
Ain't she a beautiful sight? #
# Convoy #
Quit it, Dad!
Hey, good-looking...
we'll be back
for some dinner later.
What did you say?
I can't understand you
with all that distortion.
What a crappy birthday.
I don't think
this is such a bad present.
Maybe you shouldn't talk into it
as loud as your father does.
Testing.
Testing one-two-three.
Oh, my.
Do I sound like that?
Hey, it does work.
I bet you could
have a lot of fun with this.
Why don't you
go show your father?
Mmm, chocolate.
D'oh!
Marge, we need some more...
vanilla, chocolate
and strawberry ice cream.
I'll get some
at the store tomorrow, Homer.
Mmm, chocolate.
People of Earth, this is Bartron--
commander
of the Martian invasion force.
Your planet is in our hands.
Resistance is useless.
We have captured your president.
He was delicious.
Why, you little--
Oh...
just promise me...
you won't play
any more practical jokes.
I promise.
Mama. Mama.
Maggie, you talked!
Can you say ''Mama'' again?
Sorry, lady.
Show's over.
Oh, Bart.
I dreamed
I was married to Corey...
and we lived
on a pony farm...
and Corey was always
walking around...
with his shirt off.
Oh, brother.
Mrs. Crabapple,
that was uncalled for.
Bravo!
Well done, old man.
Hmm.
Rod, Tod, this is God.
How did you get on the radio?
What do you mean?
I created the universe,
stupid kids.
Forgive my brother.
We believe you.
Talk is cheap.
Perhaps a test of thy faith.
Walk through the wall.
I will remove it...
for you...
...later.
What do you want?
I got a job for thee.
Bring forth all the cookies
from your kitchen...
and leave them
on the Simpsons' porch.
But those belong
to our parents.
Look, do you want a happy God
or a vengeful God?
Happy God.
Then quit flapping your lip.
- Yes, sir.
Whoops.
Help! Help!
Sounds like
trouble a-brewing at the old well!
Help me, please.
I fell down the well!
I'll get help, laddie.
A little nip of courage.
Out of my way!
Look out, you horse's arse!
Sucker.
Huh?
Hey, what's up?
Some poor kid...
fell down a well.
Yes!
My name is Timmy O'Toole.
I just turned ten years old.
Timmy, where are your parents?
I have no family.
I tried to enroll in school...
but Principal Skinner
turned me away...
because of my shabby clothes.
He's a liar.
The circumference
of the well is 34 inches.
So, unfortunately...
not one member
of our police force...
is slender enough
to rescue the boy.
By God, men,
you're a bunch of marshmallows.
Why don't you go, Chief?
Well, I'm too...
...important.
Timmy has told us...
his foot is trapped
under a rock.
Any attempt to pull him up
would snap him like a twig.
In desperation,
the city is considering...
more unorthodox solutions.
Grasping the child
firmly in his talons...
Socrates here will
fly him to safety.
Just watch.
I don't think
he's coming back.
With this hook
and this hunk of chocolate...
I'll land your boy...
and I'll clean him for free.
Although we can't reach the boy...
we can freeze him
with liquid nitrogen...
so that future generations
can rescue him.
Dear Lord, before we peel
the foil back from your bounty...
we ask you to watch over
little Timmy O'Toole...
trapped in that well.
Bart, what's wrong with you?
Yeah. Timmy is a real hero.
How do you mean, Dad?
Well, he fell down a well
and can't get out.
How does that
make him a hero?
Well, it's more than you did.
Channel 6's own Krusty the Clown...
has gathered members
of the entertainment community--
who normally steer clear
of fashionable causes--
for a video called...
''We're Sending Our Love
down the Well.''
I wanted to do something...
to help...
so I called my friend, Sting.
He said...
''When do you need me?''
I said, ''Thursday.''
He said, ''I'm busy.''
I said, ''Friday?''
He said...
''Friday's worse.''
Then he said,
''How about Saturday?''
I said, ''Fine.''
True story.
Yeah. I used to open
for Krusty in '69.
In fact, he fired me,
as I recall.
Oh, Sting.
But this isn't
about show business.
This is about some kid
down a hole...
or something.
We've gotta do what we can.
#There's a hole in my heart
as deep as a well #
# For that poor little boy
who sunk halfway to hell #
#Though we can't get him out
we'll do the next best thing #
#And go on TV
and sing, sing, sing #
#And we're sending our love
down the well #
#All the way down #
#We're sending our love
down the well #
# Down that well #
Krusty, what are your plans
for the royalties?
We got to pay for promotion,
shipping, distribution.
You know, those limos out back
aren't free.
Whatever's left,
we throw down the well.
Authentic Timmy O'Toole
baby teeth.
$6.00 a bag.
Step to the rear.
Plenty of room in the back.
## The Itchy and Scratchy Show ##
Hmm?
Ah.
Drop that microphone.
Drop it, boy!
This is a special report...
from Channel 6 News.
Disturbing news
from the old well...
where Timmy O'Toole...
has apparently taken
a turn for the worse.
It's very simple, Kent.
The child is reverting
to a feral or wolf-like state.
Here's an artist's conception.
Bart.
Ahem. I was trying
to gnaw my foot off, but...
I couldn't get through my sock.
Good night, everybody.
The thought
of a boy trapped in a well...
brought out the kindness
of the entire community.
When they find out you've
been fooling them...
they're gonna want to cut
you up with rusty razors.
And how are they
going to find out?
The police will catch you.
The police couldn't
catch a cold.
Maybe not,
but you're stupid enough...
to have left
a ''Bart Simpson'' label...
on that radio.
D'oh!
''...and Cinderella had...
the most beautiful gown
at the ball...
with eight
satin petticoats...
each more delicate
than the last.''
I think he's asleep.
Want a cup of coffee?
Okay.
Brave little guy.
Hey. Almost tripped
over this thing.
Ugh!
What did I do
to deserve this?
Help!
I fell down the well.
Tell us something
we don't know.
No, my name is Bart Simpson.
What are you doing
down there?
Look, I'll level with you.
There is no Timmy O'Toole.
It was just a prank
I was playing on everybody.
Well, you sure
fooled us, kid.
Hey, I got an idea
for a prank.
Let's go home...
and go to sleep.
Good one, Eddie.
Ha, ha. Great joke, guys.
Guys?
Your son...
is trapped down the well.
You must think we're
the worst parents in the world.
Yes, that's pretty much
the feeling down at the station.
Don't worry, son.
Just 'cause you're trapped...
doesn't mean you can't live
a full life.
I brought you your Krusty doll.
Ow!
Knock it off, you bald boob!
Don't make me
come down there!
Like to see you fit.
Why, you little...!
- Put a man on him.
I like the other boy.
So polite.
What are you doing
to save my baby boy?
We've located
a piece of machinery...
in Louisiana...
that could pop him out
lickety-split.
Why don't you get it?
We've got a budget problem.
Your boy picked a bad time
to fall down a well.
Had he done it at the start
of the fiscal year, no problemo.
You're telling me
the city won't pay...
to get a boy out of a well?
They would have for Timmy,
but your son...
he played us all for saps.
Mmm.
We've all been the victims
of a cruel hoax...
perpetrated by
a ten-year-old hooligan.
The time has come
for finger-pointing...
and most of them
are squarely aimed...
at the boy's parents.
It's not our fault.
We didn't want the boy.
He was an accident.
Homer!
Could you edit that last part?
Mr. Simpson, we're live.
D'oh!
# One plus one
plus three is five #
# Little Bart Simpson's
buried alive #
# He's so neat
He's so sweet #
# Now the rats
have Bart to eat... #
Hey, stop that!
Oh. Sorry, Lisa.
# How many days
until Bart croaks? #
# One, two, three, four... #
And our new number one hit
''I Do Believe We're Naked''
by Funky See, Funky Do...
replaces ''We're Sending Our Love
down the Well,''
which plunges
all the way down to number 97.
Ever since
I called for the rescue...
of that Simpson lad,
I have taken heat...
so I am flip-flopping.
I say let him stay down there.
Yeah, Shutton here.
Now, that's a story.
Bart, honey,
I made you an extra warm sweater...
you can wear
while you're down in the well.
Mom, it's too big.
You'll grow into it.
Homer!
I've done a lot of bad stuff
through the years.
Now I'm paying the price...
but there's so many things
I'll never get a chance to do--
smoke a cigarette...
use a fake I.D....
shave a swear word in my hair--
That's all I can stands.
I can't stands no more.
I'm going to get you
out of there myself.
Now, why didn't I think of that?
Agnes, we've got work to do.
This is Kent Brockman
with a special bulletin.
The Lincoln squirrel
has been assassinated.
We'll stay with the story
all night, if we have to.
What's going on?
It's an old-fashioned
hole digging.
By gar, it's been a while.
The canary.
Gas!
Out of the hole!
Gentlemen, this canary
died of natural causes.
Back in the hole!
Sting, you look tired.
Maybe you should take a rest.
Not while one
of my fans needs me.
Actually, I don't know if I've ever
heard Bart play your albums.
Shh! Marge,
he's a good digger.
Uhh!
Sting!
Mom!
Dad!
Bart, I've missed you so much.
Man, I was so scared.
Don't worry, son.
They're going to make sure...
no one ever falls down
this well again.
That should do it.
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net