##[Chorus Singing]
[Bell Ringing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[Tires Screeching]
Ah. I love these lazy Saturdays.
- It's Wednesday, Homer.
- [Screams] Work!
- [Tires Screeching]
- [Homer] Ah.
I love these real Saturdays.
They're so relaxing.
Not like that fake Saturday
that almost got me fired.
[Groans]
Is this all we're going
to do today?
Absolutely.
[Choking, Relieved Sigh]
You know, Homer, I'm starting
to realize life is short.
- It is?
- We have to make the most of the time we have.
- We do?
- Otherwise, we could wake up one day...
and realize we've wasted
our whole lives.
Oh, that.
[Laughing]
[Choking, Relieved Sigh]
Oh! Friends of the Library is holding
an historic manuscript viewing.
"Friends of the Library"?
Ooh! Ooh!
There's an azalea festival
at the public garden.
- I went yesterday.
- [Groans]
- Lenny really wanted to go.
- I'm tired of being cooped up
in this house all the time.
- Open a window.
- [Groans]
All right.
I hear ya, honey.
Change into something nice.
We're steppir out.
The police auction?
Can you believe it?
It's already been a year.
Wow, sweetheart.
Look at all this seized booty.
We could find the drug boat
of our dreams!
I don't want a drug boat.
Well, I bet there's drug dresses
and drug vacuum cleaners too.
All right. Listen up.
Listen up.
These prestigious wrought iron
security gates are bulletproof...
bombproof
and battering ram resistant.
- Now-
- Then what happened toJohnny D.?
He forgot to lock 'em.
Now, what am I bid?
- One kilo.
- Sold.
Ay, ay, ay, my gates. Ay!
Johnny C. gave me those.
Tough break, amigo.
[Laughing]
Next item up for bids.
Oh, no!
Oh, hey, look,
they're sellir your car, man.
Boy, it's nice.
Oh, I will totally kill
whoever buys L'il Bandit.
- Sold!
- Whoo-hoo!
[Imitating Engine Revving]
You bought a car
without consulting me?
I don't recall being consulted
when you bought that hat.
- I found this hat.
- Then what are you complaining about?
You got yours.
Mm, mm, mm.
- [Tires Screeching]
- [Marge Screams]
Homer, be careful.
Oh, yeah, you gotta be careful
when you do a trick like this.
[Tires Screeching]
- Stop, Homer! Stop it! Let me out!
- You're the boss.
I'm not getting back in this car
until you drive like a sane person.
- [Tires Screeching]
- Okay. Bye. Love ya.
You know, if you lived here,
you'd be home by now.
Mr. Hutz, I didn't know
you sold real estate.
You didn't? We should talk
more often, Marge.
You see, the law business
is a little slow...
and since most of my clients
wind up losing their houses...
this was a natural move for me.
Helping people find homes.
That must be really rewarding.
Yes, the money is good.
But the beauty is you get to
stay in the house until it's sold.
- Come on, guys. Let's go for a swim.
- [Dogs Barking]
Gee, this hotrod is souped up
six ways from Sunday.
Never had you figured
for a gearhead, Homer.
Oh, yeah.
I'm a real expert.
- What is that, a six-barrel Holley carb?
- You betcha.
- Edelbrock intakes?
- Nothir but.
- Myohoff lifters?
- Oh, yeah.
- I made that last one up.
- I see.
Selling real estate could be
just what I'm looking for.
I'd really like
to give it a try.
I don't know, Marge.
Trying is the first step towards failure.
- [Groans]
- Oh, boy.
I've got a lot to learn
before that license test.
Don't worry, Mom.
We'll help you study.
Of course, we'll have to
cut back on our own homework.
What in the heck
is a dwelling?
So, you're married, and you're looking
for your first house, Mr. and Mrs. -
- Superman.
- Oh!
Don't listen to my husband.
He's just an idiot.
I'm a veterinarian, and I need to keep
lots of sick animals in my house.
- Is that permitted?
- Not in my damn house.
Well, this neighborhood
is zoned R-3...
which allows dogs, cats,
phone-answering monkeys...
and, oh-
[Groans]
I'll never memorize
all this.
When I had to learn about the Magna Can'ta,
I made up a song.
## [Singing]
We should've
lived together first.
## [Singing]
You're all nuts.
## [Humming]
Easement!
- [Dings]
- Time's up.
You may now undermine
each other's confidence.
Yar! I nailed that one
about houseboats. Did you?
I passed!
[Both Cheer]
Way to go!
Mm-mmm.
Oh, thank you, Bart,
thank you, Lisa, for all your help.
What about me?
You didn't thank me.
- You didn't do anything.
- I like being thanked.
[Bells Jingle]
Welcome to
the big leagues, Marge.
There's over 50 years of real estate experience
right in this room.
And 42 of those years
are Gill's!
Marge,
it's a real pleasure.
You got any leads?
I need some leads.
- Please, help me.
- That's enough, Gill.
Don't drag her down
with you.
That's Cookie Kwan.
She's number one on the west side.
Hi, Marge!
Stay off the west side.
- And there's Nick Callahan.
- [Marge] A headset telephone?
I thought those only existed
in the movies.
- [Clanging]
- Boo-yah!
- Guess who sold the Whitman place?
- Good for you. Way to go.
I had been working on the Whitman place
for 21 years.
And now, Marge, I'd like
to welcome you to the family...
with your very own
red blazer.
[Gasps]
For me?
- Oh, ho, ho!
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Thank you, everybody.
I'm going to do my darnedest
to uphold the principles...
and ideals
this jacket represents.
- I give her a week.
- Are you guys talking about the west side?
No, Cookie. I swear it.
I'm scared of you.
- [Tires Screeching]
- Whoa, Dad, doesn't this car have seat belts?
Seat belts. [Scoffs]
They kill more people than they save.
That's not true.
You're thinking of air bags.
- There it is!
- [Both] Wow!
- Your own billboard!
- Check it out!
[Homer] Gee, that picture
makes your butt look big.
I thought so too,
but they said it sells.
Works for the Lumber King.
Lumber. We need lumber.
Excuse me, Mr. Szyslak.
Have you ever considered
selling your home?
What? No. Why? What? Why?
What have you heard?
Are you implying I'm in
some sort of financial trouble?
- No.
- Well, I am. Let me have that card.
And here we have a lovely
gourmet kitchen-
"with gas range,
central can opener...
and foam under flooring
for enanced standability."
Why, isn't this kitchen horribly cramped?
[Laughing]
- Why, yes, it is.
- Well, I suppose we could get used to it.
Yeah, but you shouldn't
have to settle.
You know, I've always loved
the house you're in now.
Really? Well, maybe
we should stay put.
- Thanks for your honesty, Marge.
- My pleasure.
If you ever need a prescription,
no questions asked-
[Clicks Tongue, Laughing]
Good shot, Barbara.
I can't believe it.
- A house with a bowling alley.
- Do you bowl often?
Actually,
this is our first time.
And I didn't really
care for it.
Oh, well, then you have to ask yourself,
is this the right house for you?
I suppose not. I guess we were just
captivated by this delightful plaque.
[Laughing]
[Tires Screech,
Engine Revving]
Hey, Skinner,
wanna drag race?
My high school sweetheart
was killed in a drag racing accident.
- Come on. It'll be fun.
- That's what Debbie Sue said.
- Come on, you stupid car.
- [Engine Grinding]
Just-Just go!
[Grinding Continues]
- No! That's L'il Bandit, and she's in pain.
- [Backfiring]
Screw the honor system.
My car needs me.
Hey, you're ruinir it
for the rest of us!
Stop! That's my car!
- [Tires Screeching]
- [Coughing, Sniffing]
Hey, that smells like regular.
She needs premium, dude!
Premium, dude!
Marge, I had a lot
of calls about you.
Customers love
your no-pressure approach.
Well, like we say,
"The right house for the right person."
Listen, it's time I let you in
on a little secret, Marge.
The right house
is the house that's for sale.
The right person is anyone.
But all I did
was tell the truth.
Of course you did.
But there's the truth...
and the truth!
- Let me show you.
- It's awfully small.
I'd say it's awfully cozy.
- [Marge] That's dilapidated.
- Rustic.
- That house is on fire.
- Motivated seller.
That's a beauty!
Forget about that house.
That's the Murder House.
Ooh, I remember.
Mrs. Astor was very lucky.
Well, no one expects you
to sell that house.
But you'd better
sell something.
Because cubicles
are for closers, Marge.
Anybody who doesn't sell a house
their first week gets fired.
I probably should've
mentioned that earlier.
I thought I'd do anything
to succeed in business.
But bending the truth?
I don't know.
Ah, so you don't have
that killer instinct. Big deal.
Yeah, honey. Even if you
don't succeed in the business world...
you're still the world's
greatest wife and mother.
[Scoffs]
So that's how you see me?
As a spineless, potato-cooking housewife
who can't compete in the real world?
[All]
Mm-hmm.
Well, I can too compete.
And I'm going to sell a house. End of story.
Kids, your mother's under
a lot of pressure.
Why don't we let her
clear the table in peace?
[Groans]
The first house
I have to show you is, um...
a handymars dream.
Mm-hmm.
Because it's so dilapidated.
[Groans]
Well, nothing's perfect. I sure hate to make you
come out here and not buy a house.
Now, slow down, Neddie.
The home buyer's course...
said always look inside the house
before buying.
Well, there it is.
Please don't tell anyone
how I live.
Hmm. It's awfully small.
Some people
would call it cozy.
- I guess it is sorta cute.
- But small. Really, really small.
Hmm. Wh-When you put it that way,
it does seem a bit small.
[Groans]
Well, that about does it
for houses in this area.
Wait.
What about that house?
That has a "for sale" sign.
Ooh, that's a dilly.
How about it, Marge?
Uh-
Oh, my-diddley-eye!
Will you look at this place!
[Gasps] And the price has been
slashed repeatedly.
It's sure built solid. The kids could scream
bloody murder, and no one would hear.
I'm just gonna spill my guts.
I love it to death.
I'm gonna give you a deposit
this minute.
Unless you can give me
a reason not to.
Is there anything else
we should know?
- There's the truth, and the truth!
- No! No!
If you don't sell a house,
you're fired, fired, fired.
[Screaming]
Well, Marge?
No. There is absolutely nothing else
to tell you about this house.
That's good enough for me!
[Screams] Purple drapes!
All my life I've wanted purple drapes!
[Screams]
- [Clanging]
- Attention.
Ding-ding, ding-ding, ding-ding.
Listen up, everybody.
- Marge Simpson sold her first house.
- How about that?
- The Murder House!
- Wow, now, that's something!
Boo-yah! Wow, you must've
told a whopper to unload that death trap.
What'd you use, Marge?
The old buff and bluff?
The Hail Murray?
The Susquehanna Shuffle?
Huh? [Clicks Tongue] Huh? [Clicks Tongue]
Huh? [Laughing]
No. No. No tricks.
It was salesmanship.
That's all.
Sure, Marge.
"Salesmanship."
- But it was.
- Sure, Marge. "Was."
Just because everyone who lived
in that house was hacked to bits...
doesn't mean
the Flanders will be.
- I guess you're right.
- Who cares?
Whatever happens,
as our newest closer...
- you're entitled to wear the coveted closing blazer.
- [Applause]
And you get a third wall
for your cubicle.
- But I earned that wall.
- Don't push your luck, pal.
You're hangir on
by a thread.
Well, I brought this wall
from home.
[Tires Screeching]
[Laughs]
Okay.
Baldy boy hits wire,
head comes off...
L'il Bandit rolls
to a gentle stop.
Everybody wins.
Man, the air feels good
on my neck.
Whoo! Gum ball!
Oh, why do I even bother?
[Car Approaching]
I told that idiot
to slice my sandwich. Ow!
Wow, honey. You sold a house
and got rid of the Flanders.
- What's for dinner?
- Well, neighboreenos, I guess this is good-bye.
Oh, I better make this quick,
or I'm gonna start blubbering like a baby.
Yeah, me too.
Let me know if you need any help.
- Now that you mention it, we could use-
- It was just an expression.
[Groans]
Good-bye, Ned.
If the slightest thing goes wrong
with that house, call me right away.
Or you can beep me. In fact,
why don't you just stay here tonight?
- We'll go to a hotel.
- Oh, you're sweet to offer...
but we're all just so tired...
we just wanna get to our new house
and rest in peace.
- So long, Simpsons.
- [All] Bye!
[Shuddering]
That old Flanders place
gives me the creeps.
## [Singing, Screams]
- Give me my car, fatty.
- [Shouts]
This is my car! And I'm not fat!
It's glandular!
- Right.
- [Shouting]
Ohhh!
You've got to tell them
the truth, Marge.
The truth!
Hello? Anyone home?
[Screaming]
Oh, hi, Marge.
I guess we gave you quite a start.
We were painting Todd's room red-
pretty messy work-
and then we came out here
to take a break.
- Must've dozed off.
- Red room.
Red room. Over there.
Well, I'm just glad
you're okay.
[Sighs]
And I have something
to tell you.
[Grunting]
[Tires Screeching]
- Stop it!
- [Grunts]
Come on.
Let's hear that snap.
[Brakes Screeching]
[Grunts]
- [Engine Revving]
- [Shouts]
- [Grunts]
- You-You-
Ow!
- You're... going... down, punk!
- Ow! Ow! Ow!
Whoa, this is so dangerous.
- Yeah, you're right. D'oh!
- [Grunting]
- Why, you-
- Wha-What the-
- This is Wiggum reporting a 318-
waking a police officer.
- [Siren Wailing]
[Gasps]
This is the Murder House?
- Mm-hmm.
- [Gasps]
You mean the infamous
Jealous Jockey Murders?
- Mm-hmm.
- [Gasps]
Of course! This must be
where he dropped the dagger.
And this is the butler's pantry,
where Mrs. Astor concealed herself.
And right here's where
they found the torso heap-
in front of
our very own fireplace!
Oh, just think, Neddie.
We're part of Springfield history.
- Look, Daddy. I'm the jealous jockey.
- I'm a torso.
I'm glad you're not mad.
But I lied to you...
and I won't feel right
until I return your deposit.
We appreciate the offer, Marge,
but I think we're gonna be very happy here.
- [Grunting]
- [All Screaming]
[Both Screaming]
- [Siren Wailing]
- [Screaming]
Uh, Marge- [Chuckles]
you still got that deposit check?
- Oh! Oh, wow.
- [Groaning]
- Lucky thing we landed on this bubble wrap.
- [Popping]
- Hey, quit hoggir.
- Oh, I'm badly hurt.
A smashed hotrod, a wrecked police cruiser,
a destroyed house!
I've had it with
your renegade ways, Simpson.
- You're a loose cannon.
- But l-
And what really fries me
is you returned his check!
I'm sorry, Mr. Hutz,
but I just can't lie to people.
[Laughing]
You're one of a kind, Marge...
and nobody deserves this
more than you.
[Groans]
Well, I'm proud of you, Mom.
You refused to compromise your integrity.
Yeah. You did the right thing,
eventually.
Still, it would've been nice
to bring home at least one paycheck.
Oh, you will, honey.
You will.
$300 for doing nothing?
I feel like such a crook.
Don't worry.
Gets easier every week.
[Kisses]
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net