##[Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
Marge, stop this
crazy thing!
We got the popcorn.
Did you get Waiting to Exhale?
Well, they put us on the
Waiting to Exhale waiting list...
but they said
don't hold your breath.
Did you get Emma?
- Did ya, did ya, did ya, huh?
- Whoa, whoa.
Calm down, little lady.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
- [Chuckles] No.
- What did you get?
Something very close,
exactly along those lines.
- A Clint Eastwood, Lee Marvin
shoot-'em-up western!
- [Both Groaning]
So prepare yourself for the bloody mayhem
and unoly carnage...
ofJoshua Logars
Raint Your Wagon.
With blood, I bet.
[Both Laughing]
[Whinnies]
Hey!
That's a pretty sorry lookir
wagon you got there, mister.
I reckon it could use
a coat of paint.
Well, what are we
waitir for?
##[Country]
## [Singing]
## [All Singing]
##[Continues]
[Shrieks]
They're singing!
They're singing, Marge.
Why aren't they killing each other?
Yeah, their guns
are right there.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here comes Lee Marvin.
Thank God.
He's always drunk and violent.
Uh, what the hell
is goir on in my town?
We're just
paintir this wagon.
You got a problem with that?
As a matter of fact, I do.
You missed a spot.
Well, grab a brush
and join in.
##[Country]
## [Singing]
## [Vocalizing]
- [Man] Yeehaw!
- Mmm. Who knew that Lee Marvin
could do such marvelous splits?
He's dreamy.
Oh, why did they have to screw up a perfectly
serviceable wagon story...
- with all that fruity singing?
- I thought it was toe-tappir fun.
Singing is the lowest form
of communication.
Homer, you sing
all the time.
No, I don't.
I hate to rhyme.
## [Singing]
## [Ends]
And a one, and a two,
and a three-
## [Singing]
##[Continues]
Hello!
Human Fly here.
Come on! I stayed up all night
dyeing my underwear.
Extra, extra! Be Sharps
sing on rooftop!
What?
Give me one of those!
Wait a minute. There's nothing in here
about the Be Sharps!
- Come back here!
- Ha-ha!
##[Singing Continues,
Indistinct]
- It's been done.
- [Tires Screech]
- Pretty, huh, Chief?
- It sure is, Lou. It sure is.
- Get the tear gas.
- ## [Continues]
## [Ends]
[Applause, Cheering]
[Glass Smashing]
Dad, we can't let this
happen to Belle. Do something.
Don't you worry, Son.
My friends! Stop!
We could tear it down...
but we'd be tearing down
a part of ourselves.
## [Singing]
## [Continues]
## [Jazz]
## [Singing]
- ## [Continues]
- [Springs]
## [Singing]
## [Both Singing]
## [Continues]
[Springs]
[Whistles]
## [Ends]
- [Horn Honks]
- [Belches]
## [Singing]
[Gagging]
Eep.
[Both Yelling, Whooping]
- [Squeaking]
- [Gasps] It's so thick!
[Sucking]
[Coughing]
Your turn, Bart.
[Sucking]
[Coughs]
Whoa! That's good Squishy.
[Groaning]
What's it like, Bart?
Bart? Bart?
- [Babbling Gibberish]
- Give me that!
[Slurps]
[Moans, Yelps]
Okay. We're young, rich
and full of sugar. What'll we do?
Let's go crazy
Broadway-style!
[Both]
Yeah!
## [Singing]
- New York is thataway, man.
- Thanks, kid.
## [Singing Ends]
- ##[Show Music Continues]
- Whoa. Wow.
- [Cats Yowling, Hissing]
- Huh? Huh?
Mmm! Free goo.
[Milhouse]
Hey! Don't bogart that Squishy!
[Gulping] I don't know where
you magic pixies came from...
but I like your pixie drink.
- ##[Continues]
- [Laughing]
[Groaning]
Oh, my head.
## [Singing]
[Chuckles]
## [Vocalizing]
## [Singing]
Bye.
## [Ends]
Whether igloo, hut or lean-to
or a geodesic dome...
there's no structure I have been to
which I'd rather call my home.
Hello.
[Yelps]
## [Singing]
- ## [Continues]
- [Chuckles] That's okay.
- [Screams]
- ## [Continues]
## [Singing]
D'oh!
[All Singing]
## [Ends]
[Sighs]
Everything really wrapped up nicely.
Hmm.
Much quicker than usual.
I guess we've learned
that happiness is wherever you find it.
And we've all found happiness,
every one of us.
- [Apu Crying]
- [TV Clicks On]
Hey, what's that sound?
[Crying Continues]
## [Singing]
## [Ends]
Hey, he's not happy at all!
He lied to us through song!
I hate when
people do that!
- ##[Drumroll]
- [Announcer] Live from Springfield...
the entertainment capital
of this state...
the Krusty Komeback Special!
##[Riano]
## [Singing]
[Sobbing]
[Applause]
- I love you, Krusty.
- Quiet!
Maybe we were wrong
about Burns on this one.
Are you sure you want
to go through with this, sir?
You do have a very full
wardrobe as it is.
Yes. But not completely full.
For you see-
## [Singing]
## [Continues]
## [Ends]
- I really like the vest.
- I gathered, yeah.
We gotta get the dogs
out of there!
## [Singing]
- Okay.
- ## [Continues]
## [Ends]
Oh, I knew I should
have shut that window.
## [Singing]
[Clicking]
## [Continues]
Bye.
## [Singing]
## [Ends]
Very well. We will now hear
suggestions for the, uh...
disbursement of the, uh,
two million dollars.
Don't you mean
three million dollars?
Of course.
How silly of me.
[Whistles]
You know, a town with money's
a little like the mule with a spinning wheel.
No one knows how he got it,
and danged if he knows how to use it.
- [Laughter]
- [Chuckles] Mule.
The name's Lanley,
Lyle Lanley...
and I come before you good people tonight
with an idea.
Probably the greatest-
Ah, it's not for you.
It's more of
a Shelbyville idea.
Now wait just a minute.
We're twice as smart
as the people of Shelbyville.
Just tell us your idea,
and we'll vote for it.
All right.
I tell you what I'll do.
I'll show you my idea.
- I give you the Springfield Monorail!
- [All Gasping]
I've sold monorails to Brockway, Ogdenville
and North Haverbrook...
and by gum,
it put them on the map!
Well, sir, there's nothir on earth
like a genuine, bona fide...
electrified,
six-car monorail.
- What'd I say?
- Monorail!
- What's it called?
- [Together] Monorail!
- That's right, monorail!
- [All] Monorail. Monorail. Monorail.
## [Singing]
## [Continues]
- ## [All Singing]
- ## [Continues]
## [Singing]
## [Ends]
Monorail!
Mono-
D'oh!
Hymns here! I got hymns here!
Get 'em while they're holy!
Fresh from God's brain to your mouth!
[Sinister Chuckle]
And now please rise
for our opening hymn...
uh, "In the Garden of Eden"...
by I. Ron Butterfly.
## [Rock]
## [Singing]
- ##[Organ Continues]
- [Sinister Chuckle]
Hey, Marge, remember when we
used to make out to this hymn?
- [Giggles] Shh! Shh! Shh!
- [Chuckling]
## [Continues]
- ##[Continues]
- Wait a minute. This sounds like rock and/or roll.
## [Ends]
##[Rousing]
## [Singing]
## [Continues]
## [Ends]
## [Singing]
- Actually, we're done.
- Done, done.
- And not a moment too soon.
- Oh, okay then.
Well, then I got no beef with you.
[Grunts]
- Okay, who wants dinner?
- [All Clamoring]
Well, let's get eatir.
- ## [Humming]
- [Gunshots]
All right, all right.
Sorry.
##[Theme Music]
- [Gunshots]
- ##[Stops]
[Snake] Yo! I told you to stop
the music, dudes. I'm serious!
[Crickets Chirping]
##[Resumes]
- [Snake] Oh, oh, oh! You're so not listening!
- [Gunshots]
[Crickets Chirping]
##[Resumes, Quietly]
[Snake]
Okay, I hear that.
- I hear that, dudes!
- [Gunshot]
- ##[Mellow Instrumental]
[Snake]
You too, Gracie music dude! Guh!
www.tvsubtitles.net