##[Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
Yuck.
Salisbury soup again?
My joe isn't sloppy enough.
And talk about weak coffee.
I'll take that.
What are they doing
with our 45 cents?
I bought my lunch
at the gas station.
It's the kind John Glenn eats
when he's not in space.
[Hissing]
Wow! Just like the commercial.
There's a brainteaser on the back.
"Professor Provolone's Picto-Puzzle."
[Martin]
That's a tough one.
- Got it!
- Is this it?
Excellent, Milhouse.
- How 'bout this?
- Nice work, Bart.
How 'bout you, Lisa?
I'll get it in a second.
Don't worry.
Oh! Of course.
It's-
[Whispering]
Yeah! Champion of the world!
Answer this, Professor.
[Grunting]
- Hey! Some of us are still trying to solve it.
- Just you.
Maybe I can't concentrate
because of all your cooties!
It's called lice.
And it's nothing to be ashamed of.
[Scratching]
- [School Bell Rings]
- [Cheering]
Okay, let's see.
It's not Egyptian.
It's not Prince's names.
Uh-
- Want a hint?
- I don't need a hint, Ralph.
But you're suffering.
[Groans]
So, Lisa.
Did you get that brainteaser yet?
For your information,
none of your business.
You look tired.
Are ya tired, Lisa?
[Sighs] If you're suggesting
I stayed up all night...
trying to solve
that childish puzzle...
you're right.
- [Clatter]
- Ah. Now I can't remember my combination.
Look at my "aggieculture" project.
It's a piece of a cow.
[Gasps] The project.
I forgot all about it.
Very nice, Janie.
Good use of pipe cleaners, Becky.
[Buzzing]
Don't open it, Ralph.
I'll just give you a C-minus.
Yea!
- Not finished, Lisa?
- I'm finished. I just got to-
[Grunts]
There. It's a pig!
It's an eraser with pushpins.
And a spring for his curly tail.
[Laughs]
Oink, oink, oink.
This is terrible at best.
I'm surprised at you, Lisa.
Me too.
Oh, it looks like somebody's
"hoggir Dazs" ice cream.
[Laughs]
I should write this down.
- More comir.
- [Door Dings]
Um, I'm looking for something
in an after-dinner burrito.
You'll have it in 45 seconds, sir.
[Beeping]
To pass the time,
please enjoy this novelty pen.
Why would I want to
look at a pen with a-[Gasps]
Oh, no!
Her clothes are coming off!
[Chuckles] Hey, you know
who would love this?
Men.
Five, four, three, two, one.
Liftoff!
[Moans]
Look at this mess.
Where is that elderly old man?
Old man! Old m-
[Screams]
Hey, look. A freezer man!
- Wait a minute. There is a note.
- Oh.
"I have frozen myself so I may live to see
the wonders of the future.
"Thaw me out when robot wives
are cheap and effective.
P.S. Please alter my pants
as fashion dictates."
##[Saxophone]
## [Off-key]
Now you're swingir, honey.
## [Scatting Off-key]
Darn it!
Oh, no! No, no!
The George Raft look is dead.
I wanted Audie Murphy!
If you would just apologize to Louie,
you could get your hair cut the way you want.
No apology!
Not until he admits he's a jerk!
Mom, I think something's
wrong with me.
I can't do anything right lately.
You're just having a bad day.
I had one last week.
I burned the roast.
My cake fell.
And I ran out of butter, so I had to spray
the English muffins with PAM.
Maybe you're just
a lousy cook. Ow!
I'll go get the Bactine.
It can't just be a bad day.
I feel like I'm getting
dumber by the minute.
Oh, ain't no big deal. All Simpsons start to lose
their smarts around your age.
- What are you talking about?
- Well, I'll show ya.
Follow me.
Wow! Dad was a good speller?
Oh, your dad used to
be smart as a monkey.
Then his mind started
gettir lazy...
and now he's dumb as a chimp.
- Grampa!
- Hey, I am too.
Your brother's comir along nicely.
Look at Bart's homework.
Back when he was your age,
he was smart as a chimp.
[Gasps]
This is just two years ago!
That's right.
Then the Simpson genes kicked in.
This is crazy. Just because you and Dad
and Bart went downill...
doesn't mean
it's gonna happen to me.
- Does it?
- Sure!
But it doesn't mean
you can't live a long and pointless life.
[Groans]
Dear Log:
Can it be true?
Do all Simpsons go through
a process of"dumbening"?
Wait. That's not how
you spell "dumbening."
Wait. "Dumbening" isn't even a word!
[Groans]
I've got to find out more.
[Voices Shouting]
[Grunting, Laughing]
That makes 22 to 16.
Time is running out.
[Dr. Hibbert Laughing] So you're worried
about your genes, huh?
Well, does it hurt
when you go like this?
- No.
- Then will you turn this projector on for me?
I think the film should answer
all your questions.
##[Introductory]
[McClure Narrating] Have you ever
wondered why fat parents have fat children...
or why Chinese parents
have Chinese children?
It's no coincidence. It's because of...
D.N.A.
Hi. I'm Troy McClure.
- [Alarm Blares]
- [Men Shouting]
You may remember me from such medical films
as Alice Doesrt Live Anymore...
and Mommy, What's Wrong
with that Mars Face?
But Mr. McClure, what is D.N.A.?
What the- Oh, hi, Billy.
Let's find out together.
D.N.A. is God's recipe
for making you.
##[Soundtrack Music Stuttering]
You take a dash of Dad,
a pinch of Mom...
then we bake for nine months, and-
Mmm. That's good Billy.
Mr. McClure,
what does D.N.A. stand for?
##[Stuttering]
That didn't answer anything.
- I need more information.
- Would you like to see it again?
Isn't there any way
I can change my D.N. A...
like sitting on the microwave?
Not according to any movie
I've ever seen.
I'm afraid you're stuck
with your genes, Lisa.
[Chuckling]
- [Door Dings]
- Hi, frozen body.
- [Thumps]
- Hmm. He's got a lob...
but I don't hear a dob.
- [Thumps]
- Oh. Uh, there it is.
You're lucky he's still alive.
This freezer
is an attractive nuisance.
Just look at all that ice cream.
It's damn near irresistible.
Well, we better leave him in there.
- Moving him now could kill him and tire us out.
- Check it out!
- A freezer geezer.
- Please, young customers...
ignore the frozen gentleman,
and return to your impulse buying.
Aw, but we wanna stare
at the ice dude.
- We'll give ya a buck.
- No. This is a convenience store...
not a freak show.
$1.20?
- ##[Carnival]
- Come one, come all.
See the amazing frozen man.
Also gaze at the Frito
found in a bag of Doritos.
Marvel at the floor
that just won't come clean!
Dear Log: My worst fears
have been confirmed.
I've hit my mental and creative peak
at the tender age of eight.
What will my life be like
after I descend into mediocrity?
- [Clank]
- [Laughing]
Oh.
- [Clank]
- [Laughing]
Well, Ralph seems happy enough.
Maybe I should just give up now
and settle into a mindless, happy stupor.
[Announcer]
We now return to...
When Buildings Collapse
on nonstop Fox.
- [Building Collapses]
- [Homer And Bart Laughing, Cheering]
- [Bart And Homer Whooping]
- [Groans]
Hey, Lise, wanna join us?
Room for one more.
We're watchir the TV.
[Narrator]
Man has always loved his buildings.
But what happens when
the buildings say, "No more"?
##[Triumphant]
[Homer] Yes!
[Laughs]
- [Both Laughing]
- [Homer] Oh! Ooh!
Yeah!
[Laughing]
[Cheering]
[Homer]
I didn't think it was gonna fall over.
- Yea!
- Whoo! Whoo! Whoo!
##[Ends]
The best part was when
the buildings fell down.
Yeah. Ha.
Maybe people got hurt.
Hey, yeah.
[Chortling]
[Announcer]
And now, a Channel 6 editorial reply.
[Singsong]
Boring!
[Announcer]
And now, When Surgery Goes Wrong.
All right.
Sounds good.
##[Carnival]
- Behold the can of mystery!
- [Crowd Murmurs]
The label vanished many years ago.
What strange wonders lie inside?
Treasure, dog food?
Whoa! Some things man
is not meant to know.
[Rod And Todd Reading]
"Show me your"-
- Hey!
It says, "Show me your tie."
It's cute. Come on. Let's go.
Me and Frostillicus
go back a long way.
I used to share a bathroom
with Frostillicus.
In fact, I got
a real funny story about that.
Actually, it's not so much funny
as it is long.
It seems that
there was this-
Whoo! What a gold mine!
[Gasps]
Oh, my goodness!
## [Whistling]
Boy, seeing that
stomach surgery made me hungry.
Marge, we need
5,000 c.c.'s of snacks, stat!
No snacks. Dinner will be ready
in three minutes.
[All Three Groaning]
If she started dinner three minutes earlier,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
Relax, Lise.
Dad and I always have a plan "B."
[Gulping, Chewing]
- Pretty neat, huh?
- But those candy bars are all squished and melted.
- Wha-
[Muffled]
Come on, Lisa. Join your family.
[Whimpering]
- [Kids Crying]
- Quit it!
Quit it.
[Southern Accent]
Quit-You kids knock it off.
Mama's watchir her stories.
Hi, honey.
It's me, your husband, Ralph.
Hey, angel pie.
Can you drive me down to the "liberry"?
I wanna rent us up some movies.
[Groaning]
Wesley, get mama's pryir bar.
Easy does it now. Easy.
Little more.
Get- Right- Back-
- [Grunts]
- I'll get your coat.
- No!
- No what?
- I don't wanna turn out that way.
- What way, angel pie?
Like you!
Lisa, come on.
Your tomato soup
is getting a skin on top.
Fine. She doesn't get her skin.
Lisa insulted us, Mom.
She thinks she is so great.
I'll dance on her grave.
- Bart!
- What? Oh, napkin. Right.
Dear Log: It won't be long now
before my mind melts...
into a soft, Simpsony sludge.
Soon, the arts and literature
I love will be replaced...
by talk radio and vulgar mud flaps.
It's time to give my brain
its last meal.
Oh, Kenny. Look at the interplay
of light and shadow.
It's so luminous and vibrant!
[Laughs]
Thanks, Lisa. I painted that one.
[Lowers Voice]
The real one's in my garage.
##[Violin]
Hmm. Sounds like
she's hitting a baby with a cat.
You have to listen
to the notes she's not playing.
[Scoffs]
I can do that at home.
[Door Dings]
Son, I represent a group of oil tycoons
who make foolish purchases.
We already bought us
a stained glass bathrobe...
and the world's fattest racehorse.
Now we need your Ice Man.
Oh, no.
I could never sell him.
He's like a frozen father to me.
- How much for just the head?
- [Cracking]
[Jasper Moans]
By gum, it worked.
I've awakened in the future.
"Moon Pie."
What a time to be alive.
Hey, who unplugged my freezer?
Return to your state
of living death at once, sir.
Is that you, Apu?
Whoa! Time has ravaged
your once-youthful looks.
- [Door Dings]
- [Grunts]
Ah, well, Sanjay.
That is the end of our freak show.
We must relinquish
the giddy glamour of show business...
and return to the humble pleasures
of the neighborhood shopkeeper.
- Hmm.
##[Disco]
Time traveler discount?
- Come on in!
- ##[Disco Continues]
- Great set.
- Oh, thanks.
But the crowd kept looking at me like I was
using too many augmented ninths.
Aw, they just came
for the buffalo wings.
But you really got through to me.
Oh, good. I figure if you've got
something special to say...
you have to share it with the world.
Yeah. While you still can.
Thanks.
[Running Footsteps]
Damn. That felt like a sale.
I'm sorry, little girl.
We don't just put people on TV.
Unless, of course,
they're replying to an editorial.
Uh, I am!
I'm strongly opposed to...
Proposition, uh, 305!
You're against discount
bus fares for war widows?
- Uh, you bet I am.
- Okay. Makeup.
I'm getting worried about Lisa.
She's been gone for hours.
If I were her, I'd be buying me
a great big chocolate apology cake.
Authorities believe
the wave of towel snappings will get worse...
before it gets better.
And now, with an editorial reply,
here's a small girl.
Hello. My name is Lisa Simpson.
[Gasps]
- I'm supposed to talk to you
about Rroposition 305.
- Moochir war widows.
But I have something
more important to say.
For reasons beyond my control, I will soon
become vapid, sluggish and slow-witted.
So before that happens, I want to share some
things with you that have meant a lot to me.
What is she doir out there?
I'll cut off her mike.
No, no, no. Let her speak.
I'm trying to get fired.
And please don't deprive yourself
of wonderful books like...
To Kill a Mockingbird, Harriet the Spy
and Yertle the Turtle...
possibly the best book
ever written on the subject of turtle stacking.
She's got that right.
Beauty is all around us,
and not just in pageants and parlors.
You can find it
in the swirl of galaxies...
or the swirl in the center
of a sunflower.
That's a good idea.
Let's go out for some frosty swirls.
Homer, your daughter
is pouring her heart out.
- We'll tape it.
- Why's she saying all this. Is she dying?
Oh, she's just upset 'cause I told her
her brairs turning to mush.
You know, on account of
the Simpson gene.
Simpson gene?
That's just foolishness!
No. Baldness too.
So please, I beg you,
don't take your brain for granted.
It's the best friend
you'll ever have.
[Clears Throat]
Little girl... likes her brain.
What's your opinion?
[Scoffs]
Simpson gene.
Somebody's gotta
set that girl straight...
and I know how to do it.
Marge, get me your address book...
four beers and my conversation hat.
- [Snoring]
- Lisa. Lisa, honey, wake up.
[Yawns]
Why bother?
Because your father
has a big surprise for you.
- I'm adopted?
- Better. Come look.
Lisa, it's me, Daddy.
Your father.
I rounded up every Simpson
in the tri-city area...
so I can prove to you there's nothing wrong
with the Simpson genes.
This is your great-uncle Chet.
Go ahead, Chet.
Tell her what you do.
I run an unsuccessful
shrimp company.
Oh. But...
you run it, right?
- Oh, yeah.
- Okay.
Uh, this is your
second cousin Stanley.
Um, I shoot birds at the airport.
Everybody hates birds, right?
[Whimpers]
Well, you look pretty successful.
Thanks. I play
a millionaire at parties.
At least I'd like to.
You probably should have
researched this first, eh, Dad?
- What about you?
- Well, sir, I step in front of cars and sue the drivers.
I beg celebrities for money.
- I'm a prison snitch.
- Jug band manager.
- My legs hurt.
- [Groans]
Oh, Lisa's right.
We're nothing but a big bunch of losers.
Show's over, folks. Go home!
- What about our five bucks?
- You get it after you leave. Now get outta here.
[Voices Mumbling]
Wait a minute, Homer. You didn't ask
everybody. What about the women?
Fine, fine.
What do you do, "Dr. Simpson"?
- Doctor?
- That's right.
I'm Chief of Complicated Surgery
at the InvasiCare Clinic.
That means you went
to college, right?
You have to if you want to be
an architect.
Or an environmental lawyer.
Or Regional Sales Coordinator
for the third largest distributor...
of bunk and trundle beds.
Oh! Did you hear that, Lisa?
So all the Simpson women
turn out okay.
That's right, sweetie.
The defective Simpson gene is on the "Y"
chromosome, so only men are affected.
[Both Growling]
- Yea!
So I'm not doomed!
Oh, Dad, I've never been happier
to be your daughter!
Oh, thanks, honey.
Remember...
there's nothing that says you can't be
a Simpson and a success.
Unless you're a man.
So wait a minute.
This means I'm gonna be a failure?
Yes, Son.
A spectacular failure.
[Grunts]
Dearest Log: I am me again!
And I feel like
there's nothing I can't do.
Except this stupid braintea-
[Gasps]
I got it! Whoo-hoo!
I mean, splendid.
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net