##[Chorus Singing]
[Bell Ringing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
Ooh.
[Grunting]
Stupid heater!
Don't make me come in there.
Why do you always wait until
Christmas Eve to do your shopping?
The crowds are just beastly.
You know me, Marge.
I crave the hustle and bustle.
[Grunting]
[Grunts]
- [Chattering]
- Homer, look at this mob.
The good toys
are probably all gone.
[Chuckles] Oh, Santa's got
a little trick up his sleeve.
Attention shoppers, Register 9 is now
open for your shopping convenience.
Sorry, these are for display only.
This has been recalled.
Ooh, Bart would like this.
We're out of these.
- Out? But I just-
- Register 9 is now closed.
[Giggles]
Hey, kids.
I made your favorite cookies.
Christmas trees for the girls
and bloody spearheads for Bart.
Aw, thanks, Mom.
[Groaning]
This year's tree is just perfect.
That old aluminium one was so fake.
I couldn't agree more.
From now on,
it's plastic all the way.
- [Footsteps]
- [Bells Jingling]
- Bart, did you hear that?
- Could it be?
- [Screaming]
- Whoa!
[Laughing]
[Whimpering]
Come on, kids.
Let's try the lights.
[Electrical Crackling]
It's "craptacular."
[Bleating]
Hocus-pocus.
Mucous "pukeous."
My powers of
deduction tell me...
you're getting a handmade
sweater, possibly yellow.
Mom, make him stop!
Bart, put down
that yellow sweater.
Nobody's going near their presents
until 7:00 tomorrow morning.
- [All Groaning]
- 7:00 a.m., no earlier.
And you can't set your alarm clocks,
'cause I've got 'em.
- For once, we're gonna
celebrate Christmas as a family.
- [Knocking]
Hello? Anybody home?
Twelve glasses of water.
That will wake me up nice and early.
And I'll have a big head start
on opening presents.
- Pure genius.
- You didn't invent that, Bart.
The Indians used to drink water
to wake up early for their attacks.
[Groans]
It's always about the Indians, isn't it, Lise?
Dear Santa, if you bring me
lots of good stuff...
I promise not to do anything bad...
between now
and when I wake up, amen.
Ow! I'll kill you.
[Water Dripping]
[Dripping Continues]
[Screaming]
[Thunderclap]
- There you go.
- Get him up there.
[Crowd Cheering]
Go! Go! Go! We're number one!
- Give me a "P"!
- "P"!
Go! Go! Go!
"P"! "P"! "P"!
[Chuckles]
Worked like a charm.
[Groaning]
[Toilet Flushing]
[Sighs]
How sweet it is.
Hmm.
[Laughing]
Oh, Aunt Selma.
Always good for a fin.
Whoa, here we go.
[Gasps]
The Inferno Buster 3000!
Oh, I knew Santa wouldn't
have time to check that list twice.
Oh, yeah.
- Cool.
- [Siren Wailing]
Uh-oh.
Eek!
[Screaming]
Who designed this house?
[Bleating]
Homer. Homer,
I think I heard a noise.
[Bleating]
[Breathing]
Knock it off.
Snow covers all.
Pure, white snow.
[Gasps, Gulps]
I gotta get back to bed.
- [Marge Gasps] What happened?
- [Gasps]
[Stammering]
Where's Christmas?
Lisa, where's Christmas?
Bart, what were you
doing outside?
I don't know how
to tell you this, but...
I came down a little early, and...
uh, well, uh...
I saw a burglar
and he was- he took-
[Sobbing]
he got all our stuff.
Including the tree.
[Sobbing]
- We were robbed?
- [Sobbing] Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh.
- [Gasping]
- How could somebody-
I know!
[Sobbing]
Can... we... skip... church?
Now, uh, what did this
Christmas thief look like?
Well, he had a glass eye,
a wooden leg...
- a big scar on his cheek.
- Anything unusual?
Hooks for hands, uh- Oh, he was
wearing a striped convict's shirt.
He was carrying a big sack
with a dollar sign on it.
[Scoffs]
Classic burglar.
Aw, cheer up.
We'll catch this guy.
- Uh, chief-
- What? You can't rule it out.
- [Door Shuts]
- Well, there's no easy way to say it, kid.
God hates us.
Hey, since when is Christmas
just about the presents?
Arert we forgetting the true meaning
of this day? The birth of Santa.
Bart's absolutely right.
This is the one day that
shouldn't be about material things.
Hey, why don't we walk over to
Grampa's and cheer up the old folks?
- That will make us feel better.
- Oh, okay.
But they'll have to be pretty damn
miserable to make me happy.
##[Christmas Carols On Stereo]
Looks like the Flanders
are having a nice Christmas.
Oh, yeah?
We'll show 'em.
Come on, kids. Pretend
we got new cross-country skis.
[Honking]
Merry Christmas, Simpsons!
[Laughing]
That's not as fun as it looks.
Nothing could be as fun as that looks.
Hey, look what I got, Bart!
A Tickle Me Krusty!
- [Goofy Laugh] Hey, kid,
get your finger out of there.
- [Laughing]
- Ow!
- [Marge] Homer!
##[Christmas Rop On Stereo]
Lisa, you promised they'd be miserable.
What the hell's going on?
Oh, the pharmaceutical man come by
and he shot us full of Christmas cheer.
[Laughing]
I can't feel nothing
below my chin.
##[Continues]
[Squeaking]
Ah, sounds like you're having
a rough Christmas, Homer.
You know what I blame this
on the breakdown of?
- Society.
- Yeah.
You're right, Moe.
You're always Moe.
Homer, look.
Your house is on TV.
You take that back, Barney.
- No, he's right, Homer.
- Stay out of this, old man.
Dateline, Kent Brockman. I'm here at
the scene of the Christmas burglary...
where a creature
was stirring last night...
and what he was stirring
was up trouble.
Is your husband
or lover here, ma'am?
No, my husband is...
at church.
Aw, that's my girl.
I love you, Marjorie.
- Yeah, she's quite a gal.
- You shut up.
So when you realized Christmas
was ruined, how did you feel?
How do you think I felt?
Absolutely devastated.
"Absolutely devastated."
The words of
a heartbroken mother.
For there will be no
fire truck for little Bart...
no sweater for little Lisa...
no Cajun sausage for little Homer.
- [Wails]
- So while you're home today...
eating your sweet,
sweet holiday turkey...
I hope you'll all choke
just a little bit.
Lousy doormat.
Homer, you won't believe
what's happened. It's a miracle.
Aw, Marge, I don't wanna hear
any more about that silver polish.
- Surprise!
- [Cheering]
- ## [Christmas Carol]
- People saw our story on the news...
and they've opened
their hearts to us.
Yar, we just gave
what we could.
Does anyone have
change for a button?
- Wow, this really restores your faith in-
- ##[Continues]
Lisa! Do you have to practice
that stupid song now?
- Sorry, Daddy.
- Hey, heard some no-goodnik stole your tree.
Well, we got a 30-footer,
so you can have the top of ours.
Thanks, Ted.
Bart, this is Patches.
- And what was your name?
- Poor Violet.
Oh, I don't like
where this is going.
Your story made everyone
at the orphanage so sad.
- We want you to have this dollar we were saving.
- Please, I don't deserve this.
Hey, listen up, everybody.
The Simpsons are
the best friends I ever had.
So I'm giving them
the tip jar from the bar.
[Cheering, Laughing]
My goodness,
there is over $15,000 here.
15,000 Missoulians?
Holy "schlamola"!
What are you gonna do
with all that "kablingy"?
Well, if you mean the money...
I suppose we'll just replace
the items the burglar took-
Boring!
Spend it on something fun.
- Go wild! Ha! Right, Seymour?
- Yes, something wild.
- Yeah, enjoy, huh?
- Get something fun.
- Something stupid.
- You only live once.
- Speak for yourself.
Marge, kids, let's go
buy some happiness.
[Cheering]
God bless you, Bart Simpson.
I'd kiss you, but Doctor says I'm sick.
[Coughs]
Is this car $15,000?
Yeah, it is now.
And because of your loss, folks...
I'll throw in the undercoating for...
200- No, 490 bucks.
What a deal.
I'd be a sucker not to get it.
I don't know about this, Dad.
Shouldrt we give the money
to charity or some- Ow!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I jabbed you with my pen.
- Ow! You're still doing it.
- Yeah, I know.
## [Singing Christmas Carol]
## [Continues]
Oh, will this
Christmas never end?
[Honking Horn]
Out of my way, snow poke.
- Slow down, Homer.
- Don't worry, honey.
I know exactly what I'm-
Whoopsie.
Tap the brakes.
- Turn into the skid.
- No, away from the skid.
- Hit the brakes!
- Floor it!
- Go with it!
- Shut up. One at a time.
- Lisa?
- Bail out!
[All Screaming]
Oh, that was close.
[Cracking]
[Explosion]
- Oh, I knew this would happen.
- Well...
at least the burglar's
having a merry Christmas.
- Bart. You're up early.
- I couldn't sleep.
What's wrong?
[Sighs]
There was no burglar.
- No burglar?
- What does he mean, no burglar?
I accidentally burned up the tree...
and the presents.
I'm really sorry.
- You little-
- [Homer] Lisa, no!
- Your hands are too weak.
- [Gagging]
- Stop that.
- I'm gonna kill him.
- No, I'm killing him first.
- [All Shouting]
- [Doorbell Rings]
Kent Brockman here
for a follow-up...
with Springfield's favorite
hard-luck family, the Simpsons.
Folks, any words for the Christmas thief,
if he's watching?
Eh, yes, Kent.
Uh, hello, jerk.
We may never find you and
we should probably all stop looking.
But one thing's for sure,
you do exist.
Strong words.
Strong, bewildering words.
- Also, we want to thank the whole
town for their generosity.
- [Dog Growling]
Hey, look.
It's little Bart's fire truck.
[Gasps]
Little Lisa's sweater. Little Homer's sausage.
What in the name of
holy hell is going on here?
Oh, it's true.
We werert robbed.
That part we made up,
but the rest is true. [Sobbing]
Wait.
He's just covering for me.
I destroyed the presents. Then I buried
the evidence. And I acted alone.
So the family never knew
about any of this?
Well, the boy told us, but that was
after we filed a phony police report.
And after we spent all
the townspeople's money.
So you can see why my husband
had to lie to you a moment ago.
So this was all a scam.
And on Christmas.
Yeah, Jesus must be
spinning in his grave.
We gave them our vitamin money.
[Coughs]
Hey, hey, hey.
Shoo, you lousy freeloaders.
Come back when
you get some parents.
In my long career,
I've seen some pretty shabby things...
but this putrid fraud
"out-stinks" them all.
[Man]
And cut.
[Chuckling]
I just wanna thank you folks so much.
This has turned out to be
a great, great story for me.
I think they're
running out of tomatoes.
- [Thud]
- Yeah, but they still got plenty of pumpkins.
[Grunts]
Homie, I'm so ashamed.
Relax, Marge.
This will all blow over.
[Groans]
- [Chattering]
- Oh, no. Look at the line.
- Oh, there they are.
- Ah, it's the swindlers.
- The Simpsons.
- Ah, them stinkir liars.
Well, there goes
Christmas dinner.
Oh, head of the line.
A family could get used to
being shunned, huh? Huh?
Hey, look, Sean.
It's that family everybody hates.
Whatever.
Uh, Miss Hoover.
Miss Hoover.
Forget it, Lisa. I'm not teaching you
anything until I get my money back.
Now turn your desk around
and stop learning.
All the way.
Hi, liar.
[Bird Cawing]
Run for your lives, everyone!
This is not a drill!
[Scoffs]
Oh, right. Yeah.
Then while we're gone,
you take our snacks.
- Just like you took our money.
- You tell him, Lenny. [Coughing]
"You'll all get yours in hell...
you lying, thieving"-
[Clears Throat]
blanking blankers-
"Sincerely, Moe."
Oh, great.
Now we have to send him a card.
I know you're used to
getting hate mail, but I'm not.
There's only one way out. We've gotta
give this greedy town its money back.
But we don't have $15,000.
Unless-
##[Easy Listening]
##[Ends]
Arert we forgetting something, Marge?
You were down $5,200 dollars.
- But Mr. Trebek-
- I asked you before the game...
if you knew the rules,
and you said you did.
- Judges.
- Run, Mom.
She ain't gettir
the home version.
[Sighs] I guess we better
get used to being pariahs.
There's no shame
in being a pariah.
Oh, no. There's
that angry mob again.
Hey, look who's here,
everybody.
- Oh, hi!
- [Chattering]
Oh, my, they've forgiven us.
It's a miracle!
You know, deep down,
people are pretty gre-
Hey, wait a minute.
They're taking our stuff.
Good Lord!
## [Humming Christmas Carol]
Hot, hot, hot, hot.
If you're headir for the medicine
cabinet, I already been there.
[Gasps]
What the hell's goir on?
Well, we hated
being mad at you, Homer.
So we decided to make things right.
Consider your debt repaid, neighbor.
And then some.
Look. I know this has been
a stressful holiday.
But in a way, having nothing
reminds us how lucky we really are.
- What?
- We still have each other.
And isn't that the best gift of all?
- But we would've had each other anyway.
- Yeah, plus lots of other stuff.
Maybe so, but there's one thing
they forgot to take away from us.
This washcloth.
- Hey, that's my washcloth.
- The hell it is!
- Give me that! Let go!
- Give me that thing!
- I want it!
- Stop this madness. It's just a washcloth.
Besides, it's mine. Yoink!
Hey, she's getting away
with the washcloth.
- Head her off at the stairs!
- Bart, you go around that way and cut her off!
[Clamoring Continues]
##[Country]
##[Man Singing]
##[Singing Continues]
##[Continues, Instrumental]
##[Ends]
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net