##[Chorus Singing]
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[Beeping]
## [Jazzy Solo]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh.
[Screams]
- ##[Singing]
- ##[Riano]
## [Singing]
## [Continues]
##[Homer Singing]
##[Marge, Homer Singing]
## [Continues]
## [Ends]
[Audience Applauding]
[Announcer] The Simpsons is filmed
in front of a live studio audience.
Hey there, meathead.
What are you watchir?
Oh, I thought I'd check out
the Warner Brothers Network.
## [Singing]
I need a drink.
[Announcer]
It's the TV movie of the year-
The Krusty the Klown Story:
Booze, Drugs, Guns, Lies...
Blackmail and Laughter.
Starring Fyvush Finkel
as Krusty the Clown.
I went through a five-year orgy
of nonstop pills and booze...
with nothing to show for it
but four Emmys and a Peabody Award.
[Groans]
All right! They're gonna show
his disastrous marriage to Mia Farrow.
Chan Ho, your mother Mia
and I are getting a divorce.
Chan Ho is over there.
I am Chin Ho.
Whoever you are.
Just pass it along, kid.
[Laughs]
What a bad father.
[Whirring]
- ##[Saxophone]
- Lisa, knock off that racket!
But, Dad, I'm supposed to
practice an hour a day.
- I'll practice you!
- You'll practice me? What does that mean?
Is it supposed to be
some sort of threat?
- [Groans]
- ##[Saxophone]
- Bart, make her stop.
- Hmm.
Look, Bart, I have to practice my saxophone,
and you can't stop me.
Oh, yeah? My dear Lisa,
you are eight, and I am 10.
And in my two extra years
on this planet...
I've learned a few tricks.
- Gimme that sax!
- No!
- I said gimme!
- I said no!
- Gimme it. Gimme, gimme, gimme!
- No! No, no, no!
[Shouts, Gasps]
[Honking]
Ha-ha!
[Crying, Sniffling]
Aw, Lisa, it doesn't
look so bad.
Oh, yeah?
Ew!
Lisa, honey...
if it'll make you feel better,
I'll destroy something Bart loves.
- Hey!
- Don't worry, Son.
If that bothers you,
I'll destroy something Maggie loves.
Dad, you don't understand.
This saxophone is like
my oldest friend.
I've had it for as long
as I can remember.
- You don't remember how you got it?
- Nuh-uh.
Oh, well,
it all happened in 1990.
Back then, The Artist Formerly Known
as Prince was currently known as Prince.
Tracey Ullman
was entertaining America...
with songs, sketches
and crudely drawn filler material.
And Bart was eagerly awaiting
his first day of school.
##[Men Harmonizing]
##[Man Singing]
- Look, Mama!
- Oh, honey, I can't right now.
Bart's gonna be late.
Hmph!
Now, Son, on your
first day of school...
I'd like to pass along the words
of advice my father gave me.
Homer, you're dumb as a mule
and twice as ugly.
If a strange man offers you a ride,
I say take it.
Lousy traumatic childhood.
[Honks]
Ooh, there's the bus.
Good-bye, sweetheart.
School will be fun.
[Skinner]
Welcome, kindergarteners.
I'm Principal Sinner-
Skinner.
- [Laughing]
- Well, that's it. I've lost them forever.
Now I'd like to introduce you
to Lunch Lady Doris...
who will serve you
healthy, nutritious meals.
- Yeah, right.
- [Skinner] Ms. Rhipps, the school nurse...
who will provide
ointments and unguents...
and Jimbo,
the school bully...
who will administer
noogies and nipple twisters.
- I look forward to whaling on all of you.
- [Gulps]
## [Singing Together]
## [Singing]
Added extra clap.
Not college material.
- ## [Humming]
- Hey, wee bairn!
[Shouts In Thick
Scottish Accent]
Can't you understand English?
- [Door Closes]
- Hi, honey. How was your first day of school?
Honey?
- ## [Singing]
- ## [Piano]
## [Singing]
## [Singing Together]
And that, my children...
is the story of Bart's
first day of school.
- Very nice.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Except you were supposed to be telling
the story of how I got my saxophone.
D'oh!
Homer, I can't get the baby to burp.
Could you try for a while?
No problem.
I'll just give her a sip of beer.
Come on, Maggie, it's Miller time.
Yes, it's Miller time.
- Homer!
- Oh, my father gave me beer as a child...
till I wrapped my little
red wagon around a tree.
[All Groaning]
Let's never drink again.
And we never did.
Mom, can you tell me the story
of how I got my saxophone...
and not have it turn into
a story about Bart?
Oh, sure, honey.
- Bart had just completed
his first day at school, and Bart-
- Mom!
Hey, she's just giving the public what it wants-
Bart by the barrelful.
Sorry, Lisa. It's just
how the story goes.
No matter what Bart tried,
he just couldn't fit in at school.
A-B-C-
- Uh, line?
- "D."
D-E-
Um, line?
"F," Bart. And believe me,
you'll be seeing plenty of'em.
Bart, would you like
to read a book?
- No.
- Would you like to color something?
I did.
Mmm.
## [Saxophone]
[Man on TV] That's damn fine coffee
you got here in Twin Reaks...
and damn good cherry pie.
Brilliant.
[Laughs]
I have absolutely no idea
what's going on.
Homer, I want you to look
at this drawing Bart did.
Oh, it's beautiful!
Oh! Oh, let's put Bart's
beautiful drawing up on the fridge.
Homer, stop. Would you
please look at the drawing?
Oh, all right.
What a-
[Screams]
Burn it! Send it to hell!
- I think we're going to have to get Bart some help.
- Get it away.
- Bart, Son? You want to play catch?
- No.
When a boy doesn't want to play catch with
his old man, something is seriously wrong.
I'll play catch
with you, Son.
- Get the hell out.
- I'm gone.
- Aah.
- Mrs. Simpson...
physically your son
is as sound as a dollar.
I'm afraid Bart's severe
emotional dysfunction...
stems from a deep-seated
psychological trauma.
[Laughs]
[Marge Narrating] With nowhere else to
turn, we went to see the school psychologist.
Mr. and Mrs. Simpson,
there's nothing to be alarmed about.
Public school can be
intimidating to a young child...
particularly one with as many flamboyantly
homosexual tendencies as your son.
- Bart's gay?
- Bart? Uh-Whoo! Wrong file.
Uh, the point I'm trying
to make here is...
that Bart must learn to
be less of an individual...
and more a faceless slug.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hmm. Lisa, how old are you?
I am three and three eighths.
Hmm. Lisa, if I have five apples,
and I take away three apples...
how many apples
do I have left?
- Two apples.
- Wait a minute.
- She's right.
- Yes. Very good.
Marge, Homer, I believe
your Lisa may be gifted.
That's wonderful. But still,
can't you do anything for Bart?
Marge, he's five. His life is over.
Lisa's the wave of the future.
- Wave of the future!
- [Chuckles] That's right, honey.
If you nurture her gift now,
there's no telling what she can do.
Wow, just think
of the possibilities.
[Man]
Lisa Simpson has won the Nobel Rrize.
Nah.
[Man] Lisa Simpson has won
the Nobel Rrize for kickboxing.
- [Grunts]
- Hmm.
Uh, I'll give you the address
of a nice preschool.
##[Girls Singing]
I can assure you, our preschool
is of the highest quality.
Over 75% of our graduates
go on to first grade.
Our little girl has a gift, and we're willing
to do what it takes to help her.
Very good. Once we receive your
$6,000 tuition check, she's in.
- I'll give you 50 bucks.
- Our fee is nonnegotiable.
- Seventy-five.
- Look, I knew private school would be expensive...
but I was hoping we could get
a scholarship of some sort.
Sorry. I don't have anything to offer you
unless you're a member of a minority group.
Excelente.
Muchos gracias, "señorata."
- Sorry.
- [Chinese Accent] Aah, so.
Come on, honey.
I guess this is a world
you'll never know.
Our family was suffering
through its worst crisis ever.
Bart was miserable at school...
and Lisa's gifts
were going to waste.
Uh, Homer? It's five years later,
and I'm still miserable at school.
And my gifts are still
going to waste.
And sometimes I feel
so smothered by this family...
I just wanna scream
till my lungs explode. [Gasps]
I'll go start dinner now.
- You do that.
- [Marge Grumbles]
- Hello.
- Dad, what are you doir here?
Lookir for my teeth.
[Muffled Barking]
Gimme those!
Better wash these off.
Oh, the hell with it.
Well, Grampa,
as long as you're here...
we were telling a story
that took place...
when Bart was five
and Lisa was three.
Oh, I know this story.
The year is
19-aught-six.
The president is the divine
Miss Sarah Bernardt.
And all over America...
people were doir a dance
called the Funky Grandpa.
## [Singing]
[Snoring]
Yes.
Well, as if our troubles
werert bad enough...
Springfield was going through
an unseasonable heat wave.
[Kent Brockman On TV]
And so Springfield's heat wave continues...
with today's temperature exceeding
the record for this date...
set way back four billion
years ago...
when the Earth was just
a ball of molten lava.
Oh, so hot.
Homer, have you seen
the frozen peas?
- [Grunts]
- Um, you keep 'em.
Now listen, if we can't
afford private school...
maybe there's some
other way to encourage Lisa.
Um, an art class,
ballet lessons.
They have some fun things you can do
at the museum on Saturday.
Uh-uh. Forget it, Marge. There is no way
I'm spending my Saturdays at a museum.
Unless- Museums don't
have foosball, do they?
- [Dings]
- You lose, Michelangelo's David. Who's next?
Me!
Oh, I guess
it doesn't matter.
All these things cost money,
and we just don't have it.
- Unless-
- Unless what?
Well, there's that $200 we've been
saving for the new air conditioner.
Oh, Marge, but we've needed
a new air conditioner for years.
And our stop-gap solution
is getting cranky.
[Yowls]
I cannot believe this. I'm trying to give
our daughter a head start in life...
and you aren't
helping a bit.
Marge, name one successful person
who ever lived without air conditioning.
- Balzac.
- No need for potty mouth just
because you can't think of one.
- But Balzac is the name.
- [Babbling]
If ifs and buts were candy
and nuts-
- Uh, how does the rest of that go?
- Please...
just promise you won't buy an air conditioner
till we've figured out a way to help Lisa.
All right, all right.
I promise.
Must be another way to get
an air conditioner.
[Machinery Whirring]
Mmm, recirculated air.
[Meows, Shivering]
- Uh, Homer?
- What, Flanders?
Well, sir, I hate to be a suspicious
Aloysius on you...
but did you steal
my air conditioner?
Well, I admit it looks bad, Flanders,
but haven't you heard of...
"Let he who is without sin
cast the first stone"? [Groans]
- Got him, Dad.
- [Groans]
And so, just as things
looked their worst-
I realized I could make money selling
my medication to deadheads.
Grampa, what are you
talking about?
Oh, nothing.
As I was saying, things couldn't
be worse for Lisa or Bart.
"And the ugly duckling was amazed
to realize it had grown into a beautiful swan."
So you see, children,
there is hope for anyone.
- Even me?
- No.
Uh, hi.
- Hi.
- I have soy milk.
The doctor says
the real kind could kill me.
I wish I was interesting
like you.
[Imitates Fart]
- [Laughing] You're funny.
- I am?
Yeah.
- And the world needs a clown.
- Hmm.
[Imitates Fart]
Doody. Booger.
[Laughing]
Man, that is killer material.
- ## [Singing]
- Young man, I can assure you...
my posterior is nothing more than flesh, bone
and that metal plate I got in 'Nam.
- [Gulps]
- I want you to knock off that potty talk right now.
The principal said "potty."
[Laughing]
[Grumbles]
You listen to me, son.
You've just started school...
and the path you choose now may be the one
you follow for the rest of your life.
Now, what do you say?
Eat my shorts.
- All right, I'll eat- Eat your shorts?
- [Kids Laughing]
Yeah, eat my shorts.
## [Singing]
- Buttman?
- [Grunts]
[Giggles] He's the greatest showman
since that kid who eats worms.
My 15 minutes
of fame are over.
[Homer] Well, Moe, this is it. Today's
the day I get my new air conditioner.
Congratulations.
Who's the little chick?
- I'm Lisa.
- She has a gift.
You have 13 pickled eggs
in this jar...
and one cockroach.
[Laughs]
Who are you, sweetheart,
the health inspector?
No, but I am.
Uh, here, have a margarita.
Uh, that's a parasol.
[Gasps]
Ooh.
- Help us, Homer.
- Yeah, help us, you fat yutz.
[Gurgling]
[Laughing]
Wow.
Musical instrument? Could that be
a way to encourage a gifted child?
Just give me a sign.
Works for me.
Uh, what do you like, Lisa?
"Viomalin"?
"Tubamaba"?
- "Oboemoboe"?
- That one.
Oh, "saxomaphone."
Two hundred dollars?
Oh, I'll take it.
- ## [Note Plays]
- [Giggling]
- Would you like an inscription, sir?
- Yeah.
To Lisa: Never forget
your daddy loves- D'oh!
And that inscription
is still there today.
Wow. So that's how Lisa
got her sax.
Next, I'll tell you
the origin of Maggie's pacifier.
What origin? We get 'em
for $ 1.95 down at the Safeway.
Well, I really liked that story,
but it still doesn't fix this.
You know, Homer,
I think we have some money...
in the air conditioner
account again, hmm?
Oh, but, Marge...
am I doomed to spend
the rest of my life sweating like a pig?
Yeah, not to mention lookir like a pig,
eatir like a pig-
- Don't forget the smell.
- Will you get off my front lawn?
- Why don't you make me?
- Why? Oh, I give up.
Well, don't worry about me, Dad.
[Chuckles]
It's not how it looks.
It's how it sounds.
[Squealing]
[Groans]
[Reporter On TV]
Well, sir, we got a scorcher today.
And to cool off,
nothir beats Fruitopia-
the iced tea
brewed by hippies...
but distributed by a heartless,
multinational corporation.
"Dear Lisa...
may your new saxophone
bring you years of d'oh!"
## [Rock]
- ## [Continues]
- ##[Band Joins In]
## [Ends]
You're a good father.
I learned from the master.
Where's Maggie?
I'm not kiddir.
I can't see. My retinas
have detached again.
[Laughing]
- He is blind as a bat.
- That's right.
- [Laughing]
- It's true.
##[Saxophone]
##[Jazz]
- [Homer] Lisa! Enough "saxomaphone" already!
- ##[Stops]
##[Jazz Resumes]
##[Ends]
www.tvsubtitles.net