##[Chorus Singing]
[Bell Ringing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
Oh, look. This is a perfect chance to get
you kids some nice church shoes.
[Both Groaning]
What do we need church shoes for?
Jesus wore sandals.
Well, maybe if he had better arch support,
they wouldn't have caught him.
[Groans]
Look, Homer!
There's that bird
you like to argue with.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't Professor Know-it-all.
Excuse me, Marge.
They need a good, stiff, all-purpose
dress shoe. Something for church...
but also for doctor's appointments,
dental checkups...
piano recitals,
building dedications...
visiting elderly relatives,
haircuts and shoe shopping.
Well, we have a brown shoe.
Did you hear that, kids? Brown.
Oh, rats.
Talk about bad luck.
I forgot to wear socks today.
Guess I can't try those on.
Yeah, no problem.
You can wear the store sock.
Ew.
[Grunts] Would you mind
lacing 'em up, kid? I have a bad back.
Hey, if you didn't want to tie shoes,
you shouldn't have become a shoe salesman.
- [Sighs]
- [Cracking]
That's where you're wrong, pal.
It's not enough to want a cracker.
You have to earn it.
Mom, these are at least
two sizes too big.
- Perfect, you'll grow into them.
- When?
Oh, you're both
way overdue for a spurt.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Do you like to laugh?
[Laughing]
Oh, yes.
As long as it's tasteful.
And never at someone,
or with, and not-
- Excuse me, sir. Do you like to laugh?
- Why, yes. Yes, I do.
Well, then you'll love our comedy
festival. It's for a good cause.
- A rest home for pirates?
- No, Dad. It's to fight soil erosion.
Now, that's a fight
I wanna be a part of.
Hey, somebody
screwed up bad.
You've got all these big comics lined up
for your show, but there's no Krusty.
- Who?
- Krusty the Clown.
Funniest man alive, prince of pies...
- the sultan of seltzer?
- Excuse me, sir. Do you like to laugh?
Well, only if something
tickles me just right.
[Laughing]
[Continues Laughing]
Yeah, excuse me. I'm looking
for someone named "Jay Leno."
- Somebody wanna get this kid a TV?
- Whoa, gee, thanks, mister.
- Yeah, just joking. l-I'm Jay Leno.
- Oh.
- So what can I do for you, huh?
- Well, if you're running the show...
how could you leave out
Krusty the Clown?
Ah, Krusty the Clown?
That takes me back.
- Didrt he die in a grease fire?
- No, he's alive.
And he is so funny you could plotz.
At least according to his press release.
Well, if he's half as alive
as you say he is, he's in.
Charity, eh?
What's my cut?
Nothing? I make more than that
takir a "schwitz."
Hey, hey, happy birthday!
[Chuckles]
Now get him out of here.
- He seems reluctant.
- Tell him it will count
towards his community service.
[Grunting]
All right, I'll do it.
[Groans]
Boy, swipe one pair of Haggar slacks...
and you're payir for it
the rest of your life.
I finally got around
to reading the dictionary.
It turns out the zebra did it.
[Laughing]
- I don't get it.
- Dad, the zebra didn't do it.
- It's just a word at the end of the dictionary.
- I still don't get it.
- It's just a joke.
- Oh, I get it! I get jokes.
[Laughing]
Hey, hey,
it's Krusty the Clown.
Hey, hey! Uh-
[Chuckles]
It's you, right?
And this guy, uh,
with all the jokes he does.
You're the reason
I went into comedy.
If it werert for you,
I'd be a doctor.
Yeah, yeah, right. Thanks.
[Sighs]
I got my period today.
[Coughs]
Oh, good Lord.
Plus, I got
this new boyfriend.
You know how it is when you're
kissing a guy with a tongue stud.
[Laughing]
Yes! Yeah! Oh, God, yes.
It's time for something special.
The man Spencer Tracy called...
"the most promising
newcomer of 1959."
Please put your hands together
for Krusty the Clown.
- [Applause]
- Whoo-hoo! Yeah, Krusty!
Hey, hey.
[Goofy Laugh]
So...
how about those
TV dinners, huh?
I tried one the other day. When lightning
strikes, the peach cobbler goes out.
[Bart Laughing]
Cobbler.
The other thing
about TV dinners...
you don't have leftovers,
you have reruns.
[Feedback On R.A.]
TV dinner jokes? Ooh!
- Take that, Swansors.
- [Chuckling]
Didrt like
that one, huh? Well-
"Me so sorry.
Ah, so."
[Groans] What's he gonna do next,
the flapping dickey?
[Booing]
Uh-oh, I'm losir 'em.
Time for the "A" material.
Hey, hey!
"Ah, so. Ah, so.
Me like the fried rice.
Me flap dickey long time."
[Chuckles]
Hey, Krusty, great set.
Are you kidding?
I stunk up the joint.
No, no. I was talking
to Lisa back there.
We both agreed.
You killed.
Really? Lisa, huh?
Sure, there were
a lot of laughs.
You probably couldn't hear them.
The acoustics were so bad.
Yeah, the acoustics.
That's what it was.
- I mean, "Me so sorry." [Laughing]
- [Laughing]
Yeah, I was great.
Did you get a load
of"Corpsey" the Clown?
[Scoffs]
That guy cheapens our whole profession.
- What do you think of him, Internet Comic?
- [Beeping]
[Laughing]
Guys, keep it down.
- Five minutes, Krusty.
- Oh, I ain't going back out there.
No, five minutes to get your stuff
and get out.
[Groaning]
Where is that
stinkir monkey?
It's about time.
Give me those reviews.
"Last night's comedy benefit delivered
wall-to-wall laughs without exception."
Phew.
"The only exception was
the embarrassingly dated humor...
of Springfield's
green-haired, red-nosed hack-"
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
"Krusty the Clown." No!
They say any publicity
is good publicity.
You, sir, are an idiot.
- [Chittering]
- Aw, that's your answer to everything!
Look at my life.
I'm talking to a monkey and a-
I don't know
what the hell you are.
You can be so cruel
when you're sober.
Well, I'll fix that. I'm goir
on the bender to end all benders.
[Gargling]
## [Disco On TV]
[Speaking Spanish]
What did he say, Lisa?
What did he say?
He said there's no shame
in their forbidden love.
Oh, Diego's
not gonna like that.
[Speaking Spanish]
Take me here,
under the disco ball.
Beep, beep. Clear the couch.
It's Krusty time.
[Announcer]
And now, here's Krusty.
[Cheering]
Hey, hey.
I'm Kent Brockman the clown...
filling in for Krusty the Clown
who didn't come in today.
He is presumed dead
or on vacation.
Today's top joke:
It seems a local moron
threw his clock out the window.
We'll tell you why
right after this.
Oh, this sucks.
I am out of here.
[Krusty Groaning]
Wow, a clown.
Do you think he's evil?
[Sniffing]
He smells evil.
Should we tell Daddy?
No, let's poke him
a little while longer.
Hey, get away from him,
you little freaks.
- [Screaming]
- [Groaning]
- [Grunting]
- Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
[Groans]
Oh, it hurts to talk.
We'll have to work out
a system of blinks.
Not you, you imbecile.
Oh, P.U., what were
you drinking, gasoline?
Yes, I was drinking
gasoline, Mother.
- Uh, Krusty.
- Hang on, kid. I got a tack in my head.
That's one of your posters.
I got all the Krusty stuff.
Man, look at all the crap
with my face on it.
"Krusty's Personal Swabs"?
What was I thinking?
All these years, I should've
been working on my act...
but I was too busy selling out.
Now I'm just a tired old hack.
[Sobbing]
Ah, that burns!
What the hell is on those things?
- Here. Quick, use my Krusty Eye Wash.
- No, not on your life.
[Bart] Thanks for coming, Jay.
Krusty really needs help.
Oh, no question.
I gotta freshen up my act.
Jay, you're a professional
comedian, right? Right?
- Answer me!
- Yes! Now stop squirming.
I'm trying to get
these tangles out.
They are just impossible.
Well, they are. Anyway,
don't you have some advice for Krusty?
Well, these days, people
like observational humor...
about things they deal with
in everyday life.
Oh, yeah. You mean like when your
lazy butler washes your sock garters...
and they're still
covered with schmutz?
Well, kind of,
but more universal.
And maybe lose
the "me so sorry" bit.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
Let's not tamper with a classic.
Shut up, kid. Come on, Leno.
Tamper, teach, impart.
## [Whistling]
- Dad!
- Whoops! Sorry, Son.
I didn't know you, Jay Leno and a monkey
were bathing a clown.
Well, they are, so make
with the loofah or get out.
- [Applause]
- And then of course, there's Mom...
who sounds something like this.
[Clears Throat]
"Eat your vegetables.
Take a sweater.
I don't think
that's a good idea. Hmm."
- [Laughing]
- [Laughing] Take that, Marge.
- [Grunts]
- Thank you, thank you.
And now, the all-new
comedy stylings of...
Krusty the Clown!
[Cheers]
Oh, Krusty!
Wait. Where's my water?
Oh, there it is. All right.
Hello.
I'm a real person.
And as a real person, I've made some
humorous observations about real life.
For example, have you ever noticed
how there are two phone books...
a white one and a yellow one?
[Chuckles]
Like, what's the deal with that?
One's residential,
the other is business.
Oh, well, that makes sense.
What will they think of next,
blue pages?
They have those.
They're government listings.
I see.
Uh, what about two-cent stamps?
Pizza pie is
very hot these days.
Can't open pickle jars.
No mail on Sunday. Out of paper towels.
- Oh, oh, oh. What's the deal with cardboard?
- Boo!
All right, let's just
move on to Notebook 2.
- I've really gotta get dinner started.
- Me too.
I also have to go. Boo!
[Groans]
- Krusty, the acoustics in here-
- I appreciate the effort, kid.
But there's only
one thing left for me to do.
[Chattering]
Thank you for coming.
[Clears Throat]
"Smart lads who slip at times away...
"From fields where
glory will not stay...
"Runners whom
the race outran...
And the name died
before the man."
- Krusty, does this have a point?
- Yes.
I'm quitting show business.
I was just trying to go out...
with a little class, you jackass.
But, Krusty, why now?
Why not 20 years ago?
'Cause comedy
ain't funny anymore.
Instead of time-tested jokes about
women drivers and doctor bills...
you got some
big-chin schlub...
reading typos from
the Ralookaville Rost.
Well, here's a headline for you:
Nobody cares.
[Laughing]
Hey, I washed your hair.
These comics today.
"Ooh, look at me.
I can't set my V.C.R.
"I can't open a bag
of airline peanuts.
I'm a freakir moron."
[Laughing]
Krusty's gone nuts.
Then you got these lady comics
talking about stuff...
that would embarrass
Redd Foxx-
God rest his smutty soul.
Who they slept with.
What time they sit on the can.
- This is supposed to get you a husband?
- [Laughing]
What the hell are you laughir at?
I'm just tellir the truth.
- [Laughing] And it's funny.
- It is?
In that case, I'm proud to announce
my triumphant return to comedy.
[Cheering]
- "Four drink minimum"?
- I'll cover you, honey.
Hi, how you folks doing?
I'm Moe.
Or, as the ladies like to call me,
"Hey, you, behind the bushes."
- Is this thing on?
- No. Sorry, Moe.
- [Feedback On R.A.]
- And now, without further Apu.
I have been zinged and I love it.
The last angry clown, the man
who spews truth from every orifice...
ladies and gentlemen, Krusty.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I'm watchir TV today-
Whoo! TV, yeah!
All I keep seeir is dead
celebrities hawkir products.
The got poor Vincent Price
floatir around on a toilet cake...
tellir me about
"the horrors of an 'unfresh' bowl."
[Laughing]
And I tell you somethir else,
I do not believe Winston Churchill...
would eat
at Der Wienerschnitzel.
[Laughing]
There's nothir those Madison Avenue
grave robbers won't do...
- to get us to buy their crap.
- [Cheering]
Impeach Churchill!
Well, here's one dollar those crooks
aren't gonna get their hands on.
- [Gasping]
- Uh, isn't that illegal?
I don't care if it is illegal.
I'm makir a stand here. Who's with me?
I am! I worked
like a dog for this.
- [Man #1] Yeah!
- [Man #2] Me too.
Oh, you're burning it
all wrong, Seymour.
It's my allowance, Mother,
and I'll burn it the way I want.
Take that, you greedy fat cats.
- Marge, give me your purse.
- Here's $42. That's everything I have.
- Run home and bury it in the yard.
- I love you, Mom.
[Cheering, Clamoring]
Wow, they're hanging
on his every word.
- Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
- I hope so.
I thought I made
myself clear in Boston.
[Chuckling]
From now on...
I'm gonna be just like Krusty
and tell it like it is.
Marge, you're getting
a little fat around the old thighs.
- Dad!
- You too, Bart.
Oh, knock it off, Homer.
You're the fattest one in the car.
You didn't have to
tell it like it is, Marge.
I'm proud of you, Krusty.
Oh, sure, I've got material success...
my own show, acres of cars,
a nice microwave oven.
But you're out there on the edge.
You're doir it for the sheer thrill.
And if I wasrt so afraid of clowns,
I'd give you a big hug.
Hey, excuse me, Krusty. We've been
watching you at Moe's all week.
And your credibility
is just-Wow.
- Get to the point, Armani.
- Well, we think you'd be the perfect spokesman...
for our company's new
sports utility vehicle, the Canyonero.
I guess you Wall Street weasels didn't
get the word. Krusty's not for sale.
But you endorse everything.
In fact, this endorsement contract...
comes from your line of legal forms.
It's a quality form.
But those days are behind me.
I don't shill for nobody no more.
Are you sure?
'Cause we're prepared to offer you...
a free, fully-loaded Canyonero.
[Stammering]
Oh, well.
No! Take your corporate blood
wagon and get the hell out.
Are you sure? It's free.
Stop saying that!
[Cheering]
I brought a bag of money
in case he wants us to burn it again.
I hope he tells us to burn our pants.
These things are driving me nuts.
So this afternoon,
two suits come up to me...
and ask me to endorse
some new sports utility vehicle.
- What did you do?
- [Gasping]
- Don't you hate pants?
- I threw those two creeps out on their ass.
[Cheering]
Then they followed me home,
beggir me to take a test drive.
And let me tell you,
talk about roomy.
The Canyonero combines the smooth
handling of a European sports car...
with the rugged drivability
of a sturdy 4x4.
- [Murmuring]
- Hey, Krusty, what are you talking about?
I thought you said
those guys were creeps.
Yeah, but that was
before I got to know 'em.
And I'm tellir you, the Canyonero
is the Cadillac of automobiles.
That's Canyonero.
[Clamoring]
Wait! Where you going?
I still got plenty of beefs.
Fat-free yogurt.
The-The quality of computer porn.
- [Groans]
- I knew I should've gone on first.
I don't get it, Krusty. You said
you would never be a shill again.
[Grunts] I learned something
about myself tonight, kid.
It ain't comedy that's in my blood.
It's selling out.
Come on,
I'll give you a ride home.
Wow. This is roomy.
##[Country]
##[Man Singing]
- ##[Singing Continues]
- [Whip Cracks]
##[Singing Continues]
- ##[Singing Continues]
- [Man] Hyah!
[Whip Cracks]
- ##[Singing Continues]
- [Whip Cracks]
- Hey, hey!
- [Announcer] The Federal Highway Commission...
has ruled the Canyonero unsafe
for highway or city driving.
- ##[Singing Continues]
- [Whip Cracks]
##[Continues]
##[Man Singing]
- ##[Singing Continues]
- [Whip Cracks]
##[Singing Continues]
- ##[Singing Continues]
- [Whip Cracks]
- [Man] Hyah!
[Whip Cracks]
##[Singing Continues]
- [Man] Hyah!
- [Whip Cracks]
##[Singing Continues]
- Hyah!
- [Whip Cracks]
- Canyonero!
- Hyah!
- [Whip Cracks]
- Whoa, Canyonero!
- Whoa!
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net