##[Chorus Singing]
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[Beeping]
## [Jazzy Solo]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[Stone Sizzles]
[Snickers]
This sting can't miss, boys.
I mailed these bogus prize certificates
to every scofflaw in Springfield.
When they show up
for their free motorboats...
we arrest them and beat them
to the full extent of the law.
[Laughs]
So the hook is baited.
- [Chuckles] Nice metaphor, Eddie.
- Yeah, good work, Eddie.
## [Cheerful Singing]
## [Continues]
## [Ends]
But we didn't enter
any police raffle.
That doesn't matter.
The important thing is we won.
I don't know.
There's something very peculiar about this.
Sheesh!
You're the most paranoid family
I've ever been affiliated with.
[Whistling]
I'd like a yellow boat, please...
- with extra motors.
- Yo, no cuts, bro.
Where's my motorboat, pig?
Uh, right through that door.
[Titters]
- [Cuffs Clicking]
- Whoa! Yo!
- [Blows Landing]
- Ouch!
[Snake Groans]
I call brutality on you.
- You have the right to remain-
- [Chuckles]
All right, uh, "Simpson, Homer."
- You're next.
- Whoo-hoo!
Howdy, gents.
I'm here to collect my free-
Ow!
Oh, my boating arm!
- What's going on!
- You're under arrest, slimebag.
- What's this perp in for, Lou?
- 235 unpaid parking tickets...
totaling $175.
[Snickers]
I hope you brought your checkbook, wise guy.
You lousy cops.
Lucky for you I'm double-parked or I'd-
There. Now, could I
please have my motorboat?
Dad, why aren't you saying anything?
Where's our motorboat?
I didn't like it.
The mast had termites.
- Why would a motorboat have a mast?
- Because!
The thing, it was- Shut up!
Whoo! There's that new mega-mall
they're building.
They say the air conditioner will be more
powerful than a million hydrogen bombs.
Hey, they can't just build a parking lot
on Sabertooth Meadow!
That's where they discovered
all those fossils.
Fossils, schmossils.
You can't stop progress
'cause of some moldy old bones.
Bones, schmones.
But they might be paving over
rare specimens.
Pull over so we can complain, Dad.
Come on!
Who wants to complain with me?
Fine.
I'll come back later.
Who wants to come back with me?
[Mutters]
Fine.
My attorney, Lionel Hutz,
calls your attention...
to Municipal Code 147-C-
- "Protection of Antiquities and Fossils."
- That's right.
There aren't any fossils here, little girl.
Museum folks dug 'em all up years ago.
But what if they missed something?
You have to allow an archeological survey.
Who's gonna make us? You?
- [Laughing]
Now, hold on, Sid.
Hold on.
May be we should let the kid dig.
Could be good publicity.
[Indistinct Whispering]
Oh, yes.
Yeah, we ought to do that.
Okay. You wanna dig?
Be my guest.
Fine!
We'll see you in court!
- Mr. Hutz, we won.
- "We"?
Principal Skinner,
remember how I didn't sue...
when I found that scorpion
in my applesauce?
Well, I'm calling in a favor.
Mmm, I knew this day would come.
[Skinner] Attention.
All honor students will be rewarded...
- with a trip to an archeological dig!
- [Cheering]
Conversely,
all detention students will be punished...
with a trip to an archeological dig.
- Oh, no. Not tomorrow.
- Oh, crud.
##[Singing Call-And-Response]
## [Ends]
This is so exciting.
I can't wait to see what we find.
I must admit, it is rather exciting.
And-
Why, look!
Here's something right here.
It appears to be some sort of rock.
Oh, no. It's just a clump of dirt.
[Chuckles]
Even so, my heart
is pounding like a kettle drum.
I'd better sit down for a moment.
"Prinskipper Skippal"- "Prinnipple Skipper"-
l-I found something!
[Teachers, Students Exclaiming]
- [Gasps]
- It's a spearhead!
That's your trowel blade, Ralph.
It fell off the handle.
- And I found it!
- Okay, everyone, back to work!
You never know when we might
uncover a Tyrannosaurus.
[Screams]
- [Whimpering]
- [Snoring]
[Grunting]
[Snickering]
Well, this was a big bust.
Come on, kids.
Let's go home to our mothers.
Don't give up.
I'm sure we'll find something.
[Grunts]
Come on. Come on!
A bottle cap, a shoe,
a bar of gold- anything!
[Exclaims]
[Gasps]
Everybody, come quick!
[Chattering]
[Wiggum]
Hey, what is that?
- Hope it's not-
- Let me through. I got here late.
[Crowd Chattering]
Hmm, from the looks of it, I'd say
this fellow died from causes unknown.
[Laughs]
Look, there's more!
What the heck is this thing?
Speaking from a strictly
medical point of view, that ain't right.
[Gasps]
Oh, my goodness!
What is it, Lisa?
It looks like a human skeleton.
But these other bones
look almost like wings.
You mean, like... an angel?
Well, obviously, that's impossible.
- Lisa's right. It's an angel!
- [Onlookers Gasp]
[Homer]
Now, that's interesting.
[Chattering Continues]
- But it can't be an angel!
- Oh, no?
Well, if you're so sure what it ain't,
how about tellir us what it am?
[Onlookers Clamoring]
Well, maybe it's, uh-
uh- a Neanderthal who got bitten
by some angry fish.
[Whiny Grunt]
[Muttering, Cries Out]
[Screaming]
[Chuckles]
Oh, I got to say, Lisa.
It sounds like you're strainir
to do some explainir.
Yeah, everyone's heard
of angels, but...
who's ever heard of a "Neanderthal"?
[Chuckles]
It could be anything. It could be
a mutant from the nuclear plant.
Oh, fiddle-faddle.
Everyone knows our mutants have flippers.
Ooh, oops. I've said too much.
[Clears Throat]
- Smithers, use the amnesia ray.
- You mean, the revolver, sir?
Precisely. Be sure to wipe
your own memory clear when you're finished.
Now, regardless
of what this thing is...
it's a priceless scientific find...
so our most pressing concern now...
is determining who owns
such a valuable skeleton.
- And I'd like to suggest that I do.
- [Onlookers Protesting]
- [Woman] Excuse me.
- I'd like to hear from Lionel Hutz.
It's a thorny legal issue, all right.
I'll need to refer to the case
of Finders versus Keepers.
Oh, we can work this out, friends.
In the spirit of sharing,
what say we simply place...
- the sacred bones-
- [Horn Honking]
So long, suckers!
[Grunting]
Come on- Come on, angel.
- [Grunts]
- What are you doing with that?
I'm locking it up in my safe-deposit closet
with my other valuables.
I'll just leave it
in here a few years...
and let it appreciate in value.
It's probably a million years old, Dad.
- I think it's as valuable as it's gonna get.
- [Scoffs]
That's what they said about
this Billy Beer, smarty-pants.
[Chugging, Sighs]
We elected the wrong Can'ter.
[Kent Brockman]
Coming up next, an hilarious boat giveaway scam...
nets Springfield's dumbest criminals.
[Laughs]
Sounds like good watchir.
[Doorbell Rings]
He-Hey there, Marge.
Just brought the kids over...
to share a prayer with the blessed angel,
if it's okay with you.
[Homer Shouting]
Get your own angel, you moocher!
[Sighs]
Thanks anyway, Homer.
[Doorbell Rings]
- Oh, hello, Agnes.
- Sorry to trouble you...
but I'm goir in
for surgery tomorrow...
and I wondered if I could rub the angel
with my foot for good luck.
- It's foot surgery.
- [Homer] Hey, I'm trying to eat here!
- Beat it, peg leg!
- Jackass!
Marge.
- We wanna see the angel.
- [Crowd Clamoring]
Come on, Homer.
I just want a quick look-see.
- Pay you a buck.
- A buck, eh?
That gives me an idea.
- Fifty cents, please.
- [Coins Clattering]
##[Recording: Homer Singing Badly]
##[Continues]
##[Ends]
Dad, it's not fair
to claim this thing is an angel.
- There's no proof of that.
- No one's calling it an angel, Lisa.
If you look carefully, you'll notice
I never once used the word "angel."
- What about that sign right there?
- That's a typo.
Just let me take it
to the museum for one day.
They can do scientific tests
and prove it's not an angel.
Oh, no. We could lose out
on bags and bags of money.
It's sacrilegious, I tell ya.
[Door Creaking]
Wow, it's so lifelike.
[Moaning]
[Gulps]
[Man]
Astonishing, simply astonishing.
One of the most singular
specimens I've encountered...
in all my distinguished career.
But enough about my work.
What did you want to show me, Lisa?
It's a bone scraping
from that skeleton I found.
Oh, yeah.
The so-called angel.
The whole thing's preposterous, of course.
Quite preposterous. But no one will
believe me until I can prove what it really is.
Can't you do a D.N.A. test
or something?
Certainly.
I'll have the results by tomorrow.
Oh, thank you so much.
Um, you know,
I can't afford to pay you.
I didn't become a scientist
for financial gain.
Whatever little money
you have will be just fine.
- ##[Recorded Music]
- I say it's the Angel of Peace, you idiot.
I say it's the Angel of Mercy,
you jerk.
Excuse me. I took a piece
of the skeleton for scientific analysis.
- Soon we'll have all the facts.
- You did what?
- You know what? I don't like that.
- [Scoffs]
Facts are meaningless.
You can use facts to prove anything...
that's even remotely true.
- Facts, schmacts.
- [Panting]
Ah, here's Dr. Gould now.
What were the results, Professor?
- Inconclusive.
- "Inconclusive"?
Then why'd you come
running up like that?
Can I use your bathroom?
[Groans]
Well, it appears science
has faltered once again...
in the face of overwhelming
religious evidence.
- But-
- Go home, science girl.
- I am home.
- Good. Stay there.
Okay, folks.
Get your "Angel Glow Sticks."
- No one gets into heaven without a glow stick.
- I'll take four.
Ach! Those morons make me so angry.
Maybe so. But I'd appreciate it
if you didn't call them morons.
But they are morons.
- What grown person could believe in angels?
- Well...
your mother, for one.
You?
- But, y-you're an intelligent person, Mom.
- [Pot Clanks]
There has to be more to life
than just what we see, Lisa.
Everyone needs something
to believe in.
It's not that I don't have
a spiritual side.
I just find it hard to believe there's
a dead angel hanging in our garage.
Hmmm. My poor Lisa.
If you can't make a leap
of faith now and then...
well, I feel sorry for you.
Don't feel sorry for me, Mom.
I feel sorry for you.
[Kent Brockman] Next on Smartline,
the Springfield angel controversy.
Our guest tonight, making her
13th appearance on Smartline...
- Miss Lisa Simpson.
- Kent.
Miss Simpson, how can you
maintain your skepticism...
in spite of the fact this thing really,
really looks like an angel?
I just think it's a fantasy.
If you believe in angels, then why not
unicorns or sea monsters or leprechauns?
Oh, that's a bunch of baloney, Lisa!
Everyone knows
leprechauns are extinct.
Look, you can either accept science
and face reality...
or you can believe in angels
and live in a childish dreamworld.
Science-
What's science ever done for us?
- TV off.
- Science is like a blabbermouth...
who ruins a movie
by telling you how it ends.
Well, I say there are some things we don't
wanna know- important things.
- [Barney] Yeah, he's right!
- Enough talk.
It's smashir time!
[Commotion]
[Mob Yelling]
Take that and that and-
[Groans]
Oh! I'm paralyzed.
I just hope medical science
can cure me.
[Commotion Continues]
Why? Why was I programmed
to feel pain?
Technocrats are learning
a lesson in humility tonight...
as angel supporters lay waste
to Springfield's scientific institutions.
Ugh! I wish I'd never found
those stupid bones!
It's time to put an end to this.
- Bart, I'm borrowing your blue crowbar.
- Good ol' Blue-y.
- Hey, she's gonna smash the angel!
- Somebody stop her!
[Gasps]
It's gone!
[Weeping]
Oh, no! This can't be happening!
What the hell are we gonna do with
10,000 angel ashtrays? [Sobbing]
- I could take up smoking.
- You damn well better.
Okay. Okay, don't panic.
Marge, stop panicking!
We need a replacement skeleton,
and we need it now.
- Bart, strip down to your skeleton.
- [Door Opening]
We've come for the angel, Homer.
It's not safe with the unbeliever.
It's gone!
We're too late.
Little girl, what have you done
with our precious angel?
Nothing!
Someone must have stolen it.
Looks to me like Lisa Simpson found
something science couldn't explain...
so she had to destroy it.
Well, that's all the evidence I need.
Arrest the girl.
- [Gasps] Hey!
- What? She didn't do anything.
Give her a nice cell-
something in "C" Block.
Lisa Simpson, you are charged...
with destruction of an historic curiosity-
a misdemeanor.
But in a larger sense, this trial
will settle the age-old question...
of science versus religion.
Let the opening statements commence.
Your Honor,
over the coming weeks and months...
we intend to prove Lisa Simpson
willfully destroyed-
- There's the angel!
- [Murmuring]
[Shouting, Chattering]
I find the defendant not guilty.
As for Science versus Religion,
I'm issuing a restraining order.
Religion must stay 500 yards
from Science at all times.
[Chattering Continues]
Wow! Do you think it flew up here?
- Well, it didn't ride up on no zebra.
- Look, a message!
[Homer]
"The end will come at sundown."
[Laughing]
Hey-
Wait a second.
I don't like the sound of that.
I'm scared, Daddy. Too scared
to even wet my pants.
It's okay, Son.
Just relax, and it'll come.
Even Lisa Simpson must now agree.
We have witnessed a miracle.
Hardly.
Anyone could've written that.
Oh, angel, listen not
to this child of Satan.
Reverend, I've got to admit. This doomsday
warning has me just a smidge twitterpated.
Oh, now, be calm, Ned.
But be afraid also-
tremendously afraid-
for the day of reckoning is upon us!
- [Gasping, Murmuring]
- Reckoning?
Your Holiness,
there is word from America.
They say an angel
has foretold the apocalypse.
Um, keep an eye on it.
[Mrs. Krabappel]
This could be our last day together, my love.
How about a farewell romp in
the Garden of Earthly Delights?
Oh, Edna, my sweet buttercup,
you read my mind.
Just, uh, give me 20 minutes
or so to finish these tardy slips.
Why we gettir dressed-up, Mom?
Are we going to Black Angus?
Well, you might say we're going
to the best steakhouse in the whole universe.
So we're not going to Black Angus.
Will you leave me alone?
It's bad enough you're making me go
to your stupid Judgment Day.
Please, Lisa.
I don't know exactly what's gonna happen.
But I really wish we could
make peace before sunset.
Nothing is going to happen, Mom!
I hate to disappoint you,
but the world is not coming to an end.
Well, shall we sing a hymn?
Uh, "Nearer, My God, to Thee" maybe?
- Or-Or-Or-Or "Amazing Grace"?
- Mmm. Nah.
Oh, Marge.
Don't let go, no matter what.
If they want you in heaven,
they got to take me too.
- Ten seconds till sundown.
- [Murmuring]
[Taking Deep Drag]
[Huffing Exhale]
We did it.
We beat cancer.
Ohhh, what the hell?
- Muuuah!
- Seven, six-
[Others Join Countdown]
five, four...
three, two, one-
[Collective Gasp]
[Crickets Chirping]
[Collective Sigh]
- [Overlapping Chatter]
- [Homer] What happened?
- There you go. I hope you all learned a val-
- [Male Voice] Silence!
- ##[Trumpet Fanfare]
- [All Gasp]
[All Gasping]
Rrepare for the end!
- [Whimpering]
- The end ofhigh prices!
- What?
- Ooh.
Behold!
The grand opening
of the Heavenly Hills Mall.
Please just follow the angel
for all your shopping needs!
[Mechanized Whirring]
[Whirring Stops, Resumes]
Wait a second!
You planted a phony skeleton for me to find!
This was all a big hoax!
[Chuckles]
Not a hoax- a publicity stunt.
You exploited people's deepest beliefs
just to hawk your cheesy wares?
Well, we are outraged!
- Arert we?
- Oh. Oh, yeah. Yeah, we're outraged.
Very, uh-Very much so.
But look at all the stores!
A Pottery Barn!
And 20% off everything?
- Hey, does that include rat spray?
- Oh, yeah.
- Out of my way, shorty!
- Hey!
[All Clamoring]
I don't understand, Professor. Why didn't
your tests show the skeleton was a fake?
I'm gonna be honest with you, Lisa.
I never did the tests.
- [Electrical Current Sizzling]
- [Excited Chattering]
Uh, sir, about that, uh-
that kiss- l-
[Laughs]
I hope you understand it was
merely a sign of my respect.
Yes. Yes, of course.
[Distant Voices]
Well, I guess you were right, honey.
But you have to admit,
when that angel started to talk...
you were squeezing my hand
pretty hard.
[Embarrassed Chuckle]
Well, it was just so loud...
and- [Laughs]
thanks for squeezing back.
Anytime, my angel.
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net