Human roaches, feeding off
each other's garbage.
The only thing you can't buy
here is dignity.
Welcome, swappers...
to the Springfield Swap Meet.
Ich bin ein Springfield
Swap Meet patron.
I need a drink and a shower.
Oyster shells!
Hand painted to resemble Lucille Ball!
You'll love Oyster Lucy!
[ Deep Voice ] Oh, Mr. Mooney,
I just gotta meet Bob Cummings!
Viv!
Oh, boy!
Free trading cards!
Wow!Joseph of Aramathea!
Twenty-six conversions
in A.D. 46!
Whoa! A Methuselah rookie card!
Who'd have thought learning
about religion could be fun?
- Religion?
- Learning?
Let's get outta here!
Hey!
Wow! An original
Malibu Stacy from 1958!
Ooh!
Yeah, they took her off the market
after some kid put both his eyes out.
Oh, my!
[ Skinner] Prisoner 2 4601 .
[ Chuckles ]
I wore this for two years
in a Vietcong internment center.
Never thought I'd see
the old girl again.
[ Voice Resonating ]
Still fits.
- Small world, huh?
- It is. It really, really is.
Ooh, five cents each.
Junk.
The airplane's upside-down.
- Stradi-''who''-vius?
- [ Strings Break ]
Your teenage son or daughter will think
this wishbone necklace is really cool.
- I doubt my son or daughter is that stupid.
- [ Groans ]
Hmm. Nah.
What the hell's this?
Melvin and the Squirrels.
Part of the rodent invasion of the early '60s.
" Stuck a feather in his cap
and called it-- "
- " Rice-A-Roni "
- Melvin!
[ Gasps ]
Bart, look. It's Dad!
Dad, when did you
record an album?
I'm surprised you
don't remember, son.
It was only eight years ago.
Dad, thanks to television, I can't remember
what happened eight minutes ago.
[ Laughing ]
No, really. I can't.
It's a serious problem.
[ Laughing ]
What are we all laughing about?
- [ Laughing ]
- Who cares?
Anyway, it all happened during
that magical summer of 1985.
A maturing Joe Piscopo left Saturday Night Live
to conquer Hollywood.
People Express introduced
a generation of hicks to plane travel.
And I was in
a barbershop quartet.
" [ Pitch Pipe Hums ]
[ Harmonizing ]
" Hello "
" Hello, my baby
Hello, my honey "
" Hello, my ragtime
ragtime gal "
[ Homer's Voice ]
Every afternoon at Moe's, Chief Wiggum...
Principal Skinner, Apu and I
would get together and sing.
And the crowds went wild.
- Yoo-hoo!
- " Then you'll be left alone "
Barbershop? That ain't been popular
since aught-six, dag-nab it!
What did I tell you?
No talking like a grizzled 1890s
prospector. Consarn it.
Anyway, rock and roll
had become stagnant.
''Achy Breaky Heart''
was seven years away.
Something had to
fill the void.
And that something
was barbershop.
[ Harmonizing ]
" Good-bye "
" Good-bye
my Coney Island baby "
That's my son up there!
- What, the balding fat-ass?
- Uh, no, the Hindu guy.
[ Sirens Wailing ]
- " Never to see you any-- "
- " Never gonna see you any "
I'm gonna nail that cop
right between the eyes.
[ Quartet ]
"Never to return again "
Right after this song is over.
[ Skinner]
" Good-bye my Coney Island babe "
- [ Whistling ]
- [ Thud ]
[ Laughing ]
"[ Organ ]
" Good-bye
my Coney Island baby "
"Farewell, my own true love
true love "
- "I'm gonna go away and leave you "
- Ching, ching.
You know, Reverend,
this really isn't a hymn.
Ned, there's an oil stain in the parking
lot that looks just like St. Barnabus.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, my stars!
- " So good-bye "
- " Farewell "
" Shop Kwik-E-Mart and save "
" Good-bye, my Coney Isle--
Good-bye, my Coney Isle-- "
" Good-bye my Coney Island babe "
[ Cheering, Whistling ]
Homer, I'm a theatrical agent.
I want to represent your group.
- Really?
- Yeah, you've got it.
All except that police officer. Yuck!
Too Village People. You'll have to replace him.
Just leave it to me.
[ Panting ] Where we goin'?
Where we goin'?
- [ Brakes Screech ]
- Run along, boy. You're free now.
[ Tires Screech ]
No! No! Noooo!
Principal Seymour Skinner.
- Apu Nahasapeemapetilon.
- Eh, never fit on a marquis, luv.
From now on your name is
Apu de Beaumarché.
It is a great dishonor to my
ancestors and my god, but okay.
[ Homer's Voice ] The next day, we started
auditioning for Chief Wiggum's replacement.
" Old MacDonald had a farm
E-I-E-I-O "
"And on this farm
he had a chick "
"The swingingest chick I know "
"With a wiggle-wiggle here
And a wiggle-wiggle there "
- Get off the stage!
- I want to, but I can't!
"When you're alone and
life is gettin' you lonely "
"Ye can always go
Ach! ''Doontoon'' "
Next!
" If I could walk
with the animals "
"Talk with the animals "
" Grunt and squeak and squawk
with the animals "
Good Lord!
Doctor Doolittle is Chief Wiggum.
This bird's gonna fly!
- [ Piano Sounds ]
- Aaah!
[ Homer's Voice ] It was one lousy
applicant after another.
- And then--
- [ Melodious Voice ] " Over in Killarney "
"So many years ago "
- Such a voice.
- Who is that?
"Me mither sang
this song to me "
"In tones so soft and--"
[ Belches ]
[ All ]
Barney!
"Just a little Irish ditty "
Barney! How'd you like
to sing for our group?
Sure! Why not?
Now whar's me toothpick?
"Too-ra-loo-ra-loo-ra "
"Too-ra-loo-ra-li "
Wiggum forever!
Barney never!
- Wiggum forever!
- [ Chuckles ]
" Sweet Adeline "
" My Adeline "
[ Women Screaming ]
Barney forever!
Wiggum never!
Hey, those girls you paid to scream
are doing a great job!
I didn't pay
any girls to scream.
Huh?
[ Tires Squeal ]
- [ Chattering ]
- [ Barney ] Boy! We sounded great, huh?
Only one question remains, gentlemen.
What do we call ourselves?
How about Handsome
Homer Simpson, Plus Three?
I like it!
- [ Stammering ]
- I do not-- I do not think--
No. We need a name
that's witty at first...
but seems less funny
each time you hear it.
How about the Be Sharps?
Perfect.
The Be Sharps.
- The Be Sharps.
- [ Apu and Barney ] The Be Sharps.
[ Wiggum ]
The Be Sharps.
[ Chuckles Nervously ]
Why, you can't blame a guy for tryin'.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, you're all under arrest.
- What'd you kids get?
- I bought this cool pencil holder.
[ Chuckles ] Far out, man.
I haven't seen a bong in years.
No one bought
a wishbone necklace.
One of us made some money.
I sold a guy our spare tire.
- [ Tire Blows ]
- D'oh!
Well, it'll be a long time before
your mother gets back with the tire...
so why don't I tell you
more of the story?
Now that we had a name,
the Be Sharps needed a hit.
Something new, something exciting,
something mid-1980s.
"There was nothing
in Al Capone's vault "
" But it wasn't
Geraldo's fault "
D'oh!
[ Grunts ]
Look what I got! Now people will stop
intentionally ramming our car!
Mmm. Baby on board.
" Baby on board "
" Something, something
Burt Ward "
This thing writes itself!
" I'm tellin' you
it's mighty nice "
" Each trip's a trip
to paradise "
"With my baby "
" On board "
Gentlemen, you've just recorded
your first number one.
- Oh, yes!
- Yes! Wait till I tell Marge!
Oh, yes. Bouffant Betty.
Well, I would prefer we kept
your marriage a secret.
A lot of women are going to
want to have sex with you...
and, uh, we want them
to think they can.
Well, if I explain it to Marge that way,
I'm sure she'll understand.
[ Sobbing ]
- [ Inhales ]
- Come on, honey.
It'll only be till we
finish our tour of Sweden.
[ Sobs Continue ]
" [ Guitar Strums ]
" Baby on board "
" How I've adored "
"That sign
on my car's windowpane "
That's my boy Homer singing.
- Eh, Paul Harvey's on.
- Ooh!
And that little boy
who nobody liked grew up to be...
- Roy Cohn.
- [ Both ] Wow!
And now you know
the rest of the story.
" 'Cause I'm driving in
the carpool lane "
"[ Continues ]
Aw, squiddy, I got
nothing against ya.
I just heard there
was gold in your belly.
Ha, ha, harr!
"With my baby "
" On board "
Homer, you're
going to be famous!
Yeah, but I'm not gonna
let it change our lives.
I'll be the same loving father
I've always been.
- Have you seen Bart?
- I stuck him somewhere.
[ Clanking ]
Look what I
got for you, Dad.
Oh, Home--
[ Groaning ]
Gimme the key.
[ Women Screaming ]
I have a question
for Apu de Beaumarché.
Isn't it true that
you're really an Indian?
By the many arms of Vishnu,
I swear it is a lie.
Barney, how did you
join the group?
They found me
on the men's room floor.
- Principal Skinner--
- Mm-hmm?
You've been referred to
as ''the funny one.''
- Is that reputation justified?
- Yes. Yes, it is.
" Good-bye, my Coney Isle--
Good-bye, my Coney Isle-- "
" Good-bye
my Coney Island babe "
Damned ceremonies. This is time
I could be working, Mommy.
We'd like to dedicate this next number
to a very special woman.
She's 100 years old, and
she weighs over 200 tons.
This enormous woman
will devour us all! Aaah!
I-- I meant the statue.
Okay. Gilligan, the Skipper,
and Chief Wiggum.
- Name three castaways.
- Hi-oh!
Ooh!
Clancy, use the remote.
- Oh, yeah.
- [ Channels Switching ]
Oh! Can we talk about Chief Wiggum?
[ Gagging Noise ]
We had fame and fortune.
Now all we needed was the approval
of record company lowlifes.
- [ Drum Roll ]
- And the Grammy for
outstanding soul, spoken word...
or barbershop album
of the year goes to--
[ Drum Roll ]
- The Be Sharps!
- [ All ] Yea!
Congratulations!
David Crosby,
you're my hero!
- Oh, you like my music?
- You're a musician?
[ Homer's Voice ] Then came
the greatest thrill of my life.
Hello, Homer.
I'm George Harrison.
Oh, my God!
- Where did you get that brownie?
- There's a big pile of'em.
[ Squealing ]
Oh, man.
What a nice fellow.
Lisa, did you
see the Grammys?
You beat Dexy's
Midnight Runners.
You haven't heard
the last of them.
- I miss you, Daddy.
- I miss you too, honey.
Oh.
Here's that champagne
you ordered, Mr. Simpson.
Oh, thanks.
- Here.
- Wow! An award statue!
Oh, it's a Grammy.
- [ Clank ]
- [ Man ] Hey, don't throw
your garbage down here!
- [ Clank ]
- [ Thud ]
Wow, look at all this
Be Sharps merchandise!
Lunch boxes, coffee mugs...
funny foam.
They took the foam off the market
because they found out it was poisonous.
But if you ask me, if you're dumb
enough to eat it, you deserve to die.
- Bart!
- What?
I can't believe you're
not still popular.
What'd you do? Screw up like the Beatles
and say you were bigger than Jesus?
All the time.
It was the title of our second album.
But we were about to learn
an iron law of show business.
What goes up
must come down.
What about Bob Hope? He's been
consistently popular for over 50 years.
- So has Sinatra.
- Well, anyway, we were all getting tired of--
Dean Martin
still packs 'em in.
- Ditto Tom Jones.
- Shut up!
With your father on the road all the time,
I tried to compensate for his absence.
[ Homer's Voice ] Hi, kids. I love--
[ Speeds Up, Unintelligible ]
[ Both ]
Aaah!
- [ Balloon Pops ]
- [ Both ] Aaah!
[ Homer's Voice ] Meanwhile, the group
was having problems of its own.
" For all the latest
medical poop "
" Call Surgeon General
C. Everett Koop "
" Koop-Koop-a-doop "
This is worse than
your song about Mr. T.
I pity the fool who
doesn't like... he.
- And where's Barney?
- Oh, he's with his new girlfriend...
theJapanese
conceptual artist.
[ Barney ] Barbershop is in danger
of growing stale.
I'm taking it
to strange new places.
- [ Woman's Voice ] Number eight.
- [ Belch ]
Then came the day
we knew we were finished.
Gentlemen, Us magazine just came out
with its what's hot and what's not issue.
- Are we hot?
- We are not.
[ Homer's Voice ]
We all went our separate ways.
Well, William,
I'm back.
So, how did you
spend your summer?
I made millions in software
and lost it at the track. Ach!
It may not be glamorous,
but it's good, honest work.
- How much is this quart of milk?
- Twelve dollars.
- Hey, Barney, what'll it be?
- I'd like a beer, Moe.
I'd like a single plum floating
in perfume, served in a man's hat.
Here you go.
Hey, fellas. I'm back.
Oh, that's great.
Your replacement is getting tired.
[ Clucks ]
- Hey, Queenie, you can go now.
- I'll give her a good home.
And I did.
I'll never forget my five
and a half weeks at the top.
-Man, that's some story.
-There are still a few things I don't get.
Like, how come we never
heard about this until today?
- What happened to the money?
- Why haven't you hung up your gold record?
- Since when could you write a song?
- [ Laughs ]
There are perfectly
good answers to those questions...
but they'll have to wait
for another night.
Now off to bed.
I can't remember the last time
we were all together.
Last year, on that stupid
Dame Edna special.
And a one, and a two,
and a three--
" Ba-bum-bum-bum "
" Baby on board "
" How I've adored "
" That sign
on my car's windowpane "
Hello!
Human Fly here.
Come on! I stayed up all night
dyeing my underwear.
Extra, extra!
Be Sharps sing on rooftop!
What?
Give me one of those!
Wait a minute.
There's nothing in here about the Be Sharps!
- Come back here!
- Ha-ha!
"[ Singing Continues, Indistinct ]
- It's been done.
- [ Tires Screech ]
- Pretty, huh, Chief?
- It sure is, Lou. It sure is.
Get the tear gas.
" Each trip's
a trip to paradise "
"With my baby "
" On board "
[ Applause, Cheering ]
www.tvsubtitles.net