The Simpsons
D'oh!
Milhouse, do you ever think about
the people in those cars?
I try not to.
It makes it harder to spit on 'em.
Sometimes I wonder
about all the people in this town.
Do you think anything interesting
ever happens to 'em?
I mean, there must be thousands
of great stories out there.
What do you think, Milhouse?
- Milhouse.
- Huh? Oh. Sorry. I saw a convertible.
- You were saying?
- Forget it.
Come on. It's 11:00.
I need some sugar.
I wish you'd come to my party, Apu.
You could use some merriment.
Listen. Serving the customer
is merriment enough for me.
Thank you. Come again.
You see? Most enjoyable.
Oh, I guarantee a wingding
of titanic proportions.
You will be there
or kindly be square.
Well, I don't like to
leave the store, but...
for the next five minutes I'm going to party
like it's on sale for 19.99.
Quick, quick. No time to cook them.
They will plump in my stomach.
Whoo. Hello, beautiful.
- No ring, I see. So you are
only arranged to be married.
Ooh, ooh, ooh! I love this song.
Let us boogie.
Whoo. I am hot.
Let us get out of here.
Don't worry. I'll tell everybody
you were untouchable.
Whoa.
Whoo!
Well, Sanjay, never have I partied
so hearty. Same time next year, yeah?
Yes!
Made it.
And with one minute to spare.
You took four minutes of my life,
and I want them back.
Oh, I'd only
waste 'em anyway.
Swing Serenade is brought
to you by Gorman's ear guards.
Guard your ears!
With Gorman's.
Mom, Dad threw his beer can
at the Miracle-Gro guy on TV.
- Can I recycle it?
- Why not?
There's gum in my hair!
- Mom! Someone threw gum in my hair!
- Are you sure?
Maybe it's just shampoo.
That washes right out.
No. It's somebody's
gross gum!
Get it out! Ow!
Ow! It's pulling out
my hair.
Wait. If I remember my Heloise,
the trick to getting out gum...
is peanut butter.
There. Now, that gum
should lift right out.
Ow.
Maybe it needs a little mayonnaise
to get going.
Okay. You go sit in the sun
and let it melt in.
Hmph. Why me?
Yuck. I smell like a sandwich.
Smithers, what's the meaning of
this slacking off?
There's a bee in my eye, sir.
- And?
- I- I'm allergic to bee stings.
They cause me to, uh, die.
But we're running out of
forward momentum.
Uh, perhaps you could pedal
for just a little while, sir.
Quite impossible.
I can try to bat him off if you like.
Uh, really, that's o-
Holy cats, man.
We're starting to wobble.
Get me to a hospital.
You have to pedal.
Oh, "tuddle" Sunday trousers.
Fear not. I'll get you
to a hospital-
the only way I know how.
Smithers, you infernal ninny. Stick your
left hoof on that flange now!
Now, if you can get it through
your bug-addled brain...
jam that second mephitic clodhopper
of yours on the right doodad.
Now pump those scrawny chicken legs,
you stuporous funker!
One more jostle,
you wretched shirk-a-day.
Help me.
Holy smokes!
You need booze.
- Hi, everybody!
- Hi, Dr. Nick.
Dr. Nick, this malpractice committee has
received a few complaints against you.
Of the 160 gravest charges,
the most troubling are:
performing major operations with a knife
and fork from a seafood restaurant-
But I cleaned them
with my napkin.
misuse of the cadavers-
I get here earlier when I drive
in the car pool lane.
There's a crazy man
with a scalpel in E.R.!
He's demanding
to see a quack.
Hi, everybody.
Now, tell Dr. Nick where is the trouble.
I'm edgy.
I got ants in my pants.
I'm discombobulated!
Get me a calmative!
Slow down, sir.
You're going to give yourself skin failure.
Okay. Now, the symptoms
you describe point to "bonus eruptus. "
It's a terrible disorder where the skeleton tries
to leap out the mouth and escape the body.
Now you're talkin'.
Our one chance is
"transdental electromicide. "
I'll need a golf cart motor
with a 1,000-volt "capacimator," stat!
Doctor, I can't
in good conscience-
Aaah!
Now there's no time, man!
We'll have to improvise.
- Oh.
- Keep doing that every five seconds.
Dr. Nick, we owe you an apology.
- Consider the charges dropped.
- All right!
Free nose jobs for everybody!
- Ay.! You first.
- Give me a Van Heflin.
Say, uh, Barn, uh, remember when I said I'd have
to send away to NASA to calculate your bar tab?
Oh, yeah. We all had a good laugh, Moe.
The results came back today.
You owe me $70 billion.
- Hmm.
- No. Wait, wait, wait.
That's for the Voyager spacecraft.
Um, your tab's $14 billion.
Well, alls I got is 2,000 bucks.
Well, that's halfway there.
Ha. Freeze, dude. Move a muscle
and I'll blow this wino's head off.
I'm behind three inches
of bulletproof glass. Do your worst.
All right.
No. Stay out of there.
Stay out of there! Oh! Good God, no!
Ho! Good-bye student loan payments.
Ha, ha!
Come back here, you stinkin'-
Hey. I wonder
how much air is in here.
Well, Seymour, I made it-
despite your directions.
Ah. Superintendent Chalmers.
Welcome.
- I hope you're prepared for an unforgettable luncheon.
- Yeah.
Oh, egads!
My roast is ruined.
But what if...
I were to purchase fast food
and disguise it as my own cooking?
Delightfully devilish, Seymour.
Ah-
Skinner
with his crazy explanations
The superintendent's
gonna need his medication
When he hears Skinner's
lame exaggerations
There'll be trouble
in town tonight
Seymour!
Superintendent, I was just-
uh, just stretching my calves on the windowsill.
Isometric exercise.
Care to join me?
Why is there smoke coming out of
your oven, Seymour?
Uh- Oh. That isn't smoke.
It's steam.
Steam from the steamed clams we're having.
Mmm. Steamed clams.
Whew.
Superintendent, I hope you're ready for
mouthwatering hamburgers.
I thought we were having
steamed clams.
D'oh, no. I said steamed hams.
That's what I call hamburgers.
You call hamburgers
steamed hams?
Yes. It's a regional dialect.
- Uh-huh. Uh, what region?
- Uh, upstate New York.
Really. Well, I'm from Utica, and I've never
heard anyone use the phrase "steamed hams. "
Oh, not in Utica. No.
It's an Albany expression.
I see.
You know, these hamburgers are quite similar
to the ones they have at Krusty Burger.
Oh, no.
Patented Skinner burgers.
Old family recipe.
- For steamed hams.
- Yes.
Yes. And you call them steamed hams despite
the fact that they are obviously grilled.
Ye-
You know, the-
One thing I should-
- Excuse me for one second.
- Of course.
Well, that was wonderful.
A good time was had
by all. I'm pooped.
Yes. I should be- Good Lord!
What is happening in there?
- Aurora borealis.
- Uh-
Aurora borealis
at this time of year...
at this time of day
in this part of the country...
localized entirely
within your kitchen?
- Yes.
- May I see it?
No.
Seymour.! The house is on fire.!
No, Mother. It's just
the northern lights.
Well, Seymour,
you are an odd fellow...
but I must say
you steam a good ham.
Help.! Help.!
"Helms calls for
doughnut tax. "
There. Done and done.
Oh.! Why did I have to stop at the railroad tracks?
Better get some change.
It's okay. It's okay.
I'm back.
See? Daddy's here.
Come on, Maggie.
Maybe if you just squeeze a little.
That's it. That's it. I-
D'oh!
Okay, okay. Think, Homer.
The dog.
Okay. Go, boy!
Go find help.
Go find help, boy.
No! Bad dog! Bad dog!
Oh. Don't worry, Maggie.
I'll think of something.
Who's that little baby?
You know, I went to the McDonald's
in, uh, Shelbyville on Friday night.
- The Mc-what?
- Uh, McDonald's restaurant.
I- I never heard of it
either, but, uh...
- they have over 2,000 locations in this state alone.
- Must have sprung up overnight.
You know the funniest thing though?
It's the little differences.
- Example.
- Well, at McDonald's you can buy a Krusty Burger with cheese.
But they don't call it
a Krusty Burger with cheese.
- Get out. Well, what do they call it?
- A Quarter Pounder with cheese.
Quarter Pounder with cheese?
Well, I can picture
the cheese, but, uh-
Do they have Krusty partially gelatinated
nondairy gum-based beverages?
Mm-hmm.
They call 'em shakes.
"Shakes. " You don't know what you're gettin'.
Well, I know what I'm gettin'-
some doughnuts.
Uh, help me out of
the booth, boys.
Ay. Que día miserable
a trabajo.
Primero, el ataque
del "woodpeckero" loco.
Luego, un "desastro"
de electricidad.
E finalmente, una "catástrofía"
con una pelota de baseball.
Tiempo para "relaxar"en paz y quieto.
Ay.!: Naranjas en la cabeza.!
Whoa!
Ay.!: Una "candelabra"
"precariosa".!
No, no, no, no, no.!
Ay. Dónde está mi tequila?
Doughnuts
I got doughnuts, I got-
Hey. I know you.
Hey, hey. Wait up.
We gotta swap insurance info.
Hey!
Hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
Hold it right there. Looks like the spider
caught himself a couple of flies.
Come on, boy.
This is the spot right here.
That's a good boy.
Good boy.
Do your dirty,
sinful business.
Howdy, Reverend Lovejoy.
Nice to see you there...
on my lawn with...
your dog.
Oh. Uh, oh.
Bad dog.
Look at that.
Right on Ned's lawn.
Now, how could you do
such a thing?
Good boy.
Don't stop now. Bad dog!
- I condemn you to hell.
- Better get the old snow shovel back from Homer, huh?
Good boy.
Don't stop the music.
Marge Simpson. Still making juice
the old-fashioned way?
No. I've got gum
in my hair.
Oh, we've tried everything.
Olive oil, lemon juice,
tartar sauce, chocolate syrup...
gravy, bacon fat,
hummus and baba ghanoush.
My scalp hurts
from horsefly bites.
Why don't you freeze it with an ice cube
and hit it with a hammer?
- Works for me when I get bubbly gum in the old push broom.
- That sounds okay.
Aaah! Aaah!
- Stop! Stop!
- Hmm.
I seem to have mashed
more hair into it. Oh, well.
Ice cubes are useless, man.
Chewing gum's got to be chewed out.
Does the whole town
have to hear about this?
Arr! Have ye tried
a Baltic squid?
They can suck the bolts
out of a submarine's hull.
All right! Fangoria will give me
25 bucks for this shot.
I can give you the name of
a good gum and hair man.
I have a word of advice.
Don't try to dig gum out with a bone.
It just makes things worse.
Leave it in as evidence.
Bazooka Joe's got deep pockets.
Perhaps I can help. My papa is foreman
of the Düsseldorf Gum Works.
Some folk'll never eat a skunk
but then again some folk'll
Like Cletus
the Slack-Jawed Yokel
Hey. What's goin' on on this side?
Hey, Brandine. You might could wear
these to your job interview.
And scuff up
the topless dancin' runway?
- Nah. You best bring 'em back where from you got 'em.
- Okay.
Back you go...
to waits for a woman
of less discriminatin' tastes.
Most folk'll never lose a toe
and then again, some folk'll
Like Cletus
the Slack-Jawed Yokel
Hey. You know what?
I could call my ma
while I'm up here.
Hey, Ma!
Get off the dang roof!
Yes. And one with
extra cheese.
- Thank you.
- C-Can I use your bathroom?
No. You may not.
The bathroom is for paying customers only.
- If you purchase an item, you may use the bathroom.
- Okay.
Um, how about that?
That is a rare photo
of Sean Connery signed by Roger Moore.
- It is worth $ 150.
- What can I get for 75 cents?
You may purchase
this charming Hamburglar Adventure.
A child has already solved theJumble
using crayons. The answer is "fries. "
Uh, Milhouse,
what's going on?
You said you just needed to use the bathroom.
Now I find you buying comics.
Oh, our transaction is completed.
You may take the boy.
Wait!
As soon as Zed gets here, the party will begin.
There he is now.
- Who are you?
- Uh, can my son use your bathroom?
- You gotta say yes!
- Okay, but be quick.
It's in back.
Uh, so, uh,
n-nice store.
Uh, you know, when I was a kid this used to be
a pet store.
Yeah. Right over there against that wall
there was the cutest little-
Get in the corner.
Hey, Dad.
Can we get this, please?
Oh, my gosh.
Sorry, mister.
Want me to cut off the gum
or just style it?
Cut it off,
but be careful.
Don't worry, sweetheart.
I know how important hair is to a little girl.
You keep squirming, there's going to be
a little bald girl with no lollipop.
I love it.
I finally look like
a real person. Thanks.
Ha-ha!
Crud.
- He's down there.
- Crud.!
Do you find something comical
about my appearance...
- when I am driving my automobile?
- Yeah.
Everyone needs to drive
a vehicle- even the very tall.
This was the largest auto
that I could afford.
Should I therefore be made
the subject of fun?
- I guess so.
- Wh- He-
Would you like it
if I laughed at your misfortune?
Huh? Maybe we should find out.
Now march.
Hey, everybody. Look at this.
It's that boy
who laughs at everyone.
Let's laugh at him.
Ha-ha!
Wave to the people.
Blow them kisses.
Well, Milhouse, I guess interesting stuff
does happen to people in Springfield.
Yep. Everybody in town's
got their story to tell.
There's just not
enough time to hear 'em all.
Oh. Sorry I'm late.
There was trouble at the lab with the running
and the exploding and the crying.
One of the monkeys stole
the glasses off my head.
Oh, no, wait.
Please, no. Please.
I have a funny story, if you listen.
I even wrote theme music.
Listen.
Hey. Hey.
Professor Frink
He'll make you laugh
He'll make you think
He likes to run
and then the thing with the
Person
Oh, boy.
That monkey is going to pay.
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net