The Simpsons
D'oh!
May I offer my condolences
on the untimely passing...
of your Great-aunt Hortense.
As her only living heirs,
you stand to inherit her entire estate.
Poor Aunt Hortense.
Whoo-hoo. Whoo-hoo.
The only stipulation
is that you spend one night...
in a haunted house.
- Oh. Isn't that somewhat unusual?
- No. It's a standard clause.
Well, luckily, there's
no such thing as ghosts.
Yes, there's no such thing
as ghosts.
Best night's sleep
I ever had.
Their tap water
tasted better than ours.
Here you go- $100 each.
The rest goes
to Ann Landers...
as was stipulated
in your aunt's will.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I must have continued talking
after you left the office.
I do that sometimes.
Oh, my.
What are you gonna
spend your money on, kids?
There's a special on tacos
down at the Taco Mat-
hundred tacos for $100-
I'm gonna get that.
I'm gonna contribute my money to
the Corporation for Public Broadcasting.
Tacos? Public broadcasting?
I won't have you kids
throwing away your money like that.
You're both coming downtown with me,
and you're gonna put that money in the bank.
Boy, I sure could go for 100 tacos
right about now.
No.
Yes, this should provide adequate
sustenance for the Doctor Who marathon.
You'll feel better
knowing your money's...
- in the hands of professionals.
- "Ook, ook. "
Are you folks ready
to go ape?
- Mom?
- A professional in an ape mask is still a professional.
And you'll find
that saving for your future...
is far more thrilling
than any roller coaster.
Really? Wow!
I should have started a long time ago.
Mm-hmm. Now fill out
these forms.
I'm sure you'll find them more exciting
than a weekend with Batman.
I got their new
Thrifty Saver savings account.
2.3% annual interest
instead of the normal 2.25.
So a year from now
I'll have an extra nickel.
I got the account where
you get free customized checks.
I chose the Hindenburg
flip-book series. Cool!
Hmm. Checking accounts aren't
really for children, Bart.
No, Mom, I can handle it.
Let's see.
Pay to the order of... Lisa-
One cent, and no cents.
And now the old John Hancock.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
A million dollars?
Thanks, Bart.
I owe you one.
That's a post-dated check,
remember.
- Don't cash it till the year 10,000.
- Okay.
Excellent.
As soon as the check clears, I'll let you go.
That's it. No more autographs.
I gotta go.
They're naming a new sandwich
after me at my restaurant.
It's okay, Bart. You can share mine.
Quick! Press against me
while the ink's still wet.
No need. I'm going to get
Krusty's autograph the easy way.
If he wants these 25 cents, he'll have to
endorse the check by signing it on the back.
Then, when my monthly
bank statement comes...
I'll get the check back,
complete with autograph.
No fuss, no muss.
That's a good plan...
but it won't
impress girls like this.
Ew!
Lisa's autograph.
Apu's autograph.
Oh, what do you know.
Jimbo's real name is Corky.
And... Krusty.
Hey! "Cayman Islands
Offshore Holding Corporation"?
Krusty was supposed
to sign this.
- Take it back and make him sign it.
- Uh, no, no.
Stamping the back of a check
is perfectly legal, little boy.
Many people do it
to save time.
You see, in this case,
instead of writing out his name...
Krusty has stamped the name of his
Cayman Islands Holding Corporation on the-
Hmm.
Uh, excuse me a minute.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I can't divulge information about
that customer's secret, illegal account.
Oh, crap. I shouldn't have said
he was a customer.
Oh, crap! I shouldn't
have said it was a secret.
Oh, crap! I certainly
shouldn't have said it was illegal.
It's too hot today.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
I bought this popcorn fair and square.
Sorry. The bank is-
Oh, kid, gosh.
I meant to tell you-
Turns out that Krusty is one
of the biggest tax cheats in history.
And they nailed him, all thanks to you.
Some might say
you're a hero, kid.
Not me, however.
I love Krusty.
Ladies and gentlemen, Krusty the Clown...
was arrested today
for massive tax fraud.
Krusty's years of tax "avoision"
would never have-
- What the heck is "avoision"?
- "Avoision"- It's a crime.
- Look it up. Would never have-
- "Evasion. " "Evasion. "
I don't say "evasion,"
I say "avoision. "
Would never have
come to light if not...
for a crafty little boy
named Bart Simpson.
Krusty's my hero.
How could I do this to him?
It is a tragedy
for all us kids...
but Bart, you can't
beat yourself up.
Yeah. There'll be enough people
to do that for me at recess tomorrow.
Oh, I can't go to jail!
I got a swanky lifestyle.
I'm used to the best.
Krusty, this is America.
We don't send our celebrities to jail.
We're just going
to garnish your salary.
Garnish my celery?
Please, Krusty. No jokes.
Who's joking?
Oh, I don't know
what you're saying.
It all sounds so crazy to me.
It simply means we'll be taking
part of your salary...
until your debt is repaid.
Say, 75% for 40 years.
- But I don't plan to live that long.
- Oh, better make it 95%.
Oy.
The Internal Revenue Service presents...
Herschel Krustofski's
Clown-Related...
Entertainment Show.
Hey, hey, kids.
Now that the Feds
are calling the shots...
this show's gotta be
a lot more cost-effective.
So we had to cut down on the frills...
like sets, props, costumes
and Sideshow Mel.
But that doesn't mean
we can't have fun.
For example, I sure wish somebody
would give me a banana cream pie. Yeah!
Uh-
I guess we can't afford
pies right now.
Well, throw something!
Oh, that corner!
Um, I'll have four Tax Burgers...
one "I.R.S. -wich"-
withhold the lettuce-
three dependent-size sodas...
and a "FICA-ccino. "
Fill out schedule "B." You should receive
your burgers in six to eight weeks.
Well, let's see here.
Add schedule "B" to line 53,
take away the-
Hey, Marge, what were your
gambling losses last year?
Seven hundred dollars.
They took my money,
they wrecked my show...
they buried a bunch
of stinking veterans in my family plot...
but at least I still got my memories.
Those are locked up safe
in my fabulous mansion.
And now, lot number 66,
a handmade leather suitcase...
carried by
the Krustofski family...
upon their arrival
at Ellis Island in 1902.
A priceless heirloom
and historic piece of"Krustyana. "
- What am I bid?
- Forty cents.
I got 40 cents.
Sold, for 40 cents.
Forty cents?
My grandpa Zev would
turn over in his grave...
if it wasn't filled
with some veteran.
Lot 67, 32 cartons
of pornography.
- Ten cents.
- Twelve.
Twelve cents to our phone bidder
in Japan. Any other bids?
All I brought is a dime.
I didn't know there'd be pornography.
- Sold, for 12 cents.
- Oh, my beloved pornography.
I can't watch this anymore.
- I'm going to bed.
- How much for Krusty's bed?
- Half a buck.
- Sold!
- Good night, everybody.
- Good night, Moe.
And now lot number 2,380-
Krusty's private plane...
- the I'm-On-A-Rolla Gay.
- But I love that plane.
I used to fly to Vegas in it
with Dean Martin.
One night he looked
out the window...
and the moon hit his eye
like a big pizza pie.
We wrote a song about it...
but it ended up infringing
on one he recorded years before.
Hey, Selma, that plane would
go great with your new suitcase.
Nah, I just bought it
to soak my feet in.
Krusty? Hi. Is it okay
if I sit down here?
Aah. Go ahead, kid.
Knock yourself out.
I'm sorry for all the trouble
I've caused you, Krusty...
but you know,
my mom says...
God never closes a door
without opening a window.
No offense, kid,
but your mom's a dingbat.
There's no silver lining here.
I was a big cheese-
a huge cheese!
But now look at me.
I gotta ride the bus like a schnook.
I gotta live in an apartment like an idiot.
I gotta wait in line with nobodies...
to buy groceries from a failure!
It doesn't matter how you live
or what you did wrong.
As long as you're on TV,
people will respect you.
Respect? Pah!
What good is respect
without the moola to back it up?
Everywhere I go
I see teachers in Ferraris-
research scientists
drinking champagne.
I tried to drink
a Coke on the bus...
and they took away my pass.
That's no life
for a famous clown.
Well, if it'll make you
feel any better, Krusty...
you can punch me in the face.
Nah, forget it.
Go home, kid.
Shiva H. Vishnu!
Where is that noise coming from?
I must say,
I've had a lovely evening, Agnes.
I don't suppose
I could come in for a cup of-
- Seymour!
- Mother. Superintendent Chalmers!
- Skinner!
- What I wouldn't give for something...
to interrupt this awkward moment.
That'll do nicely.
- You gotta hand it to Krusty.
- Yeah.
Even with all his problems,
he's still willing...
to do something
unbelievably dangerous...
just to entertain his fans.
Wow.
Oh, that's my Krusty.
I got a feeling he'll be all right.
Oh, my God!
Krusty's shoes!
Okay, folks, show's over.
Nothing to see here.
Show's-
Oh, my God!
A horrible plane crash!
Hey, everybody, get a load
of this flaming wreckage.
Come on, crowd around. Crowd around.
Don't be shy. Crowd around.
Ladies and gentlemen...
Krusty the Clown is dead.
- I can't believe Krusty's really gone.
- Don't worry, son.
I'm sure he's up
in heaven right now...
laughing it up with all
the other celebrities-
John Dillinger, Ty Cobb,
Joseph Stalin.
I wish I were dead.
We're gathered
to mourn the passing...
of Herschel Schmoeckel Krustofski...
beloved entertainer
and dear friend.
Hello. I'm Troy McClure.
You might remember me
from such show business funerals...
as "Andre the Giant,
We Hardly Knew Ye"...
and "Shemp Howard:
Today We Mourn a Stooge. "
Now, Krusty's closest friend
and sidekick...
Sideshow Mel.
I'll miss you, Krusty-
I and all
the other Sideshows-
except Sideshow Bob.
But, in the midst of our sorrow...
we can take comfort in the fact
that your elevated blood-alcohol level...
probably helped you burn up quicker.
Since you left us no earthly remains...
it is my sad duty to unveil
this simple memorial.
Next in our cavalcade of
celebrity mourners- Bob Newhart.
Uh-
See, uh-
To tell you the truth, I'm, uh-
I was just-
I'm just killing time here.
I was waiting for a...
well, a different-
different funeral to start.
I'll handle it.
Bob Newhart, everybody!
Oh, uh-
Although, you know-
Though I started my career...
several years before Krusty, so...
you know, I could never
really have learned anything...
directly from him...
still, I think, in a way-
in a very meaningful way-
that, uh- that I- uh- uh-
all of us-
have, uh- have learned from him.
You know, that is, by being,
uh, on television for-
for- for so many years.
Even- Even though...
you know, m-many of us, we-
we didn't-
we didn't watch his show.
Th-Thank you.
Well, that's the funeral, folks.
We'll be sitting shivah at the Friar's Club
at 7:00 p. m., and again at 10:00.
You must be over 18 for the 10:00.
It gets a little blue.
And so, Herschel Krustofski...
is gone, but not forgotten.
Today was the unveiling
of the new Krusty stamp.
Postal patrons were asked to choose
between two competing designs-
one of Krusty's
heartwarming smile...
and one of his fiery death.
By a nearly two-to-one vote,
the smiling Krusty was chosen.
Don't let Krusty's death
get you down, boy.
People die all the time...
just like that.
Why, you could
wake up dead tomorrow.
Well, good night.
Krusty!
Mom! I just saw Krusty!
- Yes, dear, in your mind.
- No, on the street.
- On the street in your mind.
- Why won't you believe me?
Sweetheart, maybe you just
want Krusty to be alive so badly...
you think you see him
everywhere.
I went through the same thing
when Lyndon Johnson died.
And these pills
will help with the queasiness.
Krusty? Dr. Hibbert, who was that man?
Now, Bart, telling you...
would violate
the patient-doctor privilege...
just as if I were to tell you that
Jasper here has five seconds to live.
- What'd he say?
- He said I'm next.
Am I going crazy?
I'm seeing Krusty everywhere.
Bart, you're seeing
Krusty everywhere...
because you want to tell him
you're sorry for causing his death.
Would it help if I told you
you're not responsible...
- for Krusty's death?
- Yes. Yes, it would.
Well, I can't. You'll just have to learn
to live with your mental problem.
Wait a minute. All those things I saw-
there's a connection.
The truck full
of nets and buckets...
the queasy guy, the lobsters-
They all point to one thing.
Follow me.
Arr! I've got some customers.
Call me back, Ishmael.
Ahoy there, minnows.
Ahoy. Have you seen this man?
Arr! That's Handsome Pete.
He dances for nickels.
Pete, ye got some customers.
No, we're looking for this man-
Krusty the Clown.
Hmm. N'arr, n'arr, n'arr.
It's hopeless, Bart. We've searched
up and down these docks...
from pier one
to that Pier 1 by pier 17.
Lisa, look-a signature
with stars around it, just like Krusty's.
"Rory B. Bellows, slip eight. "
Let's go!
Not a quarter!
Arr! He'll be dancing for hours.
- Are you Rory B. Bellows?
- Yes.
- How about Krusty the Clown?
- Sorry. I don't do impressions.
Well, if you're not Krusty, how come
you have the exact same signature as him?
I'm Rory Bellows, I tell you...
and I got a lot of
corroborating evidence...
over here...
by the throttle!
You know,
you two could have said something...
instead of letting me
make an ass of myself.
Hey, you got a pacemaker scar,
just like Krusty.
And Krusty's
superfluous third nipple.
Can't you see I don't want
to be Krusty anymore?
- That's why I faked my death.
- But we saw your plane crash.
Yeah, but I wasn't in it.
Just before I hit
the mountain, I jumped out of the plane...
into a carefully placed net.
Now that we've blown your cover, I guess
you gotta come back and do your show again.
Or kill us.
I won't be coming back, kids.
I got a sweet life here.
The sea air is clearing
my lungs...
the sun is toasting
my pale skin a healthy brown...
and most important, I learned
that I don't need money to be happy.
All that high living
just distracted me...
from my true calling in life-
salvaging sunken barges...
for scrap iron.
Sorry, kids. There's nothing left
for me on dry land anymore.
But Krusty, what about
all the kids who depend on you...
to brighten up
their afternoons?
- Are you gonna turn your back on them?
- Yes!
Come on, Lise. Krusty doesn't
want our attention anymore.
Let's go worship somebody
who has the guts to be a celebrity.
Yeah. Krusty doesn't
want to be a clown.
He's happy just being
another blue-collar bozo.
Meh!
Krusty's tired
of having phonies around...
pretending to be his friends.
I'm sure he'll find plenty of people
who'll like him for who he is.
Uh, it could happen.
Aw, who needs friends?
The incessant beep
of the global positioning system...
is all the companionship I need.
Tell me where you are now,
you bastard!
All right, I admit it.
I miss the phonies.
That's all I miss-
that and ShirleyJones's and Marty Ingels's
New Year's Eve party.
What about that great feeling you get from
knowing you're better than regular people?
What about being an illiterate TV clown...
who's still more respected
than all the scientists...
doctors and educators
in the country put together?
Yeah! I'm not gonna let those guys
hog all the respect...
while I'm out here on some stinkin' tub.
That's just what
those eggheads want.
Well, forget it, poindexter,
'cause Krusty's back in town!
Yea!
So, Krusty, what are you gonna do
about your tax problem?
Don't sweat it.
The life of Rory B. Bellows
is insured...
for a surprisingly large amount.
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net