The Simpsons
D'oh!
- Are we there yet?
- No.
- Where are we going?
- We're going to Storytown Village, Grampa.
It's an amusement park for babies.
- Oh! Just leave me in the car with the window open a crack.
- That's the plan.
I think it's nice we're doing something
Maggie will enjoy for once.
Besides, I'm sure Storytown Village
is also fun for everyone...
from eight to God only knows.
Come out. Come out
or I'll blow your house in.
Not by the hairs
on our chinny chin chins.
- What a load of crappy crap crap!
- Quiet, boy.
I have a feeling some bad stuff
is about to go down.
This is where the wolf
blows down the pigs' house.
He blows, all right.
He blows big-time.
That's it, honey.
Get into the spirit.
Uh, it was good,
but not great.
Somebody's been sleeping
in my bed.
Somebody's been sleeping in my bed.
Somebody's been sleeping
in my bed.
Well, I'm sorry.
But it was a 150 degrees in the car.
So long, su-Aah!
Come on! Eat the can!
Come on!
You're supposed to feed them pellets
from the machine over there.
Huh?
Oh, my!
Out of the way, you.!
Ahhh.
Oh, you are so cute.
Yes, you are. You are.
I just love you.
See? It was a good idea
to come here after all.
Attention, families. This is Mother Goose.
The following cars
have been broken into-
Hmm?
Allemande left
and do-si-diddley-diddley-do
Swing your partner
to-and-froodilly-fro
- All rightilly-dightilly.
- Hey, Flanders.
Hidilly-ho, neighboreeno!
- Shut up!
- Okilly-dokilly.
So, Ned, you're having a family reunion
and you didn't invite me?
Oh, gosh, Homer.
This is strictly a Flanders affair.
I got family here
from around the globe.
- Here's José Flanders.
- Buenos ding-dong-diddly-días, senor.
- And this is Lord Thistlewick Flanders.
- Charmed.
Eh, a-googilly-doogilly.
I can't believe you didn't invite me, after I
painted those cool stripes all over your car.
I know! I'll throw my own barbecue!
The greatest barbecue
this town has ever seen.
And I'll only invite who I want.
That'll show you.
- Can I come?
- Sure. D'oh!
This barbecue will be hard, thankless work.
But I'm sure you're up to it, Marge.
Well, it could be a good chance to get to know
our neighbors outside of a courtroom setting.
You know what
you should serve, Marge?
More of these lamb chops.
These are the best ever.
Why, thank you, Homie.
You might say
the extra ingredient is salt.
Please, Lisa.
I thought you loved me.
Loved me.
What's wrong, Lisa?
Didn't you get enough lamb chops?
I can't eat this.
I can't eat a poor little lamb.
Lisa, get ahold of yourself.
This is "lamb," not "a lamb. "
What's the difference between this lamb
and the one that kissed me?
This one spent
two hours in the broiler.
Bart, sensible bites.!
All right, Lisa.
If you don't want lamb chops,
there's lots of other things I can make.
Chicken breast,
rump roast...
- hot dogs.
- No, I can't!
- I can't eat any of them!
- Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
Lisa, honey, are you saying you're
never going to eat any animal again?
- What about bacon?
- No.
- Ham?
- Pork chops?
- Dad!
Those all come from the same animal!
Oh, yeah, right, Lisa.
A wonderful, magical animal.
I think Lisa's right, Dad.
Eating meat is ba-a-a-ad.
Hey, that's my chop!
Oh, my family just doesn't understand
my newfound vegetarianism.
Compared to them, the public schools
are a haven of enlightenment.
Okay, class,
time to dissect our worms.
First, pin them down so they don't
fly up and hit you in the eye.
- Um, Miss Hoover?
- Yes, Ralph? What is it?
My worm went in my mouth
and then I ate it. Can I have a new one?
No, Ralph.
There aren't any more.
Just try to sleep
while the other children are learning.
Oh, boy! Sleep!
That's where I'm a Viking.
Lisa, what did I ever do to you-ou-ou?
Why does it talk like a lamb?
Uh, Miss Hoover, I don't think I can dissect
an animal. I think it's wrong.
Okay, Lisa.
I respect your moral objection.
Um, excuse me.
- Isn't there anything here that doesn't have meat in it?
- Possibly the meat loaf.
Well, I believe you're required to
provide a vegetarian alternative.
Yum. It's rich
in bunly goodness.
Do you remember when you lost
your passion for this work?
- Uh-oh. Two independent
thought alarms in one day.
The students are over-stimulated.
Willie, remove all the colored chalk
from the classrooms.
I warned ya!
Didn't I warn ya?
That colored chalk was
forged by Lucifer himself!
The Itchy and Scratchy Show
Mmm!
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm.
Mmm!
I never realized before,
but some Itchy and Scratchy cartoons...
send the message that violence
against animals is funny.
Say what?
Cartoons don't have messages, Lisa.
They're just a bunch of hilarious stuff,
you know, like people getting hurt and stuff.
- Stuff like that- Ohh!
- Look, kids.
I just got my party invitations
back from the printers.
"Come to Homer's BBBQ.
The extra 'B' is for BYOBB."
- What's that extra "B" for?
- That's a typo.
Dad, can't you have some other kind of party?
One where you don't serve meat?
But all normal people love meat.
If I went to a barbecue and there was no meat,
I would say, "Yo, goober! Where's the meat?"
I'm trying to impress people here, Lisa.
You don't win friends with salad.
You don't win friends
with salad
You don't win friends with salad
You don't win friends
with salad
You don't win friends with salad
You don't win
friends with salad
You don't win friends with salad
You don't win friends
with salad
- You don't win friends with salad
- Mom!
I didn't mean to take sides.
I just got caught up in the rhythm.
Good morning, class.
A certain... agitator-
For privacy's sake,
let's call her Lisa S.
No, that's too obvious.
Uh, let's say L. Simpson-
has raised questions
about certain school policies.
So, in the interest of creating an open dialogue,
sit silently and watch this film.
Nothing beats a stroll
in cattle country.
Hi, I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me from such educational
films as Two Minus Three Equals Negative Fun.!
- And Firecrackers: The Silent Killer.
- Mr. McClure?
- Oh, hello, Bobby.
- Jimmy.
I'm curious as to how meat gets
from the ranch to my stomach.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow down, Jimmy.
You just asked a mouthful.
It all starts here
in the high-density feedlot.
Then when the cattle are just right-
Mmm!
it's time for them to "graduate"
from Bovine University.
Come on, Jimmy.
Let's take a peek at the killing floor.
Don't let the name throw you, Jimmy.
It's not really a floor.
It's more of a steel grating...
that allows material to sluice through
so it can be collected and exported.
Getting hungry, Jimmy?
Uh, Mr. McClure,
I have a crazy friend...
who says it's wrong
to eat meat.
- Is he crazy?
- No, just ignorant.
You see, your crazy friend
never heard of the food chain.
- Just ask this scientician.
- Uh-
He'll tell you that in nature one creature
invariably eats another to survive.
Don't kid yourself, Jimmy.
If a cow ever got the chance,
he'd eat you and everyone you care about.
Wow, Mr. McClure! I was a Grade A moron
to ever question eating meat.
Yes, you were, Jimmy. Yes, you were.
Ow. You're hurting me.
They can't seriously expect us
to swallow that tripe.
Now as a special treat,
courtesy of our friends at the meat council...
please help yourselves to this tripe.
Stop it.!
Don't you realize you've just been
brainwashed by corporate propaganda?
Apparently, my crazy friend here
hasn't heard of the food chain.
Yeah. Lisa's a Grade A moron.
When I grow up,
I'm going to Bovine University.
Hi, Homer.
Thanks for inviting me to your barbecue.
Whoa, Barney!
You brought a whole beer keg!
Yeah. Where can I fill it up?
Wait, Dad.!
Good news, everyone.!
You don't have to eat meat!
I made enough gazpacho for all!
- I don't like gazpacho.
- What's that anyway?
It's tomato soup served ice cold.
Go back to Russia.
Ah, diagnosis... delicious.
I've got the prescription
for you, Doctor.
Another hot beef injection.
Hey, Homer. Bring me another one of them,
uh, burgers, would you?
I can't quite seem to...
stand up under my own power anymore.
One whopper for the copper.
- Another burger, Dad?
- Here you go!
It's bad enough
they're all eating meat.
They don't have to
rub it in my face.
Okay, everybody. It's the moment
you've all been waiting for.
The pig de résistance.
Look at his nose.
Congratulations, Homer.
Your "Q" is a huge success.
Hey, a toast to the host
who can boast the most roast!
Thanks, Flanders.
I have to agree that
everything certainly- Huh?
Bart! No!
- What?
- Sorry. Force of habit.
Lisa! No!
Uhh! Ohh!
It's just a little dirty.
It's still good. It's still good.
It's just a little slimy.
It's just a little airborne.
It's still good. It's still good.
- It's gone.
- I know.
You know, Smithers, I think I'll donate
a million dollars to the local orphanage...
when pigs fly.
- That's a good one. Hey- Hey-
- Wh-Wha-
- Will you be donating that million dollars now, sir?
- No. I'd still prefer not.
Give it up, Dad.
Piggy ain't coming back.
Lisa, you ruined my barbecue!
I demand you apologize this second!
I'm never, ever apologizing,
because I was standing up for a just cause!
And you were
wrong, wrong, wrong!
- Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm going to my room!
- That's it! Go to your room!
Marge, since I'm not talking to Lisa...
would you please ask her
to pass me the syrup?
Please pass your father the syrup, Lisa.
Bart, tell Dad I'll only pass the syrup
if it won't be used on any meat product.
You dunking your sausages
in that syrup, homeboy?
Marge, tell Bart I just want to drink
a nice glass of syrup like I do every morning.
Tell him yourself.
You're ignoring Lisa, not Bart.
Bart, thank your mother
for pointing that out.
Homer, you're not not talking to me.
And, secondly, I heard what you said.
Lisa, tell your mother
to get off my case.
Uh, Dad, Lisa's the one
you're not talking to.
- Bart, go to your room!
- Why don't you just eat him, Dad?
I don't need any serving
suggestions from you...
you barbecue-wrecking,
know-nothing, know-it-all.
That's it! I can't live in a house
with this prehistoric carnivore!
I am out of here!
That's it!
Go to your room!
Look! It's Mrs. Potato Head.
She has a head made out of lettuce.
I can't believe
I used to go out with you.
Are you gonna marry a carrot, Lisa?
Yes, I'm gonna marry a carrot.
- She admitted it!
- She admitted she's gonna marry a carrot!
I can't believe it.
Your windows.
Mmm! The next-
The whole world wants me to eat meat!
I can't fight it anymore!
There! Is everybody happy now?
I take it from your yelling
that you like my tofu dogs.
- Tofu?
- Oh, yes. No meat whatsoever.
And only thrice the fat
of a normal hot dog.
- I made the switch and nobody noticed.
- But why, Apu?
Because I'm a vegetarian.
Haven't you ever seen my T-shirt?
- That's cute.
- Here. Let me show you something, Lisa.
Wow! A secret staircase.
But what do you do if somebody
wants a nonalcoholic beer?
You know, it's never come up.
Oh, Apu, it's beautiful.
Yes. This is where I come when I need
some refuge from the modern world...
or when I want to see
drive-in movies for free.
I know it is not easy
to be a vegetarian, Lisa.
- That's why I ran away from home.
- What? She's leaving home?
Wow.! Paul McCartney.!
I read about you in history class.
But where's your wife, Linda?
Right here, Lisa.
Whenever we're in Springfield...
we like to hang out
in Apu's garden in the shade.
We met him in India years ago
during the Maharishi days.
- Back then I was known as the fifth Beatle.
- Sure you were, Apu.
You know what, Lisa?
Paul and Linda are vegetarians too.
In fact, Linda has her own line
of vegetarian entrees.
Apu, I'm sure the last thing
they want to talk about is-
We weren't satisfied with
the other vegetarian meals on the market.
You'd be surprised how often
you'd find a big hunk of pork in them.
- Ew!
- Linda and I both feel strongly about animal rights.
In fact, if you play
"Maybe I'm Amazed" backwards...
you'll hear a recipe
for a really ripping lentil soup.
When will all those fools learn
that you can be perfectly healthy...
simply eating vegetables, fruits,
grains and cheese?
- Ooh, cheese!
- You don't eat cheese, Apu?
No, I don't eat any food
that comes from an animal.
Oh! Then you must think
I'm a monster.
Yes, indeed, I do think that.
But I learned long ago, Lisa, to tolerate others
rather than forcing my beliefs on them.
You know, you can influence
people without badgering them always.
It's like Paul's song,
"Live and Let Live. "
- It was "Live and Let Die. "
- Whatever, whatever. It had a good rhythm.
I guess I have been pretty hard on a lot of
people, especially my dad. Thanks, you guys.
Lisa, before you go,
would you like to hear a song?
- Wow! That'd be great!
- Okay. Take it, Apu.
Lisa.
Lisa!
Lisa, come back before everyone finds out
what a horrible father I am!
Hi, Dad.
Looking for me?
- I don't know. Were you looking for me?
- I don't know.
Oh, Lisa.
I was looking for you.
I wanted to apologize.
I don't know exactly what went wrong,
but I know it's always my fault.
Actually, Dad,
this time I was wrong-
- Oh.
- too.
While I was gone, I got some really good
advice from Paul and Linda McCartney.
Rock stars. Is there anything
they don't know?
I still stand by my beliefs.
But I can't defend what I did.
I'm sorry I messed up your barbecue.
I understand, honey. I used to
believe in things when I was a kid.
Come on! I'll give you
a piggyback ride- Uh, oops!
I mean,
a veggieback ride home.
Come on.
www.tvsubtitles.net