Live, from
the Springfield Civic Auditorium-
it's "The Simpsons 138th Episode Spectacular.!"
Hello, I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me from
such Fox Network specials as...
Alien NoseJob, and five fabulous
weeks of The Chevy Chase Show.
Tonight, we're here to honor
America's favorite...
non-prehistoric cartoon family.
You'll see long-lost footage...
never-before-seen material
from your favorite episodes...
old favorites you can't
see in syndication.
So join me, won't you, for
"The Simpsons 138th Episode Spectacular!"
The Simpsons
D'oh!
The Simpsons began
as the brainchild...
of cartoonist Matt Groening...
the already-famous creator
of such comics...
as Damnation, Johnny Reb...
and True Murder Stories.
In 1987, Groening teamed up
with award-winning producers...
James L. Brooks...
and Sam Simon.
And what better place
to premiere their creation...
than on The Tracy Ullman Show-
the nation's showcase
for psychiatrist jokes...
and musical comedy numbers.
On April 19, 1987, America
first met The Simpsons.
Well, good night, Son.
- Um, Dad?
- Yeah?
What is the mind?
Is it just a system of impulses...
or is it something tangible?
Relax. What is mind?
No matter.
What is matter? Never mind.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Good night, Son.
- Good night, Lisa.
- Good night, Mom.
- Sweet dreams.
- Thanks, Mom.
- Sleep tight.
- I will, Mom.
Don't let the bedbugs bite.
Bedbugs?
Sweet dreams.
We may be the best parents
in the world.
Mm. Good night, dear.
Good night.
All right. Climb in.
There's nothing to worry about.
Now everyone, go to sleep.
Good night.
Di-da.
They haven't changed a bit, have they?
As the weeks went on,
so did the cartoons.
Fresh chocolate chip
cookies.
Oh! Don't touch those yet.
They're very, very hot.
Aha! No one's around.
The perfect crime.
Yow!
Do I smell cookies?
Where's the cookies?
They're all gone,
the whole batch.
Somebody ate those cookies.
Did you eat
the cookies, Maggie?
I think she's trying
to tell us something.
- Go on, Maggie.
- Go on, Maggie. Go! Go!
There's no perfect crime.
Ohh!
I've got a great idea.
Let's play Space Patrol.!
I'll be Lee Suey, the devil-may-care
rocket pilot.
And Maggie can be Medina,
your spunky sidekick.
And you'll be-
Bartron, the evil robot
from Mars gone berserk.
Do I understand you correctly, Bartron?
Do you wish me to release you
from the Helmet of Evil Thoughts...
with my enchanted
space wand?
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
- I will do it, Bartron.
But who knows what mysterious forces
will be unleashed?
Oh, no. Inside the evil Bartron...
is a horrible, mutant boy.!
We'll be safe here
till Mom and Dad...
the Evil Overlords,
get home.
As wacky
as those kids were...
they were no match for Captain Wacky,
later renamed "Homer. "
Wake up, everybody! It's World War III!
Quick.! Down to the fallout shelter.!
The bombs are dropping.!
Eighteen seconds. Hmm.
If this were really a nuclear war,
we'd all be dead meat by now.
Say, you're all shivering.
Are you cold or what?
Bart.!
Bart.! Time for your
Sunday night bath, boy.!
Gotta hide.
Bart.! Huh.
Where are ya, boy?
- Oops.
- Aha!
There ya go!
Now, that's not so bad, is it?
Scrub good now.
Ahh.
Welcome
to zee exotic world of undersea explorer...
Bart Simpseau.
Come with Bart as he dive
into zee briny deep...
searching for the wily
and elusive washcloth.
Suddenly, without warning, zee brave boy
get more than he bargain for.
Help! Help!
Clean as a whistle, Homer.
Maybe the drawings were a little crude,
but all the characters were there.
Itchy and Scratchy,
Grampa Simpson...
and Krusty the Clown.
When we return,
more classic moments-
and, for
the first time on TV...
our private reel
of Simpsons outtakes...
including the alternate endings
to, "Who Shot Mr. Burns?"
The cash register says, "N.R.A.4ever. "
Just one of the hundreds of
radical, right-wing messages...
inserted into every show
by creator Matt Groening.
Over the six years The Simpsons
has been on the air...
we've received dozens of letters
from fans wanting to know...
more about the show.
Tonight, we'll answer
some of your questions.
Professor Lawrence Pierce
of the University of Chicago writes:
"I think Homer gets
stupider every year. "
That's not a question, professor.
But we'll let the viewers judge for themselves.
Hello, my name
is Mr. Burns.
- I believe you have a letter for me.
- Okay, Mr. Burns.
- Uh, what's your first name?
- I don't know.
Well, Homer, maybe you can
take some consolation...
in the fact that something you created
is making so many people happy.
"Ooh! Look at me.
I'm making people happy.
"I'm the magical man
from Happy Land...
in a gumdrop house
on Lollipop Lane. "
Oh, by the way,
I was being sarcastic.
Well, duh.
Yabba-dabba-doo!
Simpson, Homer Simpson
He's the greatest guy
in history
From the town of Springfield
He's about to hit
a chestnut tree
Hey, guys. Look
what I smuggled aboard.
Homer, no!
- Huh?
- They'll clog the instruments!
- Careful! They're ruffled!
- I'll take care of this.
Ahh-
Mmm.
Ants!
No TV and no beer
make Homer something something.
- Go crazy?
- Don't mind if I do!
Dr. Linus Irving of the Sloan-Kettering
Memorial Institute writes:
"How does Matt Groening
find the time to write and draw...
an entire Simpsons episode
every week?"
For the answer to this,
we went straight to the source.
Get outta my office!
Of course, what Matt meant to say...
according to his attorneys,
is that he couldn't possibly do it alone...
and he insisted that we make time to
acknowledge the hard work of everyone...
who makes The Simpsons possible.
Ambassador Henry Mwabwetumba
of the Ivory Coast writes:
"What is the real deal
with Mr. Burns's assistant, Smithers?
You know what
I'm talking about. "
Of course we do.
- The preparations for your birthday have begun.
- I won't get what I really want.
No one does.
Happy birthday, Mr. Smithers
Mmm.
- People like dogs, Mr. Burns.
- Nonsense.
Dogs are idiots.
Think about it, Smithers.
If I came into your house
and started sniffing at your crotch...
and slobbering all over your face,
what would you say?
Mmm. If you did it, sir?
- I'll, uh, print you out a copy.
- Thanks.
Hello. Smithers.
You're. Quite.
Good. At. Turning. Me. On.
Um, you probably
should ignore that.
Hmm. I dreamed about her
again last night, Smithers.
You know that dream where you're in bed,
and they fly in through the window?
Ahh.
As you can see,
the real deal with Waylon Smithers...
is that he's Mr. Burns's assistant.
He's in his early 40s, is unmarried,
and currently resides in Springfield.
Thanks for writing.
We'll be right back.
If you said "Bleeding Gums"
Murphy and Dr. Marvin Monroe...
you are wrong-
they were never popular.
Right about now
you're probably saying...
"Troy, I've seen
every Simpsons episode.
You can't show me
anything new. "
You've got
some attitude, mister.
Besides, you're wrong!
Because sometimes episodes run long...
and certain scenes
never get aired.
So, fire up your VCR, because here,
for the first time ever...
are the cutout classics.
When Krusty the Clown got canceled-
he tried everything to stay on the air.
Here's what you didn't see.
If you watch my show, I will
send you this book featuring me...
in a variety of
sexually explicit positions.
What? Oh. Hey! It's not really me.
I used a stunt butt.
Krusty, we're from the network.
We have some bad news.
- I'm afraid your show's been canceled.
- I thought this would happen.
I just hope you replace me
with something as educational...
and uplifting
as I tried to be.
Actually, it's a hemorrhoid infomercial
starring Claude Akins.
Can I play
"Hemorrhoid Sufferer Number One"?
- Ooh! Oh, that hurts! Aah! Oh, is there no relief?
- I don't think so.
Well, how about
one of the "after" guys?
Ahh! Oh, that's better.
- I can ride a bike again!
- Sorry.
Ohh.
When Springfield
legalized gambling...
Homer became
a blackjack dealer...
and comedy was
"in the cards. "
Twenty. Your move, Mr. Bond.
I'll take a hit, dealer.
Joker. You were supposed to
take those out of the deck.
- Oh, sorry. Here's another one.
- What is this card?
- "Rules for Draw and Stud Poker?"
- What a pity, Mr. Bond.
But-Well, it was Homer's fault.
I didn't lose. I never lose.
Well, at least tell me the details
of your plot for world domination.
I'm not going
to fall for that one again.
Earlier this year,
Homer's long-lost mother returned...
and so did a long-lost care package.
Mmm.
Homer, please. You don't have to
wolf down that 25-year-old candy...
- just to make me happy.
- But it won't make you unhappy, right?
Hey! Space food sticks!
Oh, I wish I had these
on my space adventure.
Did you know I was blasted into space
two years ago, Mom?
Oh, sure. I read all about it.
I mean-
It was national news.
Do you... still work for NASA?
- No, I work at the nuclear power plant.
- Oh, Homer.
Well, you'll be happy to know
I don't work very hard.
Actually, I'm bringing
the plant down from the inside.
When Homer sold his soul
for a doughnut...
he found out that hell isn't
all it's cracked up to be...
in these
never-before-broadcast scenes.
Mm, lawyers,
lawyers, lawyers-
Ooh, Lionel Hutz!
"Cases won in 30 minutes
or your pizza's free. " Hmm.
I'd sell my soul for
a Formula One racing car.
That can be arranged.
Changed my mind.
Sorry.
- Cool.
- Bart, stop pestering Satan!
Your Honor, we find
that Homer Simpson's soul...
is legally the property of Marge Simpson,
and not of the devil.
- Ohh.
- Yea!
Whoo-hoo! Ow!
Well, I didn't win.
Here's your pizza.
- But we did win.
- That's okay. The box is empty.
If that's what they cut out,
what they leave in...
must be pure gold!
Let's watch some more of those
fabulous Simpsons outtakes.
Apu living with the Simpsons?
It happened.
And here's a scene
you didn't see.
I'm hoping you enjoy this movie.
It made every Indian critic's
Top 400 list.
This movie you rented sucks.
No, it doesn't. It's funny.
Their clothes are different
from my clothes.
Look at what they're wearin'.
A few years back,
Bart was adopted by Mr. Burns.
In this very special outtake,
Homer attempts a reconciliation...
with his estranged son.
- Watch.
- Bart, you're coming home.
I want to stay here
with Mr. Burns.
I suggest you leave immediately.
Or what? You'll release
the dogs, or the bees...
or the dogs with bees
in their mouth...
and when they bark,
they shoot bees at you?
Well, go ahead.
Do your worst!
My worst, eh?
Smithers...
release the robotic Richard Simmons.
Come on, big boy!
Shake the butter off those buns!
Come on, girls. Shake, shake, shake.
Smithers, it's out of control.
I'll take him out, sir.
His ass is gonna blow!
This past summer, all of America
was trying to solve the mystery...
of"Who Shot Mr. Burns?"
Then they found out
it was the baby.
To keep this bombshell secret...
the producers animated several solutions
that were never intended to air.
And to keep the show's
animators, editors...
staff and hangers-on from
leaking the solution...
two completely different
endings were produced.
One real, one phony.
Here's the ending
you were never meant to see.
The one who shot me was-
Waylon Smithers!
No-o!
Wait a minute. Yes.
With the sun-blocker in place
and the town aghast, I was on top of the world.
So I wanted to kick up my heels
and indulge my sweet tooth.
I feel like celebrating.
Oh, it's you. What are you so happy about?
- I see.
- Smithers had thwarted my earlier attempt...
to take candy from a baby,
but with him out of the picture...
I was free to wallow
in my own crapulence.
Or so I thought.
At the last moment, Smithers,
drunk as a lemur...
lurched out of the darkness
and fired.!
That's right.
Right before I shotJasper.
Hmm. I was busy that night.
Stricken,
I lurched forth in search of aid.
But finding only slack-jawed gawkers,
I gave up and collapsed on the sundial.
Then, with your last
ounce of strength...
you pointed to "W" and "S".
Waylon Smithers!
I'm just relieved that Homer's safe
and that you've recovered...
and we can all get back to normal.
Not exactly.
Smithers, for attempting to kill me...
I'm giving you a five percent pay cut.
Ohh!
But, of course,
for that ending to work...
you would have to ignore
all the Simpson D.N.A. evidence.
And that would be downright nutty.
Yes, the Simpsons
have come a long way...
since an old drunk made humans
out of his rabbit characters...
to pay off his gambling debts.
Who knows what adventures
they'll have between now...
and the time the show
becomes unprofitable?
I'm Troy McClure, and I'll leave you
with what we all came here to see:
hard-core nudity!
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net