The Simpsons
D'oh!
I'd like to thank everybody who contributed
to Krusty's Canned Food Drive.
Your generous donations...
have made this our slipperiest,
slimiest slobstacle course ever!
Our contestants will drop out of my nose
and blurp into a tub of refried beans.
From there, they'll stumble down
a sluice of rich, eggy béarnaise sauce.
- How can we afford it? It's rancid!
- Uhh-
And at the finish line...
a scrumptious parfait of pudding,
pickle brine and detergent...
where a writhing pile of kids
will grope blindly for hot dogs!
Krusty, please! It burns!
Oh, just think, Lise. That's our pickle brine
burning Sideshow Mel.
That Sideshow Mel thinks he's so big.
Whatever happened
to Sideshow Bob?
Don't you remember, Dad?
He framed Krusty,
he tried to kill Aunt Selma...
he rigged an election-
And he tried to murder me.!
Oh, yeah.
But what I'll mainly remember is the laughter.
I wonder what he's doing now.
Ah, Westminster Abbey.
Edward the Confessor himself
could not have done better.
Now to set the clocks
to Greenwich mean time.
My dear abbey!
This is the way we mop the floor,
mop the floor mop the floor
Oh, must you bray night and day
at that infernal television?
- Oh, look who's talking.
- Yeah, Bob. You used to be on this show.
Don't remind me!
My foolish capering destroyed more young
minds than syphilis and pinball combined.
Oh, how I loathe that box...
that omnidirectional
sludge pump droning and burping-
Look here! That's enough now!
I own 60% of that network!
All right, break it up, boys.
It's time for work detail.
I suppose you don't like
tabloid newspapers either.
There. That's the last
condom wrapper.
Oh, I renew my objection
to this pointless endeavor.
Informally now
and by affidavit later, time permitting.
Shut your word-hole!
We gotta get this place clean for the air show.
Air show? Buzz-cut Alabamians spewing
colored smoke from their whizz jets...
to the strains of
"Rock You Like a Hurricane"?
What kind of country-fried rube
is still impressed by that?
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
I want to meet the first female
stealth bomber pilot.
During the Gulf War, she destroyed
70 mosques. And her name is Lisa too.
I want to see some birds get sucked
into the engines, rare ones.
- This year I'm making ear plugs
out of biscuit dough.
They're ready.
So weary.
Grandma, this is my friend, Craig.
Friend? You mean you two
aren't knocking boots?
Ever do the back-seat mambo, Craigie?
I know that voice.
TV's bottomless chum bucket
has claimed Vanessa Redgrave!
Now I'm gonna haul ass to Lollapalooza.
Yee-haw.!
Farewell, dear 'Nessa.
Hey, you.! The state's not paying you
five cents an hour to stand around.
- Now, get busy!
- Oh, I'll get busy.
I'll get very busy, indeed.
You still got it, Bob.
Way to guard
the parking lot, Top Gun!
I have three medals for this.
Hey! Where is Sideshow Bob and that guy who,
uh, eats people and takes their faces?
- I'm right here, Chief.
- Oh. Then where's Sideshow Bob?
- Uh, he ran off.
- Oh, great.
Well, if anyone asks, uh,
I beat him to death, okay?
Right.
At this point in time,
I would like to direct your attention...
to the particular air vehicle next
to which I am currently standing.
The Harrier jet is one of our more
dollar-intensive, ordnance-delivery vectors.
Five tires?
Am I seeing things?
Uh, and although
it looks complicated...
it's so well-designed,
even a child could fly it.
- Can I fly it?
- Of course you cannot.
Free Duff? Viva life!
Mm. Uhh-
Take that, Mom!
Take that, Dad!
Send me to a psychiatrist,
will you?
Take that, Dr. Sally Waxler!
Uh, Colonel, they're expecting you
at the podium in 10 minutes.
I'm, uh-
Hmm.
What in the World
According to Garp?
Those are my dress towels!
Who's in my private washroom?
McGuckett, let me in.
- The door already is closed.
- What?
This is Colonel Leslie "Hap" Hapablap.
If you don't open that door, I'll tear you up
like a Kleenex at a snot party!
You say you're in the military?
Sweet Enola Gay, son!
I'm gonna come in there and corpse you up!
Corpse you up
and mail you to mama!
Well, where'd he go?
Oh, got my knuckles
all lined up for nothing.
Sorry, ladies.
- Look at that hunk of junk.
- Not jun-
You're ignorant!
That's the Wright Brothers' plane.
At Kitty Hawk in 1903...
Charles Lindbergh flew it 15 miles
on a thimbleful of corn oil.
Single-handedly won us
the Civil War, it did.
So, how do you know so much
about American history?
I pieced it together
mostly from sugar packets.
Authorization code?
Code? Son, this is Colonel Hapablap!
That fool McGuckett sprayed runway foam
all over Chuck Yeager's Acura.
Now get down there with
the chamois triple-time!
- But, Colonel, I'm under strict orders to-
- Sweet Enola Gay, son!
Get moving or I'll tear you up
like a Kleenex at a, uh, snot party.
Sir, right away, sir!
They didn't have any aspirin,
so I got you some cigarettes.
Maybe my headache
will go away once the show starts.
Uh, ladies and gentlemen...
what a day for an air show!
Not a cloud in the sky.!
Except perhaps...
a mushroom cloud.
Oh, forget it.
To slip the surly bonds of Earth...
and touch the face of God.
To fly!
The dream of man
and flightless bird alike.
And now, hold on tight...
as we blast through the thrilling highlights
of aviation history!
- Say! Did somebody say box kites?
- No.!
The common box kite was originally
used as a means of drying wet string.
Do they have to play that rock music?
Every note is pounding into my skull.
Anybody out there
feel the need for speed?
- Yay!
- Yay.
Then get ready for the pride
of the United States Air Force!
The British-made HarrierJump jet!
Dad, why aren't you looking?
Why jerk my neck around like a goon...
when Tyranno-Vision decides
what I should look at?
Ooh, look!
It's Maggie!
Uh, Maggie?
Sideshow Bob!
Hello, Springfield.
Sorry to divert your attention
from all the big noises and shiny things.
But something's been troubling
me lately- television!
Wouldn't our lives be so much richer
if television were done away with?
- What?
- Surely he's not talking about VH1?
Why, we could revive the lost
arts of conversation... and scrimshaw.
Thus I submit to you,
we abolish television... permanently!
Go back to Massachusetts, pinko!
Oh, and one more thing.
I've stolen a nuclear weapon.
If you do not rid this city
of television within two hours...
I will detonate it.
Farewell.
By the way, I'm aware of the irony of
appearing on TV in order to decry it.
So don't bother pointing that out.
Kids, everything's gonna be okay!
Don't panic! Just don't panic!
Mom! Mom, you're stepping on my heels
and knocking my shoes off!
We can always get more shoes.
Move, move, move!
Stamp your hand for reentry.
Hey!
Cool! I want to be around
when those guns start going off.
Bart! No!
- Wait! Wait! My children are in there!
- You must be very proud, ma'am.
Our city will not negotiate
with terrorists.
Is there a city nearby that will?
No need, sir. We'll find that head case
faster than Garfield finds lasagna.
Oh. I'm sorry. My- My wife thought
that was gangbusters.
This elevator only goes to the basement.
And someone made
an awful mess down there.
Watch out.!
He's got his probe.!
Bart! Bart! What are you doing?
We've got to get out of here!
Target sighted!
Launching air-to-nerd missile!
Ow! Come on!
Mom and Dad are waiting!
Bob is not here.
We have searched every
square inch of this base...
and all we have found
is porno, porno, porno!
We have only 20 minutes left.
Send in the esteemed
representatives of television.
Hey, hey! Now, this is
my kind of meeting!
Gentlemen, it's time we face up
to the un-face-up-to-able.
We must sacrifice television in order
to save the lives of our townspeople.
Whoa! Whoa-ho-ho!
Let's not go nuts!
Would it really be worth living
in a world without television?
I think the survivors
would envy the dead.
- I appreciate your passion
on behalf of your medium.
But I'm afraid we're out of options.
Television must go.
May God have mercy on our souls.
And as my final newscast
draws to a close...
I'm reminded of a few of the events
that brought me closer to you.
The collapse of the Soviet Union,
premium ice cream price wars...
dogs that were mistakenly issued major
credit cards and others who weren't so lucky.
And so, farewell.
Uh, and, uh, don't forget to look for
my new column in PC World magazine.
Success!
They're giving in!
Blast! I should have
made more demands!
Some decent local marmalade,
for one. Oh, well, next time.
Not my extendo-glove!
Oh, they haven't made those
since the war.
Not- Oh, not
my Paris backdrop!
How am I gonna make fun of the Frogs?
Wait.
If I could only stay on the air...
I'd have 100% of the audience.
Think of the ratings.
Okay, so we can't go over the fence.
I feel so helpless.
What if something happens to them?
I'm sure they're fine, honey.
Hmm. Well, at least they're
wearing clean underwear.
Free and easy, Lise.
There's nothing like an unfurnished
basement for pure comfort.
Huh? Hurry up.
Mom and Dad are probably worried sick.
Do you know what really frosts my Kelvinator?
That fruitcup's probably still laughing at us
from his damn hidey-hole.
I'd rather take an order
from Bill Clinton...
than hear that guy's snooty,
high-toned voice again, sir.
"High-toned voice. "
Bart, that's it.
I know where
Sideshow Bob is hiding.
When Bob broadcast that message,
his voice was higher than normal.
And what makes your voice high?
- Tight, binding underwear?
- Helium!
Sideshow Bob
is in the Duff blimp!
All Springfield trembles
before the might of Sideshow Bob.
Blasted helium!
Shoo! Shoo!
Shoo! Shoo! That's better.
Gone. Gone too.
Fabulous. Marvelous.
This is the emergency broadcast system.
Stand by for an urgent bulletin.
Hey, hey!
Krusty the Clown
is back on the air!
Eight- No, no!
Twelve hours a day!
The only game in town!
Krusty! But how?
Coming at you live
from the civil defense shack...
in the remote Alkali Flats
of the Springfield badlands.
I'll be beaming out
11 watts of wackiness!
Hour after hour of unscripted,
unrehearsed comedy...
featuring, uh, you know, uh,
Professor Gas Can!
Uh, and, uh, former president,
Ike Eisenhower!
Let's get busy!
Oh! My utopia lies in ruins.
How naive of me to think a mere atom bomb
could fell the chattering Cyclops!
Well, at least I'll have my revenge!
Bob, no!
Don't you see? That would
be taking the easy way out.
I agree.
"Best before November 1959."
Damn it, Bob!
There were plenty
of brand-new bombs.
But you had to go
for that retro '50s charm.
Well, if it isn't
my arch nemesis, Bart Simpson...
and his sister, Lisa,
to whom I'm fairly indifferent.
So Krusty double-crossed you.
But your basic plan
was pure genius.
Where do you get your ideas?
Oh, please!
Let's not embarrass us both...
with that hoary old
stall-the-villain-with-flattery scheme.
I- I should've known you were
too smart to fall for that.
Really? What type of smart?
Book smart?
Because there are a lot of
people who are book smart.
But it takes a very special
type of genius to-
All right, Bob. It's over.!
Come out with your hands up.!
No! How did they find me?
He's getting away!
- Oh, not the Harrier!
We've got a war tomorrow.
God bless the idiot-proof Air Force.
They're gone!
Hell! Not the Wright Brothers' plane.
The Smithsonian's gonna
have my ass on a platter.
Dad! Help!
Hang on, boy! Daddy's coming to save you!
D'oh!
Mom! I found Sideshow Bob's hideout!
And I got a secret message to the police!
And I had a blimp fall on me!
And I was in an atomic blast! But I'm okay now!
Well, I wrecked the gate. But you don't
hear me bragging. Now let's roll!
Ah, for the days when aviation
was a gentleman's pursuit.
Back before everyJoe Sweat Sock could
wedge himself behind a lunch tray...
and jet off to Raleigh-Durham.
Are you getting
lots of bugs in your mouth too?
Yes.
Prepare to engage enemy.
Bogie's air speed not sufficient for
intercept. Suggest we get out and walk.
Jump, boy!
I got you!
I'm coming!
Now you, boy.
You can't escape, Bob. If the tennis rackets
don't get you, the pool skimmers will.
Oh, I- I never planned to escape.
You see, this is a kamikaze mission.
You and I are going to
kill Krusty the Clown!
Kids, Itchy and Scratchy
can't be here today.
But instead,
we've got the next best thing.
It's The Stingy
and Battery Show.!
They bite and light
and bite and light and bite
You know what I'm talking about.
Uh-oh.
You can't kill Krusty.
He made you what you are.
- Without him, you wouldn't
even be called "Sideshow. "
What the hell is that?
A lawn mower?
Get out of the way, Krusty!
What is the freakin' holdup?
Die, Krusty!
Die- Oh.
Ooh, sorry. Uh, we don't normally drive
these in the Air Force.
Gotcha!
Ya TV-hatin' mutant.
What is your major malfunction,
Sideshow Bob?
Oh, my little sugar bun.
I'm so glad you're safe.
But- But- But- But, M-M-Mom!
You're embarrassing me
in front of the army guys.
How ironic. My crusade against television
has come to an end so formulaic...
it could have spewed from the PowerBook
of the laziest Hollywood hack.
Hey, everybody!
I'm gonna haul ass to Lollapalooza!
- Here we go again.
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net