The Simpsons
D'oh!
Testing. Testing for Mr. Burns.
Here you go, sir. I've warmed up
the crowd for you.
"Welcome, employees. "
"Come in. "
"The whole night's
entertainment is on me. "
"Monty Burns. "
Welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
To an evening of exciting quarter-mile action.!
Action.! Action.!
Our first race is a benefit for daredevil
Lance Murdock.! Murdock.! Murdock.!
Who's hospitalized with cirrhosis of the liver!
Liver! Liver!
All right! Liver!
- It sure would be fun to carpool
in one of those, huh, kids?
I'd be a real hotrod mama, wouldn't I?
- Huh? Huh?
- You missed the race, Mama.
Hmm. I wish I'd pay more attention.
Smithers, this beer isn't working.
I don't feel any younger or funkier.
- I'll switch to the tablespoon, sir.
- Coming up next.!
Our feature race- the Nuclear Power Plant
Championship! Plant! Plant!
Ah! At last.
Smithers, fetch the bi-oculars.
- Damnation! Tell them to go slower.
- Yes, sir.
Hi, guys.
Could we keep it in first gear
for a couple laps?
Go.! Go.!
Slow down.
Excellent.
This novelty foam hand
is ludicrously oversized.
Go swap it for a smaller one.
It is a bit ostentatious, sir.
I'll be right back.
Hey, Burnsie!
This was some swell shindig.
- Thank you very much.
- Smithers! What's happening?
I had a great time.
I just wanna shake your hand.
You're the greatest.
Smithers! Help!
Doesn't seem as funny to me.
But what do I know?
Smithers.!
Oh, my God!
Hey-hey!
You should've seen the murderous glint
in his eyes, Smithers.
And his breath reeked of beer
and pretzled bread.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Burns.
This was all my fault.
No. Don't concern yourself.
If things had turned ugly,
I always had my mace.
Don't let me off the hook
that easily, sir.
I failed you,
and I'll never forgive myself.
Never! Never! Never!
Good morning, sir. To make up
for my failure last night...
I've alphabetized your breakfast.
You can start with the waffles
and work your way up to the zwieback.
And to prevent newsprint
from rubbing off on your hands...
I've laminated today's newspaper.
I appreciate the thought,
but my pen won't write on this.
How am I supposed to do
the "JuniorJumble"?
Oh! I can't even grovel properly.
I'm a buffoon.
I don't deserve to live
on your planet anymore!
Agh!
Pull yourself together, man.
I daresay you're in need
of a long vacation.
No! Don't make me take a vacation.
Without you, I'll wither and die!
- That's a risk I'm willing to take.
- What would you do without me?
I'm not a baby
who needs a nursemaid to burp me.
You see?
Now, I insist you take a vacation...
just as soon as a temporary substitute
can be found.
Sheesh.!
I've got to find a replacement
who won't outshine me.
Perhaps if I search the employee evaluations
for the word "incompetent. "
714 names?
Better be more specific.
Lazy. Clumsy.
Dimwitted.
Monstrously ugly.
Nuts to this.
I'll just go get Homer Simpson.
I think Smithers picked me
because of my motivational skills.
Everyone always says they have to work
a lot harder when I'm around.
You know, Dad, assisting Mr. Burns could
give your career a real shot in the arm.
You know, Homer, assisting Mr. Burns could
- Mom, I just said that.
- Sor-ry.
Next time,
get your own darn corn.
Um, is this the chair
I'll be sitting on?
Yeah. Now, I realize caring for Mr. Burns
seems like a big job...
but actually it's just 2,800 small jobs.
Uh-huh.
But this is the chair, right?
Your new duties will include
answering Mr. Burns's phone...
preparing his tax return,
moistening his eyeballs...
assisting with his chewing
and swallowing...
lying to Congress
and some light typing.
Montgomery Burns's office.
Oh, hello, Mrs. Burns.
I'll see if your son is available.
Mr. Burns has a mother?
She must be a hundred million years old.
She has limited capacities.
All she can do is dial and yell.
I'm sorry. Monty can't come
to the phone right now.
He's in a very important meeting
and can't be disturbed.
Uh-huh. Okay,
I'll give him the message.
Mr. Burns can't stand
talking to his mother.
He never forgave her
for having that affair with President Taft.
Taft, you old dog.
Really, Smithers, I'll be fine.
I'm sure your replacement
will be able to handle everything.
- Who is he anyway?
- Uh, Homer Simpson, sir.
One of your organ banks
from Sector 7G.
All the recent events
of your life...
have revolved around him
in some way.
Simpson, eh?
Uh, Mr. Smithers.!
I don't understand
2,700 of my new duties.
Well, the van's leaving. Which one duty
is giving you the most trouble?
Um, what do I do in case of fire?
Sorry. Can't hear you. Bye.
Aw! Just my luck.
Good Lord, Smithers!
You look atrocious.
I thought I told you to take a vacation.
Smithers already left, sir.
I'm his replacement- Homer Simpson.
Ah, yes. Simpson.
I'll have my lunch now.
A single pillow of shredded wheat...
some steamed toast
and a dodo egg.
- But I think the dodo went extinct-
- Get going!
And answer those phones,
install the computer system...
and rotate my office
so the window faces the hills.
Uh-huh, uh-huh. Okay.
Um, can you repeat
the part of the stuff...
where you said all about
the... things?
Uh, the things?
Lousy two-legged pants.
Homie, it's 4:30 in the morning.
Little Rascals isn't on till 6:00.
I'm taping it. I wanna get to Mr. Burns's house
bright and early to make his breakfast.
Oh, poor Homie.
Poor, poor-
Hmm. One of these
must be a breakfast maker.
Well, it's my job
to cook him breakfast...
and I'm gonna cook
the best damn breakfast he ever ate.
Hmm.
Doughnuts? I told you
I don't like ethnic food.
Here. Tell me how my stocks
did yesterday.
Uh, they all won.
- Hmm? What about my options?
- Well, you can either get up or go back to sleep.
I believe I'll get up.
Scrub harder.
Got to get that layer of dead skin off.
I think... the fangs today.
Simpson?
Simpson.
- Did you get that report on the accounting department?
- Yes, sir, I did.
"The accounting department
is located on the third floor.
Its hours are 9:00 a. m.
to 5:00 p. m."
The head of this department
is a Mr. Johnson orJohnstone.
Here are your messages.
"You have 30 minutes to move your car. "
"You have 10 minutes. "
"Your car has been impounded. "
"Your car has been
crushed into a cube. "
"You have 30 minutes to move your cube. "
- Y'ello. Mr. Burns's office.
- Is it about my cube?
It's Mr. Smithers.
He's calling for you.
How's everything
going there, sir? Heh.
I have a lot of free time
on my hands.
If you FedEx me your mail, I'd be happy
to open it and return it to you.
Everything's fine, Smithers.
This Simpson fellow seems
to be getting dumber by the minute.
I've never seen anything quite like it.
Anyhoo, you just enjoy your vacation.
Look alive, Simpson!
I'm not paying you to goldbrick.
Yes! Yes, sir!
Get cracking on my long division,
and don't forget to show your work, Simpson.
I'll have it on your desk
in the morning, sir.
Bart! Leave Simpson alone.
- Simpson, I need a ride to the library.
- Yes, sir.
Kids! Stop exploiting your father.
Homie, why don't you
lie down and relax?
No time, Marge. I think Mr. Burns
wants me to do some long division.
Simpson! Lie down!
Sorry, but you need
a good night's rest.
Simpson.!
The telephone has been ringing for some time.
Answer it.
Y'ello. It's for you.
"Relax"]
- Mr. Burns- 48 rings. Are you all right?
What did Simpson do to you?
Do? Nothing other than drive me
to distraction with his incompetent boobery.
Terrible at everything.
A complete moron.
But I'm not really free to talk right now.
Look. Stop calling me
and start enjoying your vacation.
Remember, I want to see
lots of pictures when you get back.
Uh, actually, sir, picture taking
is not allowed at this particular resort.
Oop. I gotta go now.
There's a line forming behind me.
Sixty watts?
What do you think this is,
a tanning salon?
I asked for light starch
on my nightcap!
You call this Postum?
You call this a tax return?
You call this a supercomputer?
D'egh! G'yah! D'oh!
You're a travesty of a f-
joke of an assistant!
Is there something wrong, Homie?
- No.
- Except-
Except... I killed Mr. Burns!
- What happened, Dad?
- I punched Burns right in his 104-year-old face.
Are you sure he's dead?
Maybe you just really, really hurt him.
Okay. Maybe everything's all right.
Maybe, if you go apologize,
he won't even fire you... if he's alive.
Mr. Burns?
I'm really sorry I hit you, Mr. Burns.
Here. Let me put some salt
on that eye.
No! Please! I can't bear
another thrashing.
- Just leave me be.
- Yes, sir.
Must... call... Smithers.
He'll protect me from this beast.
I've seen people activate
this machine a thousand times.
Doesn't seem to be any trick to it.
Let's see. Smithers.
S-M-I-T-H-E-R-S.
Success! It's ringing.
Moe's Tavern.
I'm looking for a Mr. Smithers,
first name Waylon.
Oh. So you're lookin'
for a Mr. Smithers, eh?
First name Waylon, is it?
Listen to me, you!
When I catch you, I'm gonna pull out your eyes
and shove 'em down your pants...
so you can watch me
kick the crap outta you!
Okay? Then I'm gonna
use your tongue to paint my boat.
Ooh.
Oh, Smithers,
if only you could hear me.
Something tells me
Mr. Burns needs me.
Praise God. That thug has finally
gone home for the day.
Now I can make my escape.
Hi, Mr. Burns. You want your coffee now?
No. I'm, uh, making it myself.
Hear that?
The percolations are imminent.
No need to come in.
Cease your ingress.
Stay back, Homer.
Approach no further.
Coffee's already made.
I stomped the beans myself.
Well, can I at least drive you home,
Mr. Burns? It's 5:00.
No! I thought- I thought
I'd chauffeur myself this evening.
Yes. That's what I thought.
How difficult can it be?
I'm sure the manual will indicate
which lever is the velocitator...
and which the deceleratrix, hmm?
I can't believe it.
All my life, I've avoided
doing things for myself.
But I'm actually enjoying this.
Plus I'm making incredible time.
Beep-beep! Out of my way!
I'm a motorist.
Uh, that's some nice
reckless drivin', Mr. B.
Would you like me to shred
those environmental reports for you, sir?
Already taken care of.
Cappuccino, Simpson?
Ahoy! Ahoy!
No, you have the wrong number.
This is 5246.
I suspect you need more practice
working your telephone machine.
Not at all. Ahoy.
Mr. Burns, is there anything
at all I can do for you?
No, Homer. You've already
done more for me than any man.
Your brutal attack forced me
to fend for myself.
I realize now that being waited on hand and foot
is okay for your average joe.
But it's not for me.
I want to thank you.
Thank you.
Oh, my God! I knew
I shouldn't have left.
Ah! Welcome back, Smithers.
Say, do you know Homer Simpson? He pitched in
around the office while you were away.
Bang-up job, Simpson, but I guess
it's back to your trusty post in Sector 7G.
You heard the man, Simpson.
Ah, and my dear, dear Smithers.
You're no longer needed at all.
You're fired. Ta.
You shouldn't have
gone away on vacation.
- Cheer up, Homie.
- I feel terrible about getting Mr. Smithers fired.
That job was all he had.
Imagine how you'd feel, Marge...
if you got fired from the-
those things that... you do.
Quick, Mom. Whip up a cake
before Dad fires ya.
Don't worry, Dad.
Mr. Smithers is a resilient man.
I'm sure he can get a great job
at any corporation he wants.
Meet your new piano mover.
We're gonna have to put a steel rod
where your spine was.
Will I ever move a piano again?
Oh, my goodness gracious! No.
Get ready for exciting quarter-mile action...
at the Springfield Drag Strip!
It'll be motorized mayhem!
Mayhem! Mayhem!
Do we need
all those "mayhems"? We do.
All right. Fair enough.
I suppose you know your business.
Get ready for fun! Fun! Fun!
Uh, people are already here.
We don't need to keep hustling them
like this, do we?
- Will you let go of me?
Where are you throwing me?
Uh, hello. Is that a "Help Wanted" sign
in the window?
Uh, yeah. I need someone to help me
with the midnight beer delivery.
Your job is to distract Barney
until it's safely off the truck.
I'll just wait out back until then.
- I look forward to workin' with ya.
- Mr. Smithers! Wait!
You can't let yourself end up in a place
like this. You've got two choices.
You can give up on yourself
and take the Barney-guarding job-
like so many of us have contemplated
in our darkest moments-
or you can admit to yourself there's only
one person that can make you happy...
and do whatever it takes
to get them back!
You're right!
But I'm gonna need your help.
Oh, my God!
Beer delivery. Sign here.
No.! It's you.!
Oh, boy.!
Gimme that.!
Okay. I gotcha covered.
Mr. Burns may have mastered
2,799 of my 2,800 duties...
but I'll wager dollars to doughnuts...
he still can't handle
a call from his mother.
You're on!
What?
Hello. Mrs. Burns.
This is Waylon Smithers.
I have your son,
Montgomery, on the line.
That improvident lackwit!
Always too busy stridin' about his atom mill
to call his own mother.
I'll give him what for
till he cries brassafrax!
Perfect.
When I give the signal,
you transfer the call to Mr. Burns.
- After she tears into him, I'll rush in and save the day.
- Got it.
- I'm transferring a call in to you, Mr. Burns.
- No problemo.
Uh, ooh. Um.
Uh-oh.
Ahoy, ahoy. Ahoy.
Hello. Mr. Burns? This is your mother.
No!
Oh, hello, Mater.
Um, sorry about pulling the plug
on you and all.
Who could have known
you'd pull through and...
live for another five decades.
Ooh! Is my face red.
Mrs. Burns is 122 years old,
so try to sound more desiccated.
And she doesn't
call her son "Mr. Burns. "
Son, this is Mrs. Burns.
I just called to say
I don't love you.
You are a bad son, Montel-
So.
Impersonate my mother, will you?
And you, Smithers,
you must have put him up to it.
I'm glad I fired you.
You really blew it this time,
Smithers.
Stop that! Stop that at once!
You're fighting!
- Stop fighting like a girl, Simpson!
- Okay.
Stop it.!
Stop it, I say.!
I'll teach you how
to use a phone, you boob!
- Ring! Ring! Ring!
- D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
- It's for you.
- D'oh!
I'll show you!
Oh, my.
Here comes the endangered condor
into the power lines.
- Mm. Mm. Mm.
- I've got Bobo, hot from the dryer.
Careful not to burn yourself
on his eye.
I don't need you to do any of this.
I'm totally self-reliant now.
What I would like, though,
is a spanish peanut.
Skin.
Mm-mmm-mmm!
It's a remarkable thing.
In the short time you were gone...
I learned to be completely
self-reli- ant.
Oh, and as for that brutish fellow
who knocked me out the window...
see that he gets
what's coming to him.
I already have, sir.
What'd you get that for?
For knocking Mr. Burns
out of a third-story window.
- Makes sense to me.
- Did he die?
What am I, a doctor?
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net