The Simpsons
D'oh!
Grampa! I don't mind when you spit at home.
But I have to work with these people.
Oh, jabber jacks! Schoolhouse don't
put out spittoons, I ain't responsible.
All right, seniors...
we'd all love to share in your wisdom,
experience, yadda, yadda, yadda.
Let's start with
Milhouse's grandfather.
Uh, how many of you have a house?
All right. Now how many of you
drove your house to school today?
- Huh?
- What?
Well, I did.
No, I'm not Superman.
I just own an R.V.
Me and the new wife travel
the country searching for adventure.
- Last fall, we won a chili
cook-off in Beaumont, Texas. - Wow!
You're livin'in a fool's
paradise, Van Houten.
If you fell down in the shower,
that thing'd be your tomb.
Grampa, hush! Here.
Why don't you spit some more?
No, I'm not Superman.
I'm a judge.
Why, just this morning
I sentenced my 46th man to death.
No, 47 th.
Wow, 47!
I love you, Grandpa.
Yeah, well, I may not have
a fancy black bathrobe...
and a hammer like Snooty...
but I do have slippers
and an oatmeal spoon.
- Look!
- Bart, perhaps your grandfather...
would like to come up front now and
give someone else a chance to interrupt.
Oh, please, no.
About time, knothead.
Now- Hey, listen!
Now, my story begins
in nineteen dickety-two.
We had to say "dickety," 'cause
the kaiser had stolen our word "twenty. "
I chased that rascal to get it back...
but gave up after dickety-six miles.
Dickety? Highly dubious.
What are you cackling at,
fatty? Too much pie.
That's your problem.
Now, I'd like to digress
from my prepared remarks...
to discuss how I invented
the "terlet. "
Terlet. Ha!
Stop your snickering!
I spent three years on that terlet!
And then he claimed he was the one who
turned cats and dogs against each other.
Why is he always making up
those crazy stories?
- Maybe it's time we put Grampa in a home.
- You already put him in a home.
Maybe it's time we put him
in one where he can't get out.
No! Old people
deserve our respect.
Look atJacques Cousteau
and Goldie Hawn.
You wouldn't shut them away
like second-class citizens.
Second-class!
What about Social Security,
bus discounts...
medic alert jewelry,
Gold Bond powder...
pants all the way
up to your armpits...
and all those other senior perks.
Oh, if you ask me,
old folks have it pretty sweet.
Mm, let's see.
Yeah, yeah.
Eh, this junk was hardly
worth gettin' up for.
Maybe if I go back to sleep for a few days,
some good mail will build up.
Hey, what's this?
"Asa Phelps has"-
The seventh Hellfish is dead!
That means the fortune's almost mine.
Asa Phelps spent
his entire life in Springfield...
except for a four-year service in World War II
and one high school day trip.
He worked at the United Strut
and Bracing Works as a molders boy...
until he was replaced
by a Moldermatic and died.
Would you do the honors?
Well, Simpson, seven gone.
As soon as you're
in your pressboard coffin...
I'll be the sole survivor,
and the treasure will be mine.
Over my dead body it will!
That's exactly the point!
Oh, Simpson, can't you go five seconds
without humiliating yourself?
How long was that?
Your clownish behavior
notwithstanding...
we have made
a gentleman's agreement...
and sworn on our lives to honor it.
Smithers, I want that man killed.
Well, let's see.
Mesmerists, dowsers, Luddites, alienists...
Zoroastrians, alphabetizers-
Aha! Assassins!
I was wondering, sir.
Do we really need to, uh...
settle Abe Simpson?
I mean, I'm familiar
with his physical state...
and perhaps if we wait,
nature will assassinate him for us.
Well, I can't risk it. I won't allow that
Simpson boy to take the Hellfish bonanza.
And I can't get it without his key.
Ah, just the man I need.
Fernando Vidal, the world's
most devious assassin.
- Hola.
- Fernando, it's M.B.
Ah, Marion Barry. Is it time
for another shipment already?
- Oi! This is Montgomery Burns!
- Oh, caramba.
I'm sending you a photo
over the Faxtrola.
I need you to fly to Springfield
and assassinate this man posthaste.
Ah, Del Monte.
Enjoy them, old man.
They will be your last.
Hey, what the- I'm up! I'm up!
Ah, he's more clever
than he looks.
Abraham Simpson,
your family is here to visit you.
Hot diggety!
My family's come to visit me!
It-Wait a minute!
My family never comes to vi-
D'oh! Not again!
I can't take much more of your
blundering numskullery.
I'll be in the car, dudes.
There is one more way
to kill a man...
but it is as intricate
and precise...
as a well-played game of chess.
Was that me,
or was that you?
Help! Nurse! Someone's
trying to kill me!
Okay, we'll do something
about that right away.
Let's start by doubling
your medication.
Our residents...
are trying... to nap!
Ah.! Let me in.!
Someone's trying to kill me.!
Sweet merciful McGillicutty.!
You gotta open the door.!
- Who is it?
- It's Grampa.
And it sounds like he's gotten
into the horseradish again.
And then a knife
flew at my head!
And you were there...
and you were there.
Uh, Grampa, maybe I should
moisten your washcloth.
It's plenty moist! Listen!
Monty Burns is trying to
kill me, and it's all because-
Uh, um,
I can't tell you why.
Well, I'm sure
you'll make up something.
Maybe you just need
more of my classmates around.
I gotta hole up here for a while.
They might still be after me!
Wow! He's even more
agitated than usual.
- Maybe we should let him stay.
- Where are we going to put him?
- Bart's room.
- Dumpster.
Sorry to crowd you, boy,
but I'll let you in on a secret.
Burns is after me 'cause
he wants the Hellfish bonanza.
Look, if you're
gonna stay in my room...
could you at least stop
making up gibberish?
Gibberish, eh?
Then what's this?
Wrinkly gibberish?
I got this
in the Second World War II.
Back then I was known
as Sergeant Simpson...
and I commanded
the Flying Hellfish...
the fightingest squad
in the fightingest company...
in the third-fightingest
battalion in the army.
We were all from Springfield.
There was Police Chief
Wiggum's father, Iggy Wiggum.
Um, if anybody finds a grenade
without a pin, that's mine.
Our radioman, Sheldon Skinner.
All right, very funny.
Well, I didn't join
the service to make friends.
And watching our backs
was Private Fifth Class Arnie Gumble.
Then there was also
Griff, Asa, Ox and Etch.
But every unit
has a troublemaker.
Ours was a cocky little private
named Montgomery Burns.
Haven't you won the war yet?
Duh, hey!
You said you was dead.
Yes. Dead tired. But I'm quite
refreshed now. Thank you.
Mm-hmm. You bossed around
the richest, most powerful guy in town?
How come you were a sergeant
and he was only a private?
Well, he got busted down for obstructing
a probe from J. Edgar Hoover.
We got stuck with him.
Now they'll never
save your brain, Hitler.
Little help?
Boom! Boom it went!
Boom! Just like that!
They took a photo of my keister
for Stars and Stripes.!
At least they told me
it was for Stars and Stripes.
Well, if you saved Burns's life,
why does he want to kill you?
It was the closing days
of the war.
We had just flushed some Germans
out of an abandoned castle.
Hey! Burnsie
found some pictures.
Wait a minute. We ain't-a supposed
to steal from civilians.
You want me to report you to Commander
Flanders? Just leave them, Burnsie.
Leave them for whom?
The Germans?
The folks who shoot at us all day?
Let's just take them.
We'll all be rich- rich as Nazis.
Wow! I'd like to be as rich as the Nazis!
Think of what a guy could get himself
with that kind of scratch.
Yeah. I could buy chicken
dinners three times a day.
I could buy a brand-new Studebaker
with a fan on the dashboard.
I could buy my way into high-
society.
Well, I don't feel
right about it...
but I could use a nest egg
for retirement.
I'd hate to wind up
in one of them old folks' homes.
Then it's agreed.
Of course, we can't sell
the paintings now. We'd be caught.
How many of you are familiar
with the concept of a tontine?
All right, Ox. Why don't you
take us through it.
Uhh, essentially, we all
enter into a contract...
whereby the last
surviving participant...
becomes the sole possessor
of all them "perty" pictures.
Well put, Oxford. Now remember,
you can't all sign with an "X."
So we sealed up the paintings...
knowing only one of us
would ever look upon them again.
Ox was the first to go.
He got a hernia carrying
the crate out of the castle.
Five more men died in the Veterans Day
float disaster of'79.
Now, with Asa gone,
it's down to me and Burns.
Great story, Grampa.
Could've used a vampire though. Night.
My own grandson thinks I'm a liar.
Don't kill me!
I've tried to meet you
halfway on this, Simpson...
but you had to be
littleJohnny Live-A-Lot.
Now give me your key
to the Hellfish bonanza.
Oh, wow!
There really is a treasure!
- Whatever you do, don't give him the key, Grampa.
- Here's the key.
Aw, figures.
Hey, Mr. Burns!
Can I go with you
to get the treasure?
I won't eat much, and I don't know
the difference between right and wrong.
Oh, you're a good boy...
but the child labor people have
been watching me like a hawk.
Well, I'm off to get the paintings.
As they say, "time is Monets. "
As you were, Sergeant.
Oh, terribly sorry.
Back to sleep, little girl.
Santa?
I guess Burns
is finally gonna be rich.
Not without the keys he isn't.
Hey, you got the keys!
- Now we can get the treasure!
- Oh, what's the use?
Burns would still find
some way to take it from me.
I can't believe you, Grampa.
The sergeant in that story you told would
never be scared of a dork like Burns.
You gotta get that treasure. You gotta do it
for Ox and Asa and Griff and Burnsie!
Well, not so much Burnsie.
You really think I can do it?
Uh, yes. But we gotta act fast.
Where are you two going
at this hour?
- On a treasure hunt.
- Oh, can I come?
Only if you're ready
to stare danger in the face...
put your manhood
to the ultimate test and take-
Pass.
Hey, Grampa, do you think your dead buddies
get up and walk around at night?
If they're anything like me,
they have to get up twice.
Okay, hold up here.
Fellas, it's me, Sarge.
At ease. I know I'm bending
the rules tonight...
but I also know none of you wants
that skunk Burns to take our treasure.
And I want you to know
that when I die...
you're all welcome to visit me
in Rich Man's Heaven.
Now it's gonna show us
exactly where to dig.
D'oh.!
Boy, you borrow us some diving
equipment while I borrow this boat.
Well, howdy-doodilly, stranger. Couldn't
help but notice you stealing my boat.
- I'll bring it back.
- You ever operated a power boat?
- No.
- Know anything about water safety?
- What do you need it for?
- It's a secret.
- Ooh, sounds spine-tingly-dingling.
Just promise
you'll have a good time.
Maude! Boys! Come on up! We're gonna
have a little campout in the dinghy.
Yea.!
Now remember the plan, boy.
If you run out of air,
tug on the rope-
Sixty-four times.
No more, no less. Got it.
No, no! Sixty-three times
if you're out of air!
Sixty-four is if you've
found the treasure.
Gotcha. Hey, Grampa, do you think
I could've been a Flying Hellfish?
You're a gutsy daredevil with a give-'em-hell
attitude and a fourth-grade education.
You could've made sergeant.
Wow!
Sixty-one, 62, 63-
Oh, no! Sixty-three!
He's out of air!
I've sent my only grandson
to a watery grave!
Sixty-four!
He found the treasure! I'm rich!
You're one heck
of a grandson, boy.
Now let's break her open
and have a look-see.
Oh! Hey- Huh?
Huh. The light
must've burned out.
I'll thank you to stop pinching my Botticelli.
Looks like I didn't need
the keys after all.
I'll take the masterpieces.
Thank you.
Consarn it!
You coward! You're an embarrassment
to the name Hellfish!
Oh, am I?
No! Look! Take the art if you want.
Just don't hurt the boy.
Hmm. I'd rather do both.
So long, Sarge. See you
at the reunion in November.
Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
I'm sorry I cost you
your fortune, Grampa.
Ah, the fortune doesn't matter, boy.
The important thing is you're safe.
Now let's get that fortune!
They're gaining on us, sir.
We'll have to jettison something.
It's been an honor to serve you, sir.
Consarn it!
He's getting away!
In a pig's eye he is!
Act your age, Simpson!
You look foolish!
- Don't kill me.
- I ain't gonna kill ya.
That'd be cowardly.
Monty Burns cowardly.
I just wanna watch you squirm.
Yes, sir.
Is this to your liking?
Now, Burnsie, there's one thing
we don't stand for in the Hellfish...
and that's trying to kill
your commanding officer.
So consider this
your dishonorable discharge.
You're out of my unit.
You're out of the tontine.
And that means
the paintings are mine!
Private, you are dismissed!
You're rich, Grampa!
You did it!
And Burns can never
take that away from you.
Freeze! U.S. State Department.
We'll take those.
We've been helping the German government
search for this stolen art for 50 years.
To avoid an international incident,
we'll be returning it...
to the descendant
of its rightful owner.
Baron Von Bertzenberger, on behalf
of the American people, I apologize for-
Ja, ja, ja. Mach schnell
mit the art things, huh?
I must get back to Dance Central
in Stuttgart in time to see Kraftwerk.
Hey, und, dummkopf! Watch out
for the CD changer in my trunk, huh?
Idiot.
I guess he deserves it
more than I do.
Well, at least I got to show you
I wasn't always a pathetic old kook.
You never were, Grampa.
Oh, I'd hug ya, but I know
you'd just get embarrassed.
I won't get embarrassed.
I don't care who knows I love my grampa.
Hey, fun boys! Get a room!
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net