The Simpsons
D'oh!
Come on, Simpson. Open up.
We know you're in there.
Mmm. That one.
Someone's in here.
No.!
No! No! Oh!
- Oh, for the love of-
- Boy.
I've never seen a man so desperate
to get out of five minutes of calisthenics.
One, two, three, four.
Up, down, three, four.
This new exercise program is great.
Yeah. Every muscle in my body's
gettin' a workout.
Especially my big fat mouth.
Yeah, especially your big fat-
Oh, wait.
Raise your right hock. Aerate.
Raise your left hock.
Aerate.
I want to see more Teddy Roosevelts
and less Franklin Roosevelts.
Two!
Uh, actually, Homer,
that's just one.
See, each pushup includes both
an up part and a down part.
D'oh!
Hey, where's Charlie?
How'd he get outta this?
Aw, he's at home on disability.
He got injured on the job,
and they sent him home with pay.
It's like a lottery
that rewards stupidity.
Stupidity, eh?
Must hurt self.
D'oh!
Hmm. Probably better
that didn't hit me.
- Yes?
- Hello.
May I help you?
Uh...
could you give me a little push
in the opposite direction?
Okay.
Thank you.
Carpal tunnel syndrome? No.
Lumber lung? No.
Juggler's despair? No.
Achy-breaky pelvis? No.
Oh! I'm never gonna be disabled.
I'm sick of being so healthy.
Hey, wait.
"Hyperobesity.
"If you weigh more
than 300 pounds...
you qualify as disabled. "
- You can do it, old boy.
- Yes, I can!
Yes, yes. That's the spirit.
If you gain 61 pounds,
they'll let you work at home?
Yuh-huh. That's the deal.
No more exercise program. No more traffic.
No more blood drives
or charity walks.
Dad, I know we don't
do a lot together...
but helping you gain 61 pounds
is something I want to be a part of.
Dad!
I must protest.
You're abusing a program...
intended to help the unfortunate.
I'm not saying
it isn't sleazy, honey.
But try to see it my way.
All my life, I've been an obese man
trapped inside a fat man's body.
- Have you told Mom about this?
- No. It would only worry her.
If you want to add
to her worries, go ahead.
I guess I'm just a little more grateful
for all she's done for us.
- Dad!
- Yes, sweetheart?
Obesity is really unhealthy.
Any doctor will tell you that.
Oh, yeah? Well, we'll just see about that,
little Miss Smart Guy.
My God! That's monstrous.
I've never heard of anything
so negligen-
I'll have no part of it.
- Can you recommend a doctor who will?
- Yes.
Hi, everybody!
Hi, Dr. Nick!
Now, there are many
options available...
for dangerously underweight
individuals like yourself.
I recommend a slow,
steady gorging process...
combined with assal horizontology.
Of course.
You'll want to focus
on the neglected food groups...
such as the whipped group,
the congealed group...
and the chocotastic.
What can I do to speed
the whole thing up, Doctor?
Ah, be creative. Instead of making
sandwiches with bread, use Pop-Tarts.
Instead of chewing gum, chew bacon.
You could brush your teeth
with milk shakes.
Hey, did you go to Hollywood Upstairs
Medical College too?
And remember, if you're
not sure about something...
rub it against a piece of paper.
If the paper turns clear,
it's your window to weight gain.
Bye-bye, everybody!
Oh, it's a dream come true, boy.
I can- Nay, I must eat everything
I've always wanted.
Now, come on.
Every second I'm out of bed...
I'm burning precious calories.
Now get grabbin'.
Eat around the banana, Dad.
It's just empty vitamins.
Lucky for you,
this stuff doesn't work.
I don't know.
Fish sandwich.
Are you sure?
Oh! 225?
That means I lost weight!
Homer. You're, uh, on the towel rack.
Whoo-hoo! Four more pounds,
and my dream comes true.
Working at home.
Here's your lemonade,
and here's your beer.
Oh! You're such a vigorous
young go-getter.
When's your next coffee break?
Anytime I want.
- Oh.
- Hey, Flanders.
- Bad day at the rat races?
- Yeah.
A crazy guy shot a bunch of people,
and a subway ran over my hat.
Hey, Lise.
Come look at this.
Neat.
Homer! Whoa!
- Hello, honey.
- Hi.
Um, there's something
I've been meaning to ask you.
Did you put on
a little weight this week?
I was going to surprise you,
but what the heck.
Honey, I'm purposely gaining 61 pounds
to get on disability.
Have you lost your mind?
Have you thought about your health
or your appearance?
Oh. So that's it, isn't it, Marge?
Looks. I didn't know
you were so shallow.
Oh, please! I would love you
if you weighed 1,000 pounds. But-
Beautiful. Good night.
Oh.! I got 15 minutes to gain a pound,
or I gotta face another day at work.
Bad news, Dad.
We're out of food.
We're even out of
the basic elements of food.
You ate all the tarragon,
and you drank all the soy sauce.
I need a miracle.
Aw, honey.
It looks just like a real doughnut.
Dad, it says "Non-Toxic. "
Well, that's a plus.
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
I did it!
Uh, Dad. Towel rack.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Hee-hee! Ho-ho! Oh, my.
I'm pleased to dedicate
this remote work terminal.
It will allow our safety inspector here
to perform his duties from home.
And so, excelsior to you, Mr. -
What's the name
of this gastropod?
Simpson, sir. One of
your chair-moisteners from Sector 7G.
Yes! Simpson!
Thank you for your pity.
Mom, are you ever planning
to step in and put a stop to this?
Normally, your father's
crackpot schemes fizzle out...
as soon as he finds
something good on TV.
But this season-
I'm looking for something
loose and billowy...
something comfortable
for my first day of work.
Work, huh? Let me guess.
Computer programmer?
- Computer magazine columnist. Something with computers.
- Well, I use a computer.
What's the connection? Must be
the nonstop sitting and snacking.
Well, sir. Many of our clients
find pants confining...
so we offer a range of alternatives
for the ample gentleman.
Ponchos, muumuus,
capes, jumpsuits...
unisheets, muslin body rolls,
academic andjudicial robes.
I don't wanna look like a weirdo.
I'll just go with a muumuu.
Arnie Pie in the Sky with the morning commute.
Traffic this morning
is as bad as it gets.
Due to a fire
at the army testing lab...
a bunch of escaped, infected monkeys
are roaming the expressway.
Despite the sweltering heat,
don't unroll your windows...
'cause those monkeys
seem confused and irritable.
Hee-hee-hee! I pity
those poor suckers on the freeway.
Gas, brake, honk.
Honk, honk, punch.
Gas, gas, gas.
8:58.
First time I've ever
been early for work-
except for all those
daylight savings days.
Lousy farmers.
"To start, press any key. "
Where's the "Any" key?
I see "Esk," "Catarol,"
and "Pig Up. "
There doesn't seem to be
any "Any" key.
Whew! All this computer hacking
is making me thirsty.
I think I'll order a Tab.
Oop. No time for that now.
The computer's starting.
"Check core temperature?
Yes/No. " Yes.
"Core temperature normal. "
Hmm. Not too shabby.
"Vent radioactive gas?"
N-O.
"Venting prevents explo-si-on. "
Ooh, this is hard. Where's my Tab?
Okay, then. Yes.
Vent the stupid gas.
Aw, no! The corn!
Paul Newman's gonna have
my legs broke.
Bart and Lisa have to go to school...
while I get to stay home.
Nyah-nyah-nyah,
nyah-nyah-nyah.
- I like school.
- Why don't you live in it then?
- I would if I could.
- Not me, sister.
When I grow up, I wanna be a lardo
on workmen's comp...
just like Dad.
I wash myself with a rag on a stick.
- Whoo-ooh-ooh.
- Euw!
Mom! This whole thing
is really creepy.
Are you sure
you won't talk to Dad?
I'd like to, honey,
but I'm not sure how.
Your father can be
surprisingly sensitive.
Remember when I giggled
at his Sherlock Holmes hat?
He sulked for a week
and then closed his detective agency.
Maybe you'll have
to hurt his feelings.
The longer he lives like this,
the harder it'll be to go back.
You're right.
Hmm. Maybe if I use
my least-nagging tone of voice-
Homer. Mmm.
Homer!
Homer?
That's it. That's the one.
All right. Send him on in.
- Dad?
- Yes, honey?
- Um, Mom just baked a cake.
- Ooh!
Hmm?
Homer, we need to have
a serious talk.
You dragged me all the way
from work for that?
Let's quietly and calmly
discuss the pros and cons...
of your controversial plan,
shall we?
- I-
- Con: You're endangering your health.
Pro: I'm drought and famine resistant.
Con: You're setting a bad example
for the children.
Pro: I, uh, don't have to go to work.
Con: You're running the air conditioner
nonstop. It's freezing in here.
Pro: Uh- Uh, I love you.
Con: I'm finding myself
less attracted to you physically.
- Marge, this is everything I've
ever dreamed of- right here.
And nobody's gonna
take it away from me.
You never had faith in me before,
but let me tell you-
the slim, lazy Homer you knew is dead.
Now I'm a big, fat dynamo!
And where's that cake?
- There's no cake.
- Oh.
"Vent radioactive gas?"
Y-E-S.
"Sound alertness horn?"
"Decalcify calcium ducts?"
Well, give me a "Y."
Give me a- Hey.
All I have to type is "Y."
Hey, Miss Doesn't Find Me
Attractive Sexually Anymore.
- I just tripled my productivity.
- Good. Good for you.
"Y." "Y."
So many letters to choose from.
I'll pick "Y." "Y." "Y."
What the heck are you
doin' over there?
There! You found the floor.
"Y." "Y." "Y." "Y."
"Y." "Y."
I'm going out.
I run errands during the day.
Could you pick me up
a lemonade and a beer?
The mail! The mail is here!
Ooh! "An urgent plea
from Edward James Olmos. "
"Lisa Simpson, can you afford to miss
another issue of the Utne Reader?"
Kids.
Free sample of fabric softener?
Whoo-hoo!
Mmm! I can feel
three kinds of softness.
Dad, what are you doing down there?
Washin' my "fat guy" hat, honey.
- We now return
to Search for the Sun.
Accordin' to Daddy's will...
I inherit the entire plantation.
I'll see to it
you don't get apricot one.
Uh, what's your dad's job again?
He's a nuclear-safety technician.
What's he doin' with that broom?
Uh, what isn't he doing?
I heard that guy's ass
has its own congressman.
Hey! Leave my dad alone.
Just because he's overweight
doesn't mean he's bad.
He's a sweet man,
and he has real feelings.
What are you kids lookin' at?
Hey, look. He's tryin' to get up to yell at us.
Don't make me close that shade!
Hey, Homer.
You promised Mom
you wouldn't wear your dress outside.
Nuts to that.
I'm goin' to the movies.
- Shouldn't you be working?
- I got someone to cover for me.
- One for Honk, please.
- Oh, gee. Uh, just a minute.
I have to check with the manager.
That overweight guy
wants to see the movie.
I'm terribly sorry, sir. I'm afraid our facilities
are not equipped to meet your needs.
- What are you talking about?
- What I'm saying, sir, is that a man of your carriage...
couldn't possibly fit in our seats.
- I could sit in the aisle.
- I'm afraid that would violate the fire code.
Hey, fatty.! I got a movie for ya.
A Fridge Too Far.
Shame on all of you.
Give me my dignity.
I just came here to see
Honk If You're Horny.! in peace.
Sir, if you just quiet down...
I'd be happy to treat you
to a garbage bag full of popcorn.
Oh! This may surprise you,
but you can't buy me off with food.
I'm sick of all your stereotypes
and cheap jokes.
The overweight individuals
in this country...
are just as smart and talented
and hardworking as everybody else.
And they're gonna make
their voices heard.
All they need is a leader!
I'll work harder than ever before...
and show the world overweight people
aren't undisciplined...
lazy and irresponsible.
What happened to my bird?
Oh! Marge?
Lisa? Flanders?
"Explosion imminent. "
Oh, my God.!
The plant's gonna explode.!
- Hey, that thing's going caca-cuckoo.
- Who cares? It's Homer's problem.
Wait. I know. Vent gas.
"Pressure too high"?
Oh! "Tank must be
shut down manually"?
Aw! Stupid bird!
I never should have
put you in charge!
Why, you-
Oh, who am I kidding?
It's all my fault.
I gotta call the plant and warn 'em.
- The fingers you
have used to dial are too fat.
To obtain a special dialing wand...
please mash the keypad with your palm now.
I'm gonna have
to shut it down myself!
Fat, don't fail me now.! D'oh.!
You gotta slow your car down and let me in
because I'm a big fat guy and I can't go anywhere.
Because there's gonna be some poison gas.
There's gonna be really poison gas.
Everybody's gonna be dead,
especially me! D'oh!
The ice-cream man.
You gotta let me in your car
and drive me-
Take anything you want, man!
Take it all!
Push out the jive.
Bring in the love.
I heard your dad went into a restaurant
and ate everything in the restaurant...
and they had to close
the restaurant.
My dad may have
gained a little weight...
but he's not some kind
of food-crazed maniac.
Ah! Oh! That's raspberry.
Oh.
Ice cream! Ice cream!
Workers, please. There'll be time
for the frozen-pudding wagon later.
You still owe me
10 more Iroquois twists.
- Ten, ha-ya-yah.
- Uh!
- And nine, ha-ya-yah.
Get away, damn it!
Run for your lives!
- I'll take a rocket bomb!
- What can I get for 30 cents?
Let go!
I gotta get to the tank!
Heck, I can't decide
without the pictures.
Six, ha-ya-yah.
Oh!
Four, ha-ya-yah.
Three, ha-ya-yah.
Two, ha-ya-yah.
Stupid switch!
I wish I had my reaching broom.
One, ha-ya-yah.
Wait a minute.
There's probably a-
Homer, your bravery
and quick thinking...
have turned a potential Chernobyl...
into a mere Three Mile Island.
Bravo.
I think it's ironic
that Dad saved the day...
while a slimmer man
would have fallen to his death.
And I think it's ironic that,
for once, Dad's butt...
- prevented the release of toxic gas-
- Bart!
We'll have you out of there as soon as
our tech boys get you decontaminated.
Thank you, Mr. Burns.
It was pretty scary up there, but-
For a while, I feared for my life.
Now, Homer, if there's anything else
I can do for you...
please don't hesitate to ask.
Mr. Burns,
can you make me thin again?
I guarantee it.
One.
One. One!
Bah! I'll just pay
for the blasted liposuction.
Whoo-hoo!
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net