The Simpsons
D'oh!
1796. A fiercely determined
band of pioneers leaves Maryland...
after misinterpreting
a passage in the Bible.
Their destination:
New Sodom.
This is their story.
This is gonna be great.
I hope they show the time where
they traded guns to the Indians for corn...
and then the Indians shot them
and took the corn.
- Egad! A monster!
- It's a horrible fiend!
It's some sort of land cow.
Stand back, fellow settlers.
Oh.
Ye have saved
our fledgling community.
Mr. Springfield, how can I hope
to achieve such greatness?
A noble spirit
"embiggens" the smallest man.
- Yea!
- Springfield rules!
Way to go, Springfield!
"Embiggens"? Hmm. I never heard that word
before I moved to Springfield.
I don't know why.
It's a perfectly "cromulent" word.
Now, as you all know, Springfield's
200th birthday is only a week away.
Every class will do its part
to make our local bicentennial...
just as memorable as
our national bicentennial.
Of course, you children
are too young to remember that...
with the possible
exception of Kearney.
Those tall ships really lifted the nation's
spirits after Watergate.
To celebrate our bicentennial,
all 20 of you...
will write an essay
aboutJebediah Springfield...
and the best 18 will be put on file
in the school library...
available to anyone
who requests them.
- Can we do illustrations?
- No.
Hey. They need volunteers to play
old-timey people in the parade.
Look. I can be a butter churner,
a typhoid carrier, an apprentice!
- I think I'll be an apprentice, Marge.
- What kind of apprentice?
That's for my master to decide.
How about town crier?
You'd be great at that.
- You think so?
- Well, yeah, Dad. You're a big, fat loudmouth...
- and you can walk when you have to.
- Aw.
Well, if you kids believe in me that much,
I'll give it my best shot.
Dangerous river crossings
threatened life and limb...
but helped our founding fathers
save on bridge tolls.
Excuse me.
I didn't mean to startle you,
but I do love to talkJebediah...
even when I'm drinking
my chicory.
I'm the curator,
Hollis Hurlbut.
Hi. I'm Lisa Simpson.
I'm here to research a report on Jebediah.
Oh, you're in for a treat.
You know, some historians consider
Jebediah Springfield a minor patriot...
but I think you'll find
he's easily the equal...
of William Dawes
or even Samuel Otis.
- Congratulations, Ned. You are our new town crier.
- D'oh!
May your shrill, nasal voice
ring throughout our streets and brains.
Well, thankily-dank, Mayor. I shan't disappoint.
"Har" ye. "Har" ye. I declare myself pickled tink...
about Springfield's
bicen-citally...
ti-tin-toodily,
rin-tin-tennial day!
You su-diddly-uck, Flanders!
Give me that.
Hear ye! Hear ye!
Ye old town crier
proclaimed crappy by all.
Chooseth Homer Simpson,
and he shalt rock thy world.
Good God! He is fabulous.
Mmm. He's "embiggened" that role
with his "cromulent" performance.
Top-notch "criering," I admit,
but the hat and bell belong to Flanders. So no dice.
Oh, they're just
family heirlooms.
That shouldn't stand in the way
of Homer taking my job and-
Less chat, more hat.
Whoo-hoo!
Hear ye! Hear ye!
The Homer broadcasting system
is on the air!
All hollering, all the time.
I'm gonna make-
You're to restrict your
criering to the parade...
- and selected preapproved publicity events.
- Okay.
This case holds our most
treasured exhibit:
objects owned and used
byJebediah.
Here's his fife, upon which he sounded
the sweet note of freedom...
his hatchet, with which he hacked
at the chains of oppression...
and his chamber pot.
Wow.
Excuse me. My microwave
johnnycakes are ready.
"The Secret Confessions
ofJebediah Springfield"?
"Know ye who read this, there is
more to my life than history records. "
Firstly, I did not tame
the legendary buffalo.
It was already tame.
I merely shot it.
Secondly, I have not always been known
as Jebediah Springfield.
Till 1796 I was Hans Sprungfeld,
murderous pirate.
And the half-wits of this town
will never learn the truth.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
"Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!"
Oh, my God.
Our town hero is a fraud.
"I write this confession
so that my infamy will live on...
long after my body has succumbed
to my infectious diphtheria. "
Ew.
Here's johnnycakes.
Is everything okay?
You look a bit flushed.
Oh, it's just the excitement
of studying Jebediah.
Sounds like you've come down
with a serious case of"Jebeditis. "
Just when I was
getting over my Chester A. Arthritis.
- Did-You had arthritis?
- Um, no.
Hear ye. Hear ye. What's for breakfast?
- Toast.
- I don't understand thee, Marge.
Hmm. Ye olde toast.
Whoo-hoo.
What would you say if I told you
thatJebediah Springfield...
wasn't as great as
he's cracked up to be?
Look. Jebediah was really a vicious pirate
named Hans Sprungfeld.
His tongue was bitten off
by a Turk in a grog-house fight.
No tongue, eh? How did he talk-
and eat and laugh and love?
He had a prosthetic tongue
made out of silver.
Yes. That'd do.
He was one of the evilest
men of the 1780s.
He even tried to kill
George Washington.
The dastard!
- Give me all your money.
- Never!
Ooh! Aaah!
I got the white stars you wanted,
but I couldn't find...
any red hearts, yellow moons
or green clovers.
Well, I'll use it,
but I'm not paying for it.
The next time
Hans Sprungfeld was seen...
he had changed his name
toJebediah Springfield.
Lisa, honey.
When my family first came to this state...
they had a choice
of living in Springfield or Stenchburg.
You know why
they chose Springfield?
Because everyone knows Jebediah Springfield
was a true American hero. End of story.
- I believe you, honey.
- You do?
Of course I do. You're always right
about this type of thing...
and for once I want in
on the ground floor.
Oh, thanks, Dad.
Ralph. "A."
Janey. "A."
And, Lisa, for your-
essay...
"Jebediah Springfield:
Super-Fraud," "F."
- But it's all true.
- This is nothing but...
dead-white-male bashing
from a P.C. thug.
It's women like you who keep
the rest of us from landing a husband.
Well, nice talking to ya.
- Lisa?
- Miss Hoover thought I made the whole thing up.
She called me a P.C. thug.
Well, I've been called a greasy thug too,
and it never stops hurting.
So here's what
we're gonna do:
Grease ourselves up real good
and trash that place with a baseball bat.
That won't help, Dad.
No one's ever gonna believe me.
But you have proof! We could go
get that confession out ofJebediah's fife.
- We could?
- Come on.
- We can use the baseball bat to smash open the case.
- No baseball bat.
Oh.
- Hi, Mr. Hurlbut.
- Oh, you're back.
And you brought a friend.
Town crier. I'd like to
ask you a few questions.
One: Where's the fife?
And two: Give me the fife.
Hey! Stop! I've got nothing but respect
for the office of town crier...
but this is well outside
your jurisdiction.
Oh, yeah?
Well, put this in your fife and smoke it.
What the-
That's Jebediah's secret confession.
It proves he was a fraud.
"The Secret Confessions
ofJebediah Springfield. "
Oh. I think, Lisa, that you've been
taken in by an obvious forgery.
Unfortunately, historical research
is plagued by this sort of hoax.
The so-called confession...
is just as phony
as the Howard Hughes will...
the Hitler diaries
or the Emancipation Retraction.
But it explains why there's no
record ofJebediah before 1795.
He was Hans Sprungfeld
until then.
That's preposterous.
Now get out.
You're banned from
this historical society.
You and your children
and your children's children.
For three months.
I'm not gonna give up. I refuse to believe
that everyone refuses to believe the truth.
- I'd like 25 copies on goldenrod-
- Right.
- um, 25 on canary-
- Canary.
- 25 on saffron-
- Mm-hmm.
- and 25 on paella.
- Okay. 100 yellow.
You don't have to
help me with this, Dad.
Oh, sure I do. I always believe
in helpin' the little guy.
And you're the littlest guy I know.
- Question. Is your name Ridley Scott orJames Cameron?
- No. It's Homer.
Then I will thank you to stop peering
at my screenplay, Homer.
And if I see a movie where computers
threaten our personal liberties...
I will know that
you stole my idea.
I'm just waitin' for my kid.
Mental note. Steal his idea.
Hi, Apu. Can I put this poster
in your window?
Well, of course you can,
you little pixie.
Oh. You're just as sweet as the sticks
which bear your name.
No, no. No, no. No, no, no.
Take that down. As a semi-legal immigrant,
your poster could land me in a predicament...
as red hot as the candies
which bear that name.
- He wouldn't let me put it up.
- Okay. Well, that's not gonna stop us.
I know a much better way
to get attention.
Hear ye! Hear ye!
My daughter has something to tell you
aboutJebediah Springfield.
Aw, the little cutie
wants to do somethin' cute.
Shut up, ya bums! Shut up!
Go ahead, angel.
Jebediah Springfield was nothing more...
than an evil bloodthirsty
pirate who hated this town.
Good God!
Homer, you know, I support,
uh, most any prejudice you can name...
but your hero phobia
sickens me.
You and your daughter ain't welcome here
no more. Barney, show 'em the exit.
- There's an exit?
- "Evil bloodthirsty pirate. "
Hello.
Town Jubilation Committee?
Yeah. I got something that's gonna
make you a lot less jubilant.
Can't you understand,
little girl?
Jebediah was no criminal.
That's right. The reason they say
he had a silver tongue...
is because he was
such a fine speaker.
That's a myth that got mixed up
with the truth.
You are tampering with forces
you can't understand.
We have major corporations
sponsoring this event.
I hope you know you're sponsoring
a celebration for a murderous pirate.
A pirate? Well, that's hardly the image
we want for Long John Silver's.
Well, I see no way
of settling this.
I say we imprison them
for the duration of our bicentennial.
There is one way.
Get the silver tongue.
IfJebediah's who I say he is,
then it should still be in his grave.
Why, that's highly unorthodox.
Yes, but human decency
prevents-
Dig him up! Dig up that corpse!
If you really love
Jebediah Springfield...
you'll haul his bones out of the ground
to prove my daughter wrong.
Dig up his grave!
Pull out his tongue!
Can't we have one meeting that doesn't end
with us digging up a corpse?
Now, Lisa, when you see there's
no silver tongue in there...
will you stop trying to ruin
Jebediah's reputation?
- Yes.
- What do we win if the tongue is there?
- Credibility.
- Aw. What a gyp.
Jebediah Springfield has been
replaced with a skeleton!
No. That's the skeleton
ofJebediah.
Gotcha. Gotcha. Okay.
Uh, well, let's start looking for that silver tongue.
Don't forget to look
in his shoes.
When I lose something,
sometimes it turns up in my shoes.
Actually, if it's anywhere
it would be lodged in the sinus.
All right. Here goes. Forgive us, Jebediah.
We mean no disrespect.
Well, that settles that.
There is no silver tongue,
is there, Bonesy?
Oh, I wish, Chief. With that kind of dough,
I could buy me some eyeballs.
Well, that's the spirit, Bonesy.
- Why don't you sing a song for the nice people?
- All right.
I was so sure.
- Hear ye. Hear ye. Everybody
makes mistakes. Let's go home.
Not so fast, Simpson.
This foul business
was all your fault.
By the power vested in me,
I hereby strip you of your ceremonial bell-
No! No!
and tri-corner hat.
You will have the hat cleaned
and then return it.
Oh, Dad.
I'm really sorry.
I know how much
you wanted to be in the parade.
Oh, it's not
your fault, honey.
I'm supposed to be
the responsible one.
I shouldn't have let you
let me get carried away.
Why did you dig up
the bones of the past?
Why did you disturb
the ghosts of history?
I- I-
General Washington?
You did some good work
exposing Jebediah, Lisa. Don't stop now.
There's just one piece left
in the puzzle.
But I've caused so much trouble already,
General Washington. I can't go on.
We had quitters
in the Revolution too.
We called them Kentuckians.
Well, I'll just have to find
another little girl to be president.
What's your friend
Janey's number?
No! NotJaney!
She'll pack the Supreme Court with boys!
Oh, let me help you, George Washington.
I still want to help you!
I want to help you,
George Washington?
Even your dreams are square.
Can you open my milk,
Mommy?
I'm not Mommy, Ralph. I'm Miss Hoover.
The missing piece of the puzzle.
I've got it.!
You? What are you doing here?
I was right aboutJebediah,
and now I can prove it.
Oh, please.
Not that claptrap again.
Haven't you hurtJebediah enough
with your childish tales...
of pirate ships and fisticuffs
and a silver tongue that can't be found?
- That's because you stole it!
- That's a lie!
I'm an antiquarian, damn it.
It's my job to seek out the truth.
But when you found the truth
you couldn't take it.
You couldn't stand that
you devoted your life to a fraud...
so you covered it up,
didn't you?
- Didn't you?
- No. No. That-That's preposterous.
I mean, I- I couldn't.
You-You can't-
Stop it!
Where's the silver tongue?
I thought no one
would ever find it.
When I pried open
the coffin it was there-
that shiny tongue
sticking out ofhis mouth...
razzing my entire career-
my-my life.
Before the dust could settle,
I pocketed it.
- But I thought I had you fooled.
- You did.
Until I realized thatJebediah's confession
was saying more than he meant it to.
How else could he have
gotten this?
Sprungfeld must have taken it
with him when he ran off after the fight.
- Exactly.
- This celebration is a sham.
And it's all my fault.
We've got to get the word out to every man,
woman and child in town.
Stop!
Stop everything! Stop the parade.
- What?
- What's goin' on here?
- This is highly unorthodox.
- This is Lisa Simpson.
She's discovered something
very important...
aboutJebediah Springfield
that you need to hear.
People of Springfield,
I, um-
I don't know
quite how to say this-
Don't be shy, little girl.
Think ofJebediah, and the words will come.
I did a lot of research on
Jebediah Springfield, and-
- Hmm. I think I can pick her off.
- Wait. Let's see what she has to say.
Jebediah Springfield was-
Jebediah was...
great.
I, um,
just wanted to say...
that I've done
some research, and, uh...
he was great.
Yeah.
- Well said.
- Great speech!
Jebediah would be
proud of you.
- Why didn't you tell them?
- Because the myth ofJebediah has value too.
It's brought out the best
in everyone in this town.
Regardless of who said it,
a noble spirit embiggens the smallest man.
- Well, hey. It's Homer. Good to see you, nei-
- Get lost.
Hear ye! Hear ye!
Hear ye!
He is not the official town crier!
Police, do something!
Well, I'd like to, ma'am,
but he's too damn good.
Let him march, boys.
Let the man march.
It's that team
ofJebediah Springfield
Whip them horses
Let them wagons roll
That a people
might embiggen America
That a man might embiggen
His soul
- His soul
- Hyah.
His soul
Hyah.!
Hyah.
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net