The Simpsons
D'oh!
Whoa.
You know, most of my life I've-
I've had to live with the shame
of being a screw-up.
But now, as I stand here with
the award for the district's safest bus driver...
well, i-it's like a dream come true.
- Otto.! Wake up.!
- Huh?
Aah!
So, um, who's good
at keepin' secrets?
"Dear parents, due to yesterday's unscheduled
field trip to the auto wrecking yard...
"the school bus will be
out of commission for two weeks.
"By reading this letter out loud...
"you have waived any legal
responsibility on our part...
in perpetuity, throughout the universe. "
Well, we'll have to organize a carpool.
Hey! Every day will be like a road trip!
With your dad! To school!
So...
how about those
rainbow suspenders, huh?
Dad-
- Pretty cool way to keep your pants up, eh?
- Dad!
I see these kids now with "jive"
printed on their shirts.
Now, I can teach you
how you're supposed to say "jive. "
Dad! Please just
drive the car, Dad.
I'm watching the road, sweetie.
"You jive turkey!"
See?
You got to sass it.
"Quit jivin' me, turkey!"
A turkey is a bad person.
KFSL- Fossil 103.
Classic hits
from ABBA to Zeppelin, comma, Led.
Tell him!
Uh, Mr. Simpson, sir?
Can you please
change the radio station?
But this is Grand Funk Railroad.
You guys back there
know Grand Funk, right?
Nobody knows the band Grand Funk?
The wild, shirtless lyrics
of Mark Farner?
The bong-rattling bass
of Mel Schacher?
The competent drum work
of Don Brewer?
Oh, man!
For more information on Grand Funk...
consult your school library.
When I listen to a really good song...
I start nodding my head,
like I'm saying "Yes!" to every beat.
"Yes! Yes! Yes! This rocks!"
And then sometimes
I switch it up, like-
"No! No! No! Don't stop a-rockin'!"
Dad, please.
You're embarrassing us.
No, I'm not.
I'm teaching you about rock music.
Now, Grand Funk Railroad
paved the way forJefferson Airplane...
which cleared the way
forJefferson Starship.
The stage was now set for
The Alan Parsons Project...
which I believe was
some sort of hovercraft.
Dad, no one cares about any
of your stupid dinosaur bands!
You have the worst,
lamest taste in music ever!
I'm just trying to party with you guys.
Homer, first of all, it's "par-tay"...
and second, we wouldn't
"par-tay" with you...
if you were the last dad on Earth.
Hi there. It's been a while
since I set foot in Good Vibrations Music.
Where can I find
the latest releases by Bread?
- Oldies.
- Oldies?
But you've got
all the top bands in here!
Styx? I just heard them on
the King Biscuit Flower Hour.!
Now, here are some of
your no-name bands.
Sonic Youth? Nine-Inch Nails?
Hullabalooza?
Hullabalooza is a music festival.
The greatest music festival of all time?
There can be only one truly great music festival
a lifetime, and it's the Us Festival.
- The what festival?
- The Us Festival!
Yeesh! It was sponsored by
that guy from Apple Computers.
What computers?
Why do you need new bands?
Everyone knows rock
attained perfection in 1974.
It's a scientific fact.
Quadraphonic sound, a water bed,
and now a strobe light.
Gentlemen, say hello
to the Second Base-Mobile.
Wicked!
Back then
we didn't care what anyone thought...
and the chicks
found that irresistible.
I think you're cool, Homer Simpson.
Sandra, that was mean.
But most of all, I remember the music.
- What the hell are you two doin'?
- It's called rockin' out.
You wouldn't understand, Dad.
You're not with it.
I used to be "with it. "
But then they changed what "it" was.
Now what I'm with isn't "it,"
and what's "it" seems weird and scary to me.
It'll happen to you!
No way, man.
We're gonna keep on rockin' forever.
Forever. Forever.
Forever.
What's wrong, Homie?
I went to the record store today and they
were playing all this music I never heard of.
It was like the store had gone crazy.
Hmm. Record stores have always seemed
crazy to me, but it doesn't upset me.
Music is none of my business.
That's fine for you, Marge...
but I used to rock and roll all night
and party ev-er-y day.
Then it was every other day.
Now I'm lucky if I can find half an hour a week
in which to get funky.
I've gotta get out of this rut
and back into the groove!
Well, good!
Try to include Bart and Lisa.
Dear Lord, if you keep Homer
from embarrassing us today...
we promise to build several
churches in your honor.
Bart! No!
Hey, wait! I'm okay today!
My mom bought me deodorant!
Dad, you forgot to pick up Milhouse.
I did? I must be
getting forgetful in my old age.
Open the glove compartment
and fetch me my brain medicine.
What are you talking about?
Well? What have we here?
Looks like your uncool dad...
scored tickets to Hullabalooza!
Bart, these look real.
Check the authenticator spot.
This is an authentic Hullabalooza ticket.
For authentic refreshment,
eat Clark bars.
And for totally outrageous
class rings, it's Jostens.
Go, Jostens!
You're not going to school today.
Today your classroom
will be the Capitol City Amphitheater.
Your teacher-
four dozen rock bands.
So get ready for some
well-supervised craziness...
while you rock out
with your father!
Whoo-hoo!
Wow, it's like Woodstock...
only with
advertisements everywhere...
and tons of security guards.
People, have your tickets out.
Throw your cameras out.
Surrender all identification.
Ohh!
My homemade Kahlua!
Generation X may be shallow, but at least
they have tolerance and respect for all people.
Hey! A freak show!
Oww!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
And now the band
you've all been waiting for, Cypress Hill!
Before we start-
We have a lost child here.
If she's not claimed
within the next hour...
she will become property
of Blockbuster Entertainment.
- What is that smell?
- It smells like Otto's jacket.
- Dude, karma.
- What?
Karma. Karma.
Oh, I get it.
Dad, you cannot wear that!
That's a Rastafarian hat!
Hey, I been safari-in'
since before you were born.
Wearing a Jamaican hat makes a bold statement
about your connection to reggae music.
Well, excu-u-use me!
You know what, Dad?
Maybe we'll go exploring
on our own for a while.
Well, Homer, this is it.
Time to get back with the people.
The young people.
All right! Yeah!
Cool concert.
Am I right?
- Yeah, nice try, narc.
- Where's the narc?
- Who?
- That fatJamaican guy.
What'd I say?
What's goin' on?
Hey, we're just tryin' to have a good time, narc.
Why do you want to destroy us?
Don't commit your hate crimes here!
Hate crime!
Okay, I'm heading out now.
More butt support.
More butt support!
D'oh!
It may be bleak...
but this music is really
getting to the crowd.
Ah, making teenagers depressed
is like shooting fish in a barrel.
Oh!
Makes no sense.
I haven't changed since high school,
and suddenly I'm uncool.
I've been kicked out of paradise.
I'll never be part
of the scene again.
Uh-oh.
Oh, man,
There goes Peter Frampton's big finale.
He's gonna be pissed off.
You're damn right
I'm gonna be pissed off!
I bought that pig
at Pink Floyd's yard sale!
- Dad, are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Sir, I run Hullabalooza's Pageant
of the Trans-Mundane- the freak show-
and I've been looking for a big fatso
to shoot with a cannon.
I'd like very much
for you to be that fatso.
So, you wanna go on tour
with a traveling freak show.
I don't think
I have a choice, Marge.
- Of course you have a choice.
- How do you figure?
You don't have to join a freak show
just because the opportunity came along.
You know, Marge, in some ways...
you and I are
very different people.
And now, get ready for the man...
with the iron stomach!
Hi, everybody.
Is everybody... good?
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Stay in school.
Your hero, Homer.
Hey, Cannonball.
I like your statement.
When life takes a cheap shot at you,
you stand your ground.
Billy Corgan,
Smashing Pumpkins.
Homer Simpson, smiling politely.
You know, my kids think
you're the greatest.
And thanks to your gloomy music...
they've finally stopped dreaming of a future
I can't possibly provide.
Well, we try to make a difference.
"Dear Bart and Lisa"-
All is well on tour...
with America's most popular
alternative music festival.
Our firstjob is to entertain.
And I like to think sometimes
we get a message across as well.
But the main thing is...
I finally tapped into
that spirit of self-destruction...
that makes rock and roll the king of music.
Whoo-hoo!
Hello, ticket holders!
Oh, here comes
that cannonball guy.
He's cool.
- Are you being sarcastic, dude?
- I don't even know anymore.
Thank you!
And remember,
don't trust anyone over 30!
And now, Peter Frampton!
Thanks, Homer.
Homer Simpson, everyone!
Hey, Homer, looks like our next stop
is your hometown, Springfield.
Is it true that we have to
bring our own water?
We got a little rule back home-
If it's brown, drink it down.
If it's black, send it back.
The hometown show's
the big one, Homer.
People who called you a weirdo in high school get
to see what a successful freak you've become.
Hey, I wasn't a weirdo.
I was in the audio-visual club.
Really? Me too.
But I got kicked out
'cause of my views on Vietnam.
Also, I was stealing projectors.
Anyway, get ready, beer belly.
- We're gonna show Springfield what we're made of!
- All right, Homer!
Yeah, Homer.!
That was odd.
Gee, I don't like
the sound of that.
No biggie. I'm cool.
Nothing's more important to me than
the health and well-being of my freaks.
I'm sending you to a vet.
My God.!
Those cannonballs have practically
demolished your stomach.
From now on,
no cannonballs, no spicy foods...
and when you lie
in a hammock, please...
rest your beer on your head
or your genitals.
Rules. I'm a rocker!
I don't care for rules.
Mr. Simpson, this is serious.
If you take one more cannonball
to the gut, you will die.
Die?
Well, you don't scare me, Doc.
'Cause dyin' would be a stone groove!
Got any messages forJimi Hendrix?
Yes.
Pick up your puppy.
So, what's it like being famous, Dad?
People know your name,
but you don't know theirs. It's great.!
Dad, do you wear boxers or briefs?
Nope!
What religion are you?
You know, the one with all the well-meaning
rules that don't work out in real life.
Uh, Christianity.
- What's with all the questions?
- Just some report I gotta do for school.
- Hey, you want some pie?
- Sure.
We've got a lot of catching up to do.
Mmm.
Clear the way. Clear the way!
Performer coming through!
This is so exciting.
Last time I got to go backstage was when
Bart ripped his pants at the Christmas play.
- Mom!
- Ha-ha!
Hello, bands.!
Who is playing with
the London Symphony Orchestra?
Come on, people. Somebody ordered
the London Symphony Orchestra.
Possibly while high!
Cypress Hill,
I'm looking in your direction.
Hey, man,
did we order an orchestra?
- What's up with this orchestra?
- Where'd the orchestra come from, man?
- I don't know.
- You didn't tell me about this, man.
We gotta do somethin'.
Uh, yeah, we think we did.
Uh, do you know
"Insane in the Brain"?
We mostly know classical,
but we could give it a shot.
Now, this I like.
Man, that guy's guitar is talkin'!
Hey, my shoes are talkin' too!
Don't worry.
We won't hurt you.
We only want
to have some fun.
And to think, Smithers,
you laughed when I bought Ticketmaster.
"Nobody's going to pay
a hundred-percent service charge. "
Well, it's a policy that ensures a healthy mix
of the rich and the ignorant, sir.
Do you feel like we do, Springfield?
Yeah! Do y-
Wait. Do ya- Do ya feel-
Do- Do ya feel-
Oh, come on!
Do you feel-
Homer Simpson wrecks my pig...
Cypress Hill steals my orchestra...
and Sonic Youth's in my cooler!
Get out of there, you kids!
Oh, come on, Mr. Frampton.
You're not gonna eat all that watermelon.
Please!
I'm trying to perform.
Go ahead.
We'll stay here and guard your cooler.
Twenty-five years
I've been in this- I've never-
And now, Springfield, this is the moment
that you've been waiting for!
The man who embodies everything
about rock and roll- except the music.
Give it up for your very own
homegrown hero...
Homer Simpson.!
I used to carpool with that guy!
Oh, this is heavy.
Okay, Homer,
don't fear the reaper.
Ohh! I'm gonna die!
Cannons are designed to hurt.
They're designed to hurt!
Shh! Mom!
Dad needs our support.
You're the coolest dad alive!
Oh, Marge, I thought I had
an appetite for destruction...
but all I wanted
was a club sandwich.
There might be one in this cooler.
- Oh! Here we go.
- Ohh!
Oh, man, Homer wussed out.
I'm so disillusioned.
Hey, Hullabalooza isn't about freaks.
It's about music and advertising...
and youth-oriented product positioning.
That, and getting toasted.
Nicely toasted.
Homer, I'm sorry. There's nothing worse
than a yellow-bellied freak.
Unless that's his act.
- I expect your letter of resignation on my desk.
- You have a desk?
I mean the hood of my car.
I'll miss you Pumpkins,
but I just can't share your bleak worldview.
- I've got too much to live for.
- We envy you, Homer.
All we have is our music,
our legions of fans...
our millions of dollars and our youth.
Whoo-hoo!
- Let's all go out and buy fur coats!
- I want a walk-in humidor.
So I realized that being
with my family is more important...
than being cool.
Dad, what you just said
was powerfully uncool.
You know what the song says.
It's hip to be square.
That song is so lame.
So lame that it's... cool?
- No.
- Am I cool, kids?
- Good. I'm glad.
- And that's what makes me
cool- not caring. Right? - No.
Well, how the hell do you be cool?
I feel like we've tried everything here.
Wait, Marge.
Maybe if you're truly cool,
you don't need to be told you're cool.
- Sure you do.
- How else would you know?
Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net