## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
What a perfect outing
for a beautiful autumn day.
I feel sorry for everyone
who's cooped up inside...
watching the seventh game
of the World Series.
Yeah, they won't learn
anything about apples today.
And the cider mill operated
continuously until 1941...
when its workers left to fight
in the Second World War.
When they returned,
the old girl was just as they'd left her...
only now she was infested
with thousands upon thousands of rats.
[All Gasping, Reacting]
Right. And if you listen
real carefully...
you can still hear them
gnawing away at the apples...
and splashing around
in the toilets.
And that concludes
this portion of the tour.
[Change Rattling]
One of the most historically
significant fruit presses...
- in this part of the state-
- [Sighs]
was based on a German design,
but modified for the larger American apple.
Well, if God didn't make little green apples,
it's Homer Simpson.
- How long have you been here?
- Twenty of the suckiest minutes of my life.
Oh, sucking down the cider, huh?
Hey, word to the wise- season pass.
Pays for itself
after the 16th visit.
You know, most people
don't know the difference...
between apple cider
and apple juice.
But I do. Now, here's a little trick
to help you remember.
If it's clear and yella,
you've got juice there, fella.
If it's tangy and brown,
you're in cider town.
Now, there's two exceptions and it gets kind of-
[Fades]
[Homer Thinking]
Oh! You can stay, but I'm leaving.
[Continues, Indistinct]
And of course in Canada,
the whole thing's flip-flopped.
Oh, my!
I better get you some cider.
Next to spring and winter,
fall is my absolute favorite season.
Just look at all
this beautiful "foilage."
It's not "foilage," Mom.
It's foliage. Foliage.
That's what I said- "foilage."
It doesn't take a "nucular" scientist
to pronounce "foilage."
[Wind Whistling]
Honestly, Smithers, I don't know
why Harvard even bothers to show up.
They barely even won.
Their cheating was even more rampant
than last year, sir.
Well, I say let Harvard have
its football and academics.
Yale will always be first
in gentlemanly club life.
Why, every friend I have,
I made right here.
- Hello, Burnsie. It's your old roomy, Dink.
- [Shudders]
[Pool Chalk Squeaking]
Steady. Steady.
- Oh, nicely played, sir.
- [Man On P.A.] Attention, passengers.
The train has been
temporarily delayed...
because of a discarded couch
on the tracks.
Yes, it looks like
some sort of a couch.
Oh, this may take
a while, Smithers.
Why don't you get drunk and stumble around
comically for my amusement?
I'll be a one-man conga line.
[Snoring]
Ah, customers. Thank God.
Papa needs a new pair of everything.
Hey, how you doing?
Welcome to scenic Waynesport.
And remember your visit
with a googly-eyed walnut.
How about a googly-eyed rock?
Some nice local squash candy?
A stressed-out Pepsi bottle?
Come on.
If this stuff is too nice for you,
I've got some crap.
## [Humming]
Oh, oh!
[Train Whistle Blows]
Hey, CaseyJones,
where's this train headed?
- Springfield.
- Yeah, yeah. What state?
- [Continues, Indistinct]
- [Train Whistle Blows]
I can honestly say
that was the most fun I've ever had.
The mill, the history,
all that gorgeous foliage.
I can't "exscape" Lisa,
our little walking "libary."
Can't they get a pole
for that sign?
- That's a hitchhiker, Homer.
- Ooh, let's pick him up.
- No. What if he's crazy?
- And what if he's not? Then we'd look like idiots.
- We're not picking him up.
- Oh, yes, we are.
- There's not enough room.
- Yes, there is.
I just don't think
it's a good idea.
And I think it's the best idea
I've ever had.
- We're picking up the weirdo, and that's final.
- [Tires Squeal]
Hey, you folks are all right.
Man, it was rough
getting a ride out there.
The only car that stopped
was a hearse that thought I fell out.
It was rough, I tell you.
- Careful of the apple pie on the seat.
- Uh-oh.
Grampa, are you sitting on the pie?
I sure hope so.
Hey, I'm looking for this guy.
Anybody know who he is?
Yeah, sure, we know him.
That's Mr. Burns.
- He tried to kill our puppies.
- He sexually harassed me.
- He stole my fiancée.
- He made fun of my weight.
Okay, so there's been a little friction.
Know his address?
Whoa! This guy's got more bread
than a prison meat loaf.
He's rich, I tell ya.
I never seen a place with a walk-in mailbox.
Hey, who am I talking to?
[Doorbell Rings]
- Yes?
- Yeah.
Uh, hi. My-My name is Larry.
I'm here to see Mr. Burns.
Well, I hate to break it
to you, Larry...
but if Mr. Burns ever
wants to see a stranger...
he will observe him
through a powerful telescope.
- Now, if you-
- Smithers, what's going on?
How dare you interrupt
my lime rickey?
[Slurping, Sighs]
State your business.
Well, geez! I'm a little nervous here.
What I'm trying to say is I'm-
You're what? Selling light bulbs?
Worried about the whales?
- Keen on Jesus? Out with it!
- Well, Mr. Burns, I'm your son.
Oh, and I stepped on one of your peacocks.
You got a paper towel?
It's true. He is my son.
- Hey, now you're talking!
- Good God.
Ah, Pop, don't get me wrong.
It's great to be here.
But how's a guy like you
wind up with a son like me?
Ah, Larry, my lad, I've gone over this story
in my mind a million times.
It was 1941, the-
No, '39,
my 25th Yale reunion.
[Burns Narrating] Who should appear
but the unrequited love of my college years-
Mimsie Bankcroft.
Of course by then, Mimsie
had her share of wrinkles...
and a gray hair or two, but my adoring eyes
saw past those minor imperfections...
to her 21-year-old daughter, Lily.
I took Lily
to the local "cinematorium'...
where our passions were inflamed by Clark
Gable's reckless use of the word "damn. '"
We sneaked into
the nearby Peabody Museum.
There, under the smiling eyes
of four stuffed Eskimos...
we expressed our love physically...
as was the style at the time.
[Guffaws]
Well, how do you like that?
I have been in a museum.
- What happened with you and Ma?
- There was a terrible scandal.
Lily's family forced her
to give you up...
and bundled her off to a convent
in the South Seas.
I never heard from her again.
But I prattle on.
Tell me everything about your life.
Oh, what's to tell?
I was at the orphanage till I was 18.
Then I got my job
at the souvenir stand.
Oh, and once I saw a blimp.
Well, you must be tired.
Let me show you your room.
Oh, is this posh!
Ah, Pop, nobody's
ever been so nice to me.
Yes, yes. All right.
Uh-huh.
It's good to see you too.
Now then, in case you get bored,
here's the playroom.
You can't just eat the orange
and throw the peel away!
A man's not a piece of fruit!
This show was supposed
to close last week!
Close this show!
Close it, I say.
Hey, don't worry about it.
You're all right.
[Bird Squawks]
[Snoring, Mumbles]
- [Snoring]
- [Both Scream]
Hey, you're that hitchhiker.
What are you doing here?
Learning the family business.
I'm Larry Burns, the boss's son.
Uh-oh.
Oh, relax.
I don't wanna work.
I'm so lazy I took lessons
on a player piano.
Wow! That's really lazy.
Lazy, you're not kidding.
Why, I'm like a rug on Valium. I'm talking lazy.
So lazy.
And Larry and I have so much in common,
Marge, way more than you and me.
If I could be stranded on an island with anyone,
it would definitely be Larry.
I think we've heard enough
about Larry Burns for one evening.
Why? It's not like anything interesting
happened to anyone else today.
## [Ballroom]
[Chattering, Laughing]
Hey, Pop, this crowd
is pretty swanky.
- I'm not gonna fit in here.
- Nonsense, Larry.
Your blood is bluer
than any of theirs.
Just give them a snootful
of the old Burns charm.
Oh, Admiral Carstairs,
I'd like you to meet my son, Larry.
Hey, Skipper, good to meet you.
Where'd you start out,
on the Merrimack?
Hey, I should talk.
I hope I look that good when I'm 200.
- That's such insubordination!
- Larry, please.
He's very sensitive about his age.
Oh, Monty, this must be the son
I've heard so much about.
Larry, you must meet our daughter,
the debutante. She came out last spring.
- Whoa! Put her back in! She's not done yet.
- [Scoffs]
Smithers, there's something a bit odd
about young Larry.
I can't quite put
my finger on it.
Well, he is a bit rough
around the edges, sir.
One might blame his truly heroic
intake of cocktails.
Pull up a seat, Pop.
You too, Chuckles.
I mean, the food ain't great,
but the portions are terrific.
Hey, I'm kidding. Relax.
Hey, give my regards to Mrs. Boyardee.
[Shudders]
A total lack of refinement.
Smithers, send for the boys
at Yale admissions, hmm?
Well, did you meet Larry?
Oh, yes. He made light
of my weight problem...
then suggested my motto
should be "Semper Fudge."
At that point
he told me to "relax."
- How were his test scores?
- Let's just say this-
he spelled "Yale" with a six.
I see. Well, l-
Oh, you know, I just remembered
it's time for my annual donation.
I wonder how much I should give.
Well, frankly, test scores like Larry's
would call for a very generous contribution.
For example, a score of 400 would require
a donation of new football uniforms.
Three hundred- a new dormitory.
And in Larry's case,
we would need an international airport.
Yale could use
an international airport, Mr. Burns.
Are you mad?
I'm not made of airports! Get out!
Summon my son at once.
- Uh, it appears he's gone drinkin', sir.
- [Scoffs]
Everybody, go nuts. I'm buyin'!
Hey, handsome,
send the bill to my dad.
Okay, but the last guy who charged a drink
to Burns turned up in a landfill.
Yeah, but it was worth it.
[Burps]
Hey, what's everybody in this burg
have against my dad?
He's a pussycat. I tell you,
he's a doll-baby.
Come on over.
I'll show you.
- [Sipping Loudly]
- [Smacking Lips]
Ah, this is some party. If it gets any livelier,
a funeral's gonna break out.
Quiet, you.
Nobody likes a comedian.
Geez! Come on, Dad, we got company.
Make with the yakety-yak-yak.
Oh, yakety-yak-yak.
- You, food bag, do you have a son?
- Yes, sir, I do.
And is he a constant
disappointment?
Does he bring home nitwits
and make you talk to them?
Oh, all the time.
Have you ever heard of this kid Milhouse?
- He's a little wiener who-
- Fascinating. Good night.
Dad, what's with you tonight?
I mean, I'm getting frostbite over here.
I'll tell you what's with me-
the humiliation of having a coarse,
boorish ignoramus for a son.
Uh, I should go.
What's the matter, Pop?
Don't you love me anymore?
[Door Slams Shut]
Oh.
[Grumbling]
Geez! Dad and I,
we started out great...
but now it's falling apart,
like a Chinese motorcycle.
It's so unfair.
You're everything a dad could hope for.
Yeah. I tell ya,
I don't get no regard.
No regard at all.
No esteem either.
Larry, there's only one sure way to make him
realize how much he loves you...
and that is a phony kidnapping.
Yeah, right. I don't know.
Maybe I should just leave town.
Phony kidnapping.
Nah. I know what I gotta do.
I gotta clean up my act.
No more joking around all the time.
No more slacking off at work.
And most important, no more booze.
- [Glass Breaks]
- I know I can do it.
"Your son has been kidnapped."
I can't believe someone
would kidnap my Larry.
- I won't rest until he's returned to me.
- Not to be impertinent, sir...
but didn't you want Larry out of your life
as recently as two hours ago?
It's the principle, Smithers.
Nobody steals from Montgomery Burns...
whether it be my Sunday newspaper
or my loutish oaf of a son.
All right, Mr. B., when the kidnappers
call with the ransom demand...
you tell them you'll leave the money
under the big net in the park.
And then down comes the net.
Right, Chief?
Hey, I like it.
I like it a lot.
[Birds Twittering]
Hmm?
- Hmm?
- [TV, Indistinct]
What are you doing
in the basement?
- It's like you're hiding out down here.
- Hiding out?
[Raspberry] Marge, you've been reading
too many "hide out" books.
And what's that hitchhiker
doing here?
Is every drifter we meet
going to move in with us?
Of course not.
We'll decide that on a drifter-by-drifter basis.
He's not a drifter, Mom.
That's Mr. Burns's son, Larry.
He's great at pointing out
everyone's foibles.
Hey! How you doing?
Ooh, look at your hair.
What happened?
You saw yourself in a mirror?
He's kidding, Mom.
But, seriously, I'd love to have hair like yours.
I just can't get the zoning permits.
Hey, that reminds me, Mom. Buckingham Palace
called. They want their hat back.
- [Groans]
- Hey, kids, how about a hand
for your mom? She's all right.
- Yeah, Mom!
- All right, Mom!
- Oh, yeah. Thank you.
- [Ringing]
- Ahoy, hoy?
- Hello, Mr. Burns. This is the kidnapper.
- [Chuckling]
- Do you miss your son?
- Yes, I'm missing one son. Return it immediately.
If you really love Larry, prove it,
and you can have him back today.
Whoa!
How much proof do you need?
Five thousand, six thousand?
I swear, that's all I've got.
Don't you care about your son?
This is more important than money.
More important than money?
Who is this?
- Uh- Uh, just a second.
- [Dial Tone]
Beautiful. Eddie, did you trace
the phone number?
- Sure did, Chief.
- 555-
Oh, geez, that's gotta be phony.
Hey, I think I got a pai gow.
[Groans] I hate pai gow!
Can't we just play "quang jong"?
- Can't we just go upstairs?
- No!
This is Kent Brockman in Chopper Copter 6
with a special report.
Montgomery Burns's son
has been kidnapped.
- Kidnapped?
- Marge, it's not a real kidnapping.
It's a simple hoax
to win a father's love.
- You know how I feel about hoaxes.
- Still?
I want you to take Larry
back to Mr. Burns right now...
- before you get in a lot of trouble.
- What, but, but-
Marge, it's broad daylight,
and there's cops everywhere.
- No excuses. Just do it.
- [Groans]
Of course, we'll bring you updates
just as soon as they-
Oh, wait a minute!
There they are, Larry Burns and his kidnapper.
[Screams]
Appearing in broad daylight with police
everywhere, ladies and gentlemen...
there's only one word
for that- idiocy.
[Groans]
- [Tires Squealing]
- [Sirens Wailing]
We gotta find someplace to hide.
[Gasps]
The abandoned warehouse!
D'oh!
Stupid economic recovery.
[Bell On DoorJingles]
Hey! Buy a costume
or get out, fellas.
We gotta find someplace
no one will ever go.
Hello!
- [Tires Squealing]
- [Child] Drive faster, Grandma!
Grandma's gaining on us!
[Chuckles]
They'll never look for us here.
Yeah, this place is emptier
than a Scottish pay toilet.
Shh. Some people are trying
to watch the movie.
You don't like it, call a cop.
- [Whimpers]
- [Laughing]
[Both Laughing]
[Sirens Wailing]
This is Kent Brockman live
from the Aztec Theater...
where police have learned
that kidnapper Homer Simpson...
and hostage, Larry Burns,
are inside talking loudly.
Ooh, give yourself up, Homie!
- No, Dad! Shoot your way out!
- [Groans]
- [Grunts]
- [Gunfire]
[All Screaming]
[Kent Brockman]
A bloody end for Homer Simpson...
is just one of several possible outcomes,
according to our computer simulation.
Now, here's how it would look if the police
killed him with a barrage of baseballs.
We've gotta go down there
and help Dad.
- [Baseballs Thudding]
- [Homer Groaning] Oh, stop it!
Shh.
[Feet Sticking To Floor]
- Still warm. They can't be far.
- Chief!
[Grunts]
Don't be a fool, Simpson.
Let the kid go.
The negotiations have failed.
Shoot him!
[Cocks Gun]
- Wait!
- [All] Wait?
I mean, Homer's no kidnapper.
Well, he's the best friend I ever had.
We faked the whole thing.
[Chattering]
I should've known. You're
the only one stupid enough to kidnap you.
Now, get down here so I can spank you
in front of this gawking rabble.
- Smithers, take off my belt.
- With pleasure, sir.
Hold on, Mr. Burns.
Maybe we did fake a kidnapping.
But is that really such a crime?
All your son wanted
was a little attention, a little love.
I'm a father myself, sir.
And, sure, sometimes
my kids can be obnoxious...
or boring, or stinky.
But they can always
count on one thing-
their father's unconditional love.
- [All] Mmm!
- How about it, Pop?
I know it's tough,
but can you love me for what I am?
[Groans]
Well-
[Mumbles]
There, there, sonny boy.
I suppose
I have been a bit-
Oh, no, I can't do it.
It's just not me.
I'm sorry, Larry.
I can't be the family that you need.
Oh, that's okay.
I got a wife and kids.
Oh, that reminds me.
They're probably wondering where I went.
I told them I'm going for coffee.
That was a week ago.
Well, Son, delighted
to have met you.
It's good to know that...
there's another kidney out there for me.
You got it, Pop.
Just let me run a few pints through it first.
- As long as everybody's here, let's party!
- [All Cheering]
## [Pop Rock]
- Who's playing that music?
- And where is all that liquor coming from?
It's a party, Marge.
It doesn't have to make sense.
- ## [Continues]
- Whoo! Oh, yeah!
## [Continues]
www.tvsubtitles.net