## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[Static]
[Chomping]
[Squeaking]
Marge, can't we get some clear plates?
I can't see the TV!
Is it really necessary to watch TV
while we're eating?
We're getting food all over.
Yoink!
If you really wanted us to be neater,
you'd serve us out of one long bowl.
You're talking about a trough.
We're not going to eat from a trough.
And another thing.
It's only 5:15.
- Why are you in your underwear?
- Hey, this ain't the Ritz.
[Groans] At least let's have
a civilized conversation, shall we?
- Lisa, how was school?
- How was what? What?
- School! School!
- It's not time for school.
I know it's not time-
[Groans]
I'm going into the dining room
to have a conversation.
Anyone who wants to
join me is welcome.
[Marge] Hello, Marge. How's the family?
I don't want to talk about it!
- Mind your own business.
- Keep it down in there, everybody!
Homer, is this the way you
pictured married life?
Yeah, pretty much, except we drove around
in a van solving mysteries.
Well, I pictured cocktail parties
and candlelit dinners. I pictured napkins.
Homer, I want to throw
a dinner party.
Oh, I hate having parties.
The toilet always gets backed up.
I don't care if the sink shoots sludge.
We're having a party.
Man, that is flagrant
false advertising!
[Gasps] It's just not a dinner party
without a melon baller.
And we'll need a citrus zester,
a ravioli crimper.
Ooh, an oyster mallet.
"Made in U.S.A."
[Groans]
No, thank you.
Hey, Lise, check this out.
Nonstick coating.
Ooh. A punch bowl like that
just screams good taste.
Wouldn't it be perfect
for the dinner party?
Oh, we can't afford that.
Who do you think I am, Liz Taylor?
Well, maybe we could use
it once and then return it.
- Marge, we're not talking about a toothbrush here.
- [Groans]
- [Beeps]
- ## [Humming]
Bart, company's coming.
- Go put doilies under the coasters. Hurry! Hurry!
- [Dings]
Lisa, quick!
Screw these back on.
Mom, calm down.
The party's not for another three hours.
Oh, good. That will give me time to
add another coat of glaze to the ham.
[Groans]
- Ohh!
- Homer!
- [Homer] What?
- Are you ready?
Just gotta put my shoes on.
The only thing I asked you to do
for this party was put on clothes...
- and you didn't do it.
- [Doorbell Rings]
And now it's too late!
They're here!
Bart, greet our guests
and take their coats.
Mom, Reverend Lovejoy doesn't
have a coat. Should I let him in?
My coat was stolen
at last week's interfaith banquet.
So I helped myself to a few
of the better umbrellas.
Well, as you can see,
we don't believe fur is murder...
- but paying for it sure is.
- [Laughing]
Uh, sorry we're late.
But Luann had to put on her face.
She doesn't want anyone to know
she's got no eyebrows. What? You don't.
[All Laughing]
[Chattering]
Did anyone see that
new Woodsy Allen movie?
You know, I like his films, except for
that nervous fella's always in 'em.
If you want to talk nervous, you should have
seen Kirk deal with the high school boys...
- who egged our Bonneville.
- Ha! Should have asked them to hurl some bacon.
Then maybe I could have had
a decent breakfast for once.
You know what you two need?
A little comic strip called Love Is.
It's about two naked eight-year-olds
who are married.
Mmm! Well, Marge,
if that was my last meal...
- I'd tell the warden, "Bring on the lethal injection!"
- [Laughing]
Yeah, Marge. I know I haven't eaten
that well since I was in the army.
- Or that noisily.
- All right, that's it.
So, who wants to play
a game? Hmm? Hmm? Hmm?
Oh, that's a noodle-scratcher.
- Oh! Cornstarch!
- Oh, rightio!
It's good for
keeping down the urges.
Oh, come on, Luann.
You know what this is.
Kirk, I don't know what it is.
Oy! It could not be
more simple, Luann.
Do you want me to show this to the cat
and have the cat tell you what it is?
- 'Cause the cat's gonna get it.
- I'm sorry. I'm not as smart as you, Kirk.
We didn't all
go to Gudger College.
- [Dings]
- It's dignity!
Gah! Don't you even know
dignity when you see it?
- Kirk, you're spitting!
- Okay, genius, why don't you draw dignity?
- Oh, that's dignity, all right!
- That's great!
Worthy of Webster's.
Well, it's no wonder I can't draw dignity.
I gave it up when I married her.
Now, Kirk, it's only a game.
Sometimes we-
- Oh, cram it, Churchie!
- Maybe we should all have a few drinks.
I'd have a drink,
but it might loosen my tongue.
You want to talk?
Go ahead, Luann, talk.
Why don't you tell them one of
your little bedtime stories, huh?
Like the one about how rotten
it is to be married to a loser.
Or how about the one about
how I carry a change purse?
- Yeah, a purse!
- Shut up and let the woman talk!
Okay, Kirk, I'll tell a story.
It's about a man whose
father-in-law gave him a sweet job...
- as manager of a cracker factory.
- [Homer] Boring!
A man whose complete lack of business
sense and managerial impotence-
- Ooh! Here we go!
- sent the number one cracker factory in town...
into a tie for sixth with
Table Time and Allied Biscuit.
[Kirk] You want to
hear a secret, everybody?
Luann loves it!
Loves it when I fail!
Oh, yes, Kirk. I love having to
borrow money from my sister.
I love having to steal clothes
from the church donation box.
- Oh, sweetJesus!
- [Groaning]
Lisa, why don't you
come sing for us?
- ## [Singing]
- Oh, great!
You got the kid singing!
I hope you're happy now!
I am not happy.
And I haven't been happy for a long time.
- I want a divorce!
- [All Gasping]
l- l-
A... divorce?
Sure. Divorce.
Hey, you got it, toots!
And here's a picture
even you can figure out!
- It's a door! Use it!
- That's a door?
Hello, I'm Dr Hibbert. I'm afraid
I'm going to have to amputate your butt.
[Imitates Hibbert Laughing]
All right,
if you think you must.
Come on, Milhouse.
We are going.
- Oh, can't I come home later?
- There's not going to be a home later.
Oh, okay. Ta-ta!
I'm off to the beauty salon!
Good night. Thanks for coming.
We'll see you. Bye-bye.
Well, I think that went pretty well.
[Tires Screeching]
What?
I feel terrible.
The Van Houtens split up at our party.
Marge, please.
That was 20 minutes ago.
I shouldn't have served
those North Korean fortune cookies.
They were so insulting-
"You are a coward."
No one likes to hear that
after a nice meal.
You can't keep blaming yourself.
Just blame yourself once and move on.
You know who the real victim
is in all this- Milhouse.
Hey, Van Houten,
I heard your folks broke up.
Aren't you gonna say "Ha-ha"?
Oh, by no means. My dad left my mom
after she got hooked on cough drops.
By the end,
her breath was so fresh...
she wasn't really
my mother anymore.
Oh. So I guess I'm not alone.
Aw, you'll do fine. My divorce was
tough on my kid, but he got over it.
I sleep in a drawer.
## [Singing]
## [Humming]
## [Humming Continues]
I must say, Luann,
you're really handling this splendidly.
From now on, forget everything you
thought you knew about Luann Van Houten.
Actually, Luann, I don't really
know anything about you.
Forget it! She's gone!
Presto change-o!
Kaboom!
Sweet Fanny Adams! Bye-bye!
Uh, singles life is great,
Homer. I can do whatever I want.
- Today I drank a beer in the bathroom.
- The one down the hall?
Yeah. And another great thing-
you get your own bed.
Uh, I sleep in a racing car.
Do you?
I sleep in a big bed with my wife.
- Oh, yeah.
- [Knocking]
- Hey, there, Kirk.
- Oh, boy! What's going on? Patio party?
Nah. A possum drowned in the pool.
You have any garbage bags?
Ah, just throw it over the fence.
Let Arby's worry about it.
That's Jerry. He's a major player
down at the sewing store.
Well, thanks for introducing me.
Ah, don't worry, Homer.
You know me.
And I'm a superstar
at the cracker factory.
[Kirk]
You're letting me go?
Kirk, crackers are a family food.
Happy families.
Maybe single people eat crackers.
We don't know.
Frankly, we don't want to know.
It's a market we can do without.
So that's it after 20 years-
so long, good luck?
I don't recall saying "good luck."
[Imitating Engine]
And the winner
of the Milhouse 500 is Milhouse!
[Luann] Milhouse, are you sure you
want to drive that inside?
- Yes!
- Okay. Be careful, sweet, sweet treasure.
[Doorbell Rings]
God, I missed you, Lulu.
[Giggles]
Chase, it's only been three hours.
- Who's Chase?
- Oh, that's Mom's new boyfriend.
Hey, I know you from American Gladiators.
You're Pyro!
[Laughs]
Only on weekends.
During the week,
I'm just your average workaday stuntman.
- Really?
- Go ahead. Break a chair on me.
- Wow! Thanks.
- Okay, boys, I gotta go. Come on, Lulu. Let's roll.
## [Whistling]
Ow! Ow!
Ow! What the hell
is wrong with you?
Gee! Sorry! It's a pretty
standard stunt, Homer.
- [Marge] Homer, get ready!
- For what?
Remember? Luann and Chase are
taking us out to hear Spalding Gray.
- I don't want to go to that.
- You said you'd do it as a favor to me.
- That doesn't sound like something I'd say.
- Fine. I'll go without you.
- Okay. Love ya!
- [Door Slams Shut]
Homer, I want you to meet
my new special lady. Say hello to Starla.
- [Cigarette Hisses]
- [Gulping]
Can I have the keys to the car, lover?
I feel like changing wigs.
Oh, okay.
Starla's a temp at KZUG, radio 530.
She's gonna help me
launch my singing career.
- [Tires Screeching]
- My car!
Oh, my demo tape!
"Can I Borrow a Feeling?"
[Laughing]
It's your picture on the front.
- Go ahead, Homer. Laugh at me.
- I already did.
[Sighs] You know why
all this happened, don't ya?
'Cause I took my marriage for granted.
You know, in 12 years,
I never once helped out with the housework.
Oh, yeah, you gotta do that.
- I could have at least stayed in shape for her.
- Oh, and for yourself.
I could have taken just a little time to-
to make her feel special.
It can't just be sex.
It can't!
God, I was so self-centered!
No wonder I didn't see it coming.
That's how it is though. One day your wife
is making you your favorite meal...
the next day, you're thawing a hot dog
in a gas station sink.
Oh, that's tough, pal.
But it's never gonna happen to me.
Well, how do you know?
What makes you guys so special?
'Cause Marge and I have one thing
that can never be broken-
a strong marriage built on
a solid foundation of routine.
Marge, I'm home!
Where are you?
Are you okay?
I don't smell dinner.
"Dear Homer." Ahh.
"Sorry you didn't want to join me tonight.
I left you hot dogs for dinner.
They're thawing in the sink."
[Screams]
Hi, Dad.
- You know, there's buns in the cabinet.
- Lisa, wait!
I know you're only eight years old, and I
don't want to put a lot of pressure on you...
but you've got to save my marriage!
Oh, okay?
Can I stay up?
All right.
[Clears Throat] As you know, there's
been a lot of talk about divorce lately.
And I think your mom
might not be happy with me.
You've done a lot of crazy stuff
over the years and she's stood by you.
- Why would she leave you now?
- Because there's lots of stuff
she doesn't know about!
- You mean, like your poker shack
out in the swamp?
- Mm-hmm.
- She knows.
- Oh, I knew this would happen.
Our whole marriage started
off on the wrong foot.
Dearly beloved, we are gathered here in
the sight of God and this casino tojoin-
- Homer.
- and-
- Marge.
- in holy matrimony.
By the power vested in me by the state gaming
commission, I pronounce you man and wife.
Here's $10 worth of chips.
You may kiss the bride.
See? You don't have to spend a lot of money
to have a first-class wedding reception.
[Marge Sighs]
It's getting less and less likely...
you're going to yell "surprise"
and have all my friends jump out.
Levis. Hey, you think that truck
is full of jeans?
You're very lucky to have Mom.
That's your advice?
Go to bed!
- [Footsteps]
- Good morning!
You know, Marge, I was thinking about
how much I enjoy your interests.
So I wandered over to that theater
you went to last night...
and I bought tickets
to their entire season.
Look, "Mostly Madrigal. '"
Uh, that might be good.
Oh! Oh, "A n Evening with
Philip Glass. '"Just an evening?
"Voices of the Elderly, '"
or- Hmm.
Homie, I appreciate this.
But I'd really like to
get some sleep.
Oh, of course, my sweet. I'll just make
some soothing ocean sounds for you.
[Imitates Wind Blowing]
[Imitates Fog Horn]
- [Imitates Bird Squawking]
- Huh?
Arr, Matey!
## [Humming]
Armando, don't you think
you're taking a lot off-
[Screams]
Homer, what are you doing?
I wanted to surprise you
with a kicky summer do.
How many husbands would
do that for their wives?
None! They'd have more
sense than that!
Oh, you're feisty.
I'm gonna give you a Madonna cut.
Homer, I don't need you
around me 24 hours a day!
I'm a grown woman!
I can take care of myself!
Now, would you please just go away?
Oh, I just made things worse.
A few clumsy gestures aren't gonna
make up for 10 years of neglect.
Marge deserves someone
who will treat her right.
Marge deserves a fresh start.
I'd like to file for... divorce.
These things happen.
Eight dollars.
Only three cavities, Bart.
Your best checkup ever.
I'm going to make you my specialty-
butterscotch chicken.
[Homer] Marge, can you come in here?
We need to talk.
Ooh.
- [People] Surprise!
- [Gasps]
- [Chuckles]
- Surprise.
Marge, will you marry me?
Why? Am I pregnant?
No. It's a second wedding, honey.
Our first one was so crummy,
I had to make it up to you. I really love you.
Oh, Homie.
I know you love me.
- We don't need to get married again.
- Yes, we do!
- I got us a divorce this afternoon.
- What?
I didn't want a hokey second
wedding like those ones on TV.
This one is for real. I want our marriage
to be perfect right from the start...
so we don't end up
like Kirk and Luann.
We never will.
- Dearly beloved-
- Wait! I want one last chance to enjoy single life.
[Belches]
Okay, ready.
I will now read the special vows
which Homer has prepared...
for this occasion.
"Do you, Marge, take Homer in richness
and in poorness-" " Poorness" is underlined-
"in impotence and in potence,
in quiet solitude...
or blasting across the alkali flats
in a jet-powered, monkey navigated-"
And it goes on like this.
It doesn't matter.
All I want to know is...
will you make me the luckiest guy
in the world again?
I will.
Oh, Homie,
of course I will.
[Grunting]
Come on, you stupid-There.
By the power vested in me,
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
It's the most perfect wedding
I could ever ask for.
You've even got a hip
rock-and-roll combo.
Okay, everybody, who likes The Doobie Brothers?
'Cause we got one of them.
## [RomanticJazz]
What a wonderful evening.
A magical way for two people
to renew their love.
[Gulping]
Marge is right.
- Uh, I've got something I'd like to say.
- ## [Stops]
Would you guys do a favor
for a guy in love?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
- That's why we're here.
[Kirk]
Uh, hi, everybody. Uh, hi.
- And... hit it!
- ## [Romantic]
Hmm?
## [Singing]
## [Stops]
How about it, Luann?
Will you marry me... again?
- Ooh, no!
- Oh. Well, uh, can I have my shirts back at least?
Okay, you heard the lady.
Why don't you take it outside, all right?
Uh, I'll be back...
pr-probably.
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net