## [Chorus Singing]
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[Beeping]
## [Jazzy Solo]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
## [Singing]
## [Humming]
Mr. Smithers, may we
offer you a ride to work?
[Chuckles]
No, thank you.
## [Humming]
We're from
Globex Corporation.
We'd like to talk to you
about an exciting...
employment opportunity
in our nuclear division.
Flattered but spoken for.
We're prepared to offer you
an impressive salary...
plus health benefits for you
and your life partner.
The answer is no.
What's wrong with this country?
Can't a man walk down the street
without being offered a job?
[Sighs] We'll have to go
to the next-most-senior man at the plant.
Here we are.
Ten years' experience. His name is-
Marge, I got a new job!
It's with Globex Corporation.
I get more money, plus health benefits
for me and my life partner.
- And they'll move us and give us a nice house and-
- Move us?
It's in Cypress Creek,
upstate somewhere.
You took a new job in a strange town
without discussing it with your family?
Of course not.
I wouldn't do that. Why not?
We have roots here, Homer.
We have friends and family
and library cards.
- Bart's lawyer is here.
- But, Marge...
this is a chance for me
to fulfill my lifelong dream.
- What lifelong dream?
- Promise not to laugh?
I always wanted to own
the Dallas Cowboys.
[Laughing]
I'm sorry, Dad.
I just find that very cute.
Homer, I don't want
to leave Springfield.
I've dug myself into
a happy little rut here...
and I'm not about
to hoist myself out of it.
Just bring the rut with ya, honey.
Come on. Take a look.
[Announcer]
Cypress Creek, A Tale of One City.
Uh, let's watch
something else.
Homer, you're trying
to talk us into moving to this place.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Let's watch this.
- [Woman] Look at this place.
- [Police Siren In Distance]
- Somebody ought to build a town that works.
- [Announcer] Somebody did.
It's called Cypress Creek-
a planned community designed for
the workers of the Globex Corporation.
Cypress Creek,
where dreams come true.
[Announcer #2] Your dreams may vary
from those of Globex Corporation...
its subsidiaries
and shareholders.
Well, what do you think of me
and Cypress Creek now, Marge?
It does seem nicer
than Springfield.
Yeah, did you notice how the people
weren't shoving or knocking each other down?
I've never been to a place
like that before. Ow!
Me neither.
Well, we could use
the extra money.
And this house
is falling apart.
All right.
[Cheering]
Oh, wow! Windows!
[Chuckles]
I don't think I could
afford this place.
- [Doorbell Rings]
- Hello. I am not interested in buying the house...
but I would like
to use your rest room...
flip through your magazines,
rearrange your carefully shelved items...
and handle your food products
in an unsanitary manner.
- Ha! Now you know how it feels!
- Thank you. Come again.
We'll never sell
this rotten dump.
Uh, a little help here?
Even if we sell the house, we still don't
come close to paying off the mortgage.
[Both]
Hey!
Uh, Homer, uh, about those things
you borrowed from me over the years-
you know, the TV trays,
the power sander...
the downstairs bathtub-
You gonna be needing those things
in Cypress Creek?
- Yes.
- Oh. Uh-
[Reciting]
Okilly-dokilly-
Okilly-dokilly!
- [Tires Squeal]
- Bye-didilly-eye!
- So long!
- God bless you!
- See ya!
- Good-bye!
- Bye-bye, Homer!
- Take care!
- Adios!
- So long!
- Fare thee well!
- Arr! Bon voyage!
- Toodle-oo!
- Uh, so long!
- Bye-bye!
- Ta-ta!
- Bye, everybody!
- Bye-bye!
- Sayonara, dudes.
- So long!
- [Children] Bye-bye!
- Bye-bye now.
- Bye!
- See ya!
- Bye-bye!
Ha-ha!
I'm gonna miss Springfield.
This town's been
awfully good to us.
- No, it hasn't, Dad. That's why we're leaving.
- Oh, yeah.
So long, Stinktown!
[Tires Squealing]
It says here one of these giant
redwood trees can provide...
enough sawdust to cover an entire day's
worth of vomit at Disneyland.
[All]
Ooh!
Aah!
[All]
Oh!
Ooh!
Here we are.
15201 Maple Systems Road.
[Homer]
Our new home.
[Whistles]
I call this room.
[Knocking]
I am here to welcome you on behalf
of the president of the Globex Corporation.
Me!
Try the papayas.
They're juicy
and full of papain.
Makes you strong like Popeye.
Popeye, papain.
See? Same thing. Same-
Uh, forget it.
How are you? I'm Hank Scorpio.
- Wow, my boss.
- Don't call me that word.
I don't like things that elevate me above
the other people. I'm just like you.
Sure, I come later in the day, I get paid
a lot more and I take longer vacations...
but I don't like the word "boss."
Look at my feet.
- Okay.
- You like those moccasins?
Look in your closet. There's a pair for you.
Don't like 'em? Then neither do I!
Get the hell outta here!
Ha!
- Ever seen a guy say good-bye to a shoe?
- Yes, once.
Mr. Scorpio, this house
is almost too good for us.
I keep expecting to get
the bum's rush.
We don't have bums. If we did, they wouldn't rush.
They'd be allowed to go at their own pace.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm in the middle of a fun run!
See you at work tomorrow,
although I don't really like to call it work.
Whoa-ho-ho.
- [Buzzing]
- Okay, the oven is cleaning itself...
- the auto-vac's on dirt patrol-
- [Beeping]
and Maggie's enjoying
her Swing-A-Majig.
[Electric Motor Humming]
[Whimpering]
I can't believe it.
I've done all my housework,
and it's only 9:30.
Well, better go upstairs
and make sure the beds are still made.
[Tires Squealing]
You will notice,
my new best friend...
that we are pretty
casual around here.
Yes, sir. I will notice that.
Very casual, Mr. Scorpion.
Don't call me Mr. Scorpion.
It's Mr. Scorpio, but don't call me that either.
Call me Hank.
Uh, say, before we continue our tour...
would you mind hanging my coat
up on the wall, please?
Mm-hmm.
Um, uh, let's see.
- Um, uh-
- [Laughs] Relax, Homer.
At Globex, we don't
believe in walls.
- Matter of fact, I didn't even give you my coat.
- Hmm?
Wow.
Having a place like this has
always been my dream, Homer.
- What's your dream?
- Um, to work for you?
[Chuckles] Don't do that.
My butt is for sitting, not for kissing.
Now, you tell me the truth.
What's your real dream? Your real dream!
Um, someday I'd like
to own the Dallas Cowboys.
- I bet people laughed at you
when you told 'em that dream.
- Yeah.
Homer, don't give up. They laughed at me
the first time I wore jeans with a sport coat.
I was the first wealthy man in America
to ever do that. Now they all do it!
- Did you ever hear of Mike Milken?
- Ye- No.
- Hi there.
- Nice to see you.
Now, Homer, these gentlemen here
will be your eyes and your ears...
and should the need arise,
they'll fill in for any other part of your body.
Your job will be to manage
and motivate 'em.
Give 'em the benefit of
your years of experience.
Don't worry.
That won't take long.
The key to motivation is trust.
Let me show you what I mean.
I want you to close your eyes
and fall backwards, and I'll catch you.
That's gonna show you
what trust is all about. Ready?
- All right.
- Three, two-
- [Rings]
- One second. Hello?
- D'oh!
- Oh, my God! A guy's on the floor!
That was a phone call.
Don't chalk that up to mistrust.
Yes? What happened?
When did that happen? How much of it?
Oh, my goodness.
I'll be right up.
Homer, I gotta go upstairs. There's
a problem. Somebody ate part of my lunch.
I'm gonna leave everything to you.
We're on a tight schedule.
You keep them
motivated.
- Are you guys working?
- Yes, sir, Mr. Simpson.
Could you, um,
work any harder than this?
Sure thing, boss.
Hey, call me Homer.
[Children Chattering]
[Making Fart Noises]
[All Laughing]
You got a fresh sound.
It'll play well
at this school.
Hey, Bart, do you have
a best friend yet?
'Cause I've been looking
for someone to boss me around.
- [Door Opens]
- Okay, folks, let's do it to it.
[Chuckles]
Grammar, that is.
Uh, everybody write down this
sentence and circle the nouns.
Bart, as the newest addition to our menagerie,
you have the honors.
Um, uh-
Well, start by readin'
the sentence.
"Two... wentam
and jolly were"-
[Mumbles]
[Makes Fart Noise]
So, you never
learned cursive?
Uh, well, I know hell
and damn and bit-
Cursive handwriting.
Script.
Do you know the multiplication tables?
Long division?
- I know of them.
- Hmm.
You know, Bart, I think you'd profit
from a more remedial environment.
I'm sure you'll feel right
at home in the Leg-Up Program.
[Gasps]
[Groans]
Guess I can't complain.
Everything's perfect here.
So, what are you in for?
I moved here from Canada,
and they think I'm slow, eh?
I fell off the jungle gym,
and when I woke up I was in here.
I start fires.
Okay. Now, everyone take out your
safety pencil and a circle of paper.
This week I hope we can finish
our work on the letter "A."
Let me get this straight.
We're behind the rest of our class...
and we're going to catch up
to them by going slower than they are?
- Cuckoo!
- [All] Cuckoo! Cuckoo! Cuckoo! Cuckoo!
Stop it! Stop it! Warren!
Melvin! Gary! Dot! Gordy!
Look, lady, I'm supposed
to be in the fourth grade.
Sounds to me like someone's got
a case of the "s'pose'das."
[Groans]
Warren!
Wildflowers!
We don't have you in Springfield.
[Chittering]
Hello, Mr. Chipmunk.
You're a northern reticulated chipmunk.
Yes, you are.
You are so reticulated.
- Hi, Mrs. Owl.
- [Hoots]
You're out kind of early.
## [Singing]
[Screeches, Hoots]
[Chattering]
Mr. Scorpio says productivity
is up two percent...
and it's all because
of my motivational techniques...
like doughnuts, and the possibility
of more doughnuts to come.
I knew you'd
do well, Homer.
Sports collectibles!
Wow, a baseball made out of Secretariat!
[Gasps]
Tom Landry's hat! And it's autographed!
"To Berman's Dry Cleaning.
Best wishes, Tom Landry."
- Why don't you buy it?
- I can't buy that.
Only management-type guys with big salaries
like me can afford things like that.
[Gasps]
Guys like me! I'm a guy like me!
All right, team,
it's the fourth quarter.
The Lord gave us the atoms,
and it's up to us to make 'em dance.
Hey, ifTom Landry's hat
doesn't motivate you...
then I should
just quit right now.
I'm sorry.
We're just a little tired, sir.
We've been pushing ourselves
real hard to get the reactor online.
Tired, eh?
What you guys need is hammocks.
Uh, hi, Homer.
What can I do for you?
Sir, I need to know
where I can get some business hammocks.
Hammocks?
My goodness, what an idea.
Why didn't I think of that?
Hammocks!
Homer, there's four places.
There's the Hammock Hut. That's on Third.
- Uh-huh.
- There's Hammocks-R-Us. That's on Third too.
- You got Put-Your-Butt-There.
- Mm-hmm.
- That's on Third. Swing Low, Sweet Chariot.
- Right.
Matter of fact, they're all in the same complex.
It's the hammock complex on Third.
- Oh, the hammock district.
- That's right.
Ready for the linkup,
Mr. Scorpio.
Homer, one second.
I gotta take care of this.
- Very important. Be right back.
- Fine.
Good afternoon,
gentlemen.
This is Scorpio.
I have the doomsday device.
You have 72 hours
to deliver the gold...
or you'll face
the consequences.
And to prove
I'm not bluffing, watch this.
Oh, my God,
the 59th Street bridge!
Maybe it just collapsed
on its own.
We can't take
that chance.
You always say that.
I want to take a chance.
Collapsed on its own?
You, sh-
You have 72 hours.
See ya.
Back to the hammocks,
my friend.
- Yes.
- You know, there's a little place
called Mary Ann's Hammocks.
The nice thing about that place is
Mary Ann gets in the hammock with you.
- [Laughs] I'm just kidding.
- Oh.
- You know who invented the hammock, Homer?
- No.
That's something for you to do.
Find that out.
- Any sugar around here?
- Try in there, Homer.
Hi, Homer. I'm keepin' two
of my fingers crossed...
that you're gonna have that nuclear generator
up to full power by tomorrow.
- Uh, yes, sir. No problemo.
- Good.
By the way, Homer, what's your least
favorite country? Italy or France?
- France.
- [Chuckles] Nobody ever says Italy.
[Motor Whines]
I never noticed
this office before.
Why should you?
It's mine.
- Uh, you have any sugar around here?
- Sugar? Sure.
Here you go.
Sorry it's not in packages.
- Want some cream?
- Uh, no.
## [Singing]
## [Singing Continues]
- Hooray! Everyone's a winner!
- [Groans]
## [Humming]
Oh, the whole forest
is blooming.
[Sneezes]
Excuse me.
Oh, my eyes are burning.
[Sneezing]
[Coughs, Sniffles]
Oh, little chipmunk friend,
I'm allergic to everything.
- [Chitters]
- [Sneezes]
[Sneezing]
Ingenious, isn't it,
Mr. Bont?
Scorpio, you're totally mad.
[Laughs]
I wouldn't point fingers, you jerk.
So, do you
expect me to talk?
I don't expect anything from you except
to die and be a very cheap funeral.
You're gonna die now.
[Grunts]
Stop him!
He's supposed to die!
[Grunts]
- Nice work, Homer! Am I proud of you!
- Well-
When you go home tonight,
there's gonna be another story on your house.
- [Hank] Thank you.
- [Gunfire]
I tackled a loafer
at work today.
Hey, what's with
you sad sacks?
I'm allergic
to everything here.
My nose is so stuffed up, I can't even
taste Mom's delicious boiled celery.
I've been so bored
since we moved here...
I found myself drinking
a glass of wine every day.
I know doctors say you should drink a glass
and a half, but I just can't drink that much.
Well, the Simpson men
are doing fine, right, Bart?
You haven't even gotten
in trouble at school.
I can't get in trouble
at school.
They put me
in the remedial class.
I'm surrounded by arsonists and kids with
mittens pinned to their jackets all year round.
Hey, Dad-
[All]
We wanna go back to Springfield.
What?
We've got it great here.
And for the first time in my life,
I'm actually good at my job.
My team is way ahead of the weather machine
and germ warfare divisions.
[Sighs]
It's up to you, Homer.
Whatever you decide,
that's what we'll do.
[Groans]
[All Shouting]
[Female Electronic Voice]
T- minus one minute 35 seconds.
- Uh, I got a problem, Hank.
- Aw, gee, Homer, could it wait a sec, please?
Well, it's pretty important.
- Say, what's goin' on?
- I'm having a little trouble with the government.
Oh, those jerks-
always walking over the small businessman.
Don't get me started
about the government.
What's the problem?
- Well, my family wants
to move back to Springfield.
- [Screaming]
Let 'em go. You'll stay here with me.
We'll go bowling. What's bothering 'em?
Nothing big.
It's just a lot of little things.
Well, you can't argue
with the little things.
It's the little things
that make up life.
Homer, I'm disappointed, but I think you
need to do what's best for your family.
Well, thanks
for everything, Hank.
[Female Electronic Voice]
T- minus 14 seconds.
- If you need anything, you call me.
- All right. What's the number?
I never had to call my own company.
Someone will tell you upstairs.
But, Homer, on your way out, if you wanna
kill somebody, it would help me a lot.
[All Screaming]
[Laughing]
[Hank]
Hey, Homer, you're missin'out on some fun!
[Explosion]
[Grunts]
Uh-oh.
Sorry.
Let me just get my girlfriend,
and I'll go.
- Hey, Crystal, wake up!
- [Doorbell Rings]
Telegram.
"Project Arcturus couldn't
have succeeded without you.
"This will get you a little
closer to that dream of yours.
"It's not the Dallas Cowboys,
but it's a start.
Drop me a line if you're on the East Coast.
Hank Scorpio."
[Players Chattering]
Aw, the Denver Broncos!
I think owning the Denver Broncos
is pretty good.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Well, explain to me why it isn't.
[Sighs]
You just don't understand football, Marge.
## [Woman Singing]
## [Ends]
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net