## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[Yells]
[Snoring]
- [Wind Howling]
- [Kissing]
[Muttering]
[Kissing, Muttering]
[Wind Howling Continues]
- [Squeaking]
- Hmm?
Pressure dropping, humidity rising
over (0%, increasing wind?
Here we are. Chapter 2.
"So your pressure is dropping."
[Gasps]
Dad, wake up!
- [Muttering] What?
- I think a hurricane is coming!
Oh, Lisa! There's no record
of a hurricane ever hitting Springfield.
Yes, but the records
only go back to 1978...
when the hall of records
was mysteriously blown away.
[Whining]
- What is it, boy? Fire? Earthquake? Hippies?
- [Yipes]
Hurricane! Somehow the animals
are always the first to know.
And the weather service has warned us
to brace ourselves for the onslaught...
of Hurricane Barbara.
And if you think naming a destructive
storm after a woman is sexist...
you obviously have never seen the gals
grabbing for items at a clearance sale.
[Groans] That's true,
but he shouldn't say it.
We better pick up
some supplies.
Stand behind the flaming
garbage cans.
We'll be letting you into the store
70 people at a time.
Let's just beat him up
and take his stuff!
No, no, no!
Do not listen to that man.
Remain calm. You will all have
a chance to be gouged.
- [Relieved Sighing]
- Thank goodness!
- [Crowd Yelling]
- Whoa!
[Chattering]
Oh, there's so little left.
"Creamed Eels"?
"Corn Nog'"?
"Wadded Beef.'"
Mom, let's just grab what we can
and get out ofhere.
This storm
is making people crazy.
The last pineapple!
And plenty ripe too!
But I'm not fruit!
I'm a kid!
- That's what the pumpkin said.
- Hi, Lisa.
We're going to be in a pie!
Sir, for your own safety,
we do advise you to evacuate.
I ain't leaving! I was born
in this nursing home...
and I'll die
in this nursing home!
- Is there any chance of you changing your mind?
- Sure. Let's go.
Well, need some help there?
You know, maybe you folks...
should come over
and hunker in our bunker.
Oh, it'll be fun. We're gonna go through
our old canceled checks...
and receipts
and give ourselves an audit.
- Make sure we don't owe anything extra.
- I'm sure I'd be a third wheel.
Oh, no, siree. We'd be happy
as hens to have you-
I would make it my business
to be a third wheel.
Okilly-dokilly. Ooh!
I better go take down the manger scene.
If babyJesus got loose,
he could really do some damage.
Okay, it's the standard
Grampa drill.
Everybody into the cellar.
- ## [Chorus Singing]
- [Thunderclap]
[Clock Chimes]
- [People Yelling]
- Awesome! So long, suckers!
[Disappointed Sigh]
[All Cheering]
Why don't we do something
to take our minds off the storm?
Ooh, a Rubik's Cube!
Let's all work it together.
Okay, start with
diagonal colors.
[Homer] Use your main finger on
the yellow side and your other finger...
on the orange side,
and turn it.
- My main finger?
- [All Talking At Once]
- You gotta start backwards!
- [Talking Continues]
- Alternate corners.
- One at a time!
Spin the middle side topwise.
Topwise!
Now I remember why I put this
down here in the first place!
- [Electricity Buzzing]
- [Thunderclap]
## [Harmonicas]
## [Harpsichords: Dissonant]
- It's dying down.
- All clear, everyone!
Dad, no! This may just be
the eye of the hurricane.
Relax. Can't you see
how eerily calm it is?
See? I told you it was over.
Hmm.
I don't remember a bowling alley
being there- [Screams]
[Yelling]
[All Yelling]
Dear God,
this is Marge Simpson.
If you stop this hurricane
and save our family...
we will be forever grateful...
and recommend you
to all our friends.
So, if you could find it in
your infinite wisdom to-
Wait!
Listen, everybody.
- The hurricane's over.
- He fell for it! Way to go, Marge!
Remarkable. There doesn't seem
to be any damage at all.
It just goes to show you that everything
will work out if you have faith.
It's all gone.
Everything... gone-diddilly-on.
Maude? Rod? Todd?
I'm right here, Daddy.
Oh, Neddy,
it was terrifying.
I thought I was headed
for the eternal bliss of paradise.
Oh, my gosh!
Look at Rod!
I have a headache!
[Grunting]
Well, sir, everyone's alive. Guess that's
something to be thankful for.
Now, that kind of attitude's
not gonna get your house back.
I'm sure your insurance
will cover the house.
Oh, well, no.
Neddy doesn't believe in insurance.
- He considers it a form of gambling.
- You know, it's kind of funny.
The only thing that survived the storm
were the family tombstones.
- They're all we have left.
- Well, call us if you need anything.
We got new clothes
from the donation bin. I'm a surfer!
Look, Daddy.
Todd is stupid, and I'm with him.
And now Mommy's stupid!
[Laughs]
Looking good, Rod.
Looking good.
[Sighs]
Neddy, I know this has been
a terrible day...
but, by golly,
first thing tomorrow...
we're going to open up
the Leftorium...
and before you know it,
we'll be back on our feet.
Down here at Springfield Mall,
a storm-addled crowd...
- appears to have turned its rage on the Leftorium.
- [Chattering]
Surprisingly, people are
grabbing things with both hands...
suggesting it's not just southpaws
in this rampaging mob.
Ohh!
Start looking in the back. Meantime,
Springfield bowlers will be happy to hear...
that the Bowlarama is back in business
at its new location...
teetering over
the Carter Dixon Tunnel.
- [Pins Crashing]
- [People Cheering]
Reverend Lovejoy...
with all that's, uh,
happened to us today, uh...
you know, l-I kind of
feel likeJob.
Well, aren't you being
a tad melodramatic, Ned?
Also, I believe
Job was right-handed.
But, Reverend, I need to know.
Is God punishing me?
Ooh!
Short answer-
yes, with an "if."
Long answer-
no, with a "but."
If you need additional solace,
by the way...
I've got a copy of something
or other by Art Linkletter in my office.
Even in my darkest hour, I can
turn to the Good Book for- [Groans]
Son of a gun-diddilly-un!
Those gilded edges smart.
Why me, Lord?
Where have I gone wrong?
I've always been nice to people.
I don't drink or dance or swear.
I've even kept kosher
just to be on the safe side.
I've done everything
the Bible says!
Even the stuff that
contradicts the other stuff!
What more could I do?
[Stammering]
I feel like I'm coming apart here.
I want to yell out,
but I just can't...
dang-diddily-do-dang,
do-dang-diddily-darn do it!
l-l-l-
[Sighs]
Ned, Maude, you've got
to go back to your house!
Something incredible
has happened!
Oh, what happened now?
Did the rubble burn down?
No! Come on!
[All]
Yea!
[Gasps]
Oh, they rebuilt our house!
Oh, it's a miracle!
I started making some calls last night,
and before I knew it...
practically all of Springfield
was offering to help.
- Mm-hmm. My pleasure.
- Happy to help.
- Fabulous experience.
- Sure!
Hope you like it, neighbor. We didn't have
the best tools or all the know-how...
but we did have a wheelbarrow
full of love.
And a cement mixer full of hope
and some cement.
Oh, it's wonderful!
l-l- I don't know how
I can possibly repay you.
But if any of you ever need a favor, just
look for the happiest man in Springfield!
No, no, not me, friends.
He's talking about himself.
But thanks for looking!
Mmm.
[All Cheering]
The living room
and dining rooms...
with a lovely flow
for entertaining.
Uh-huh. And- Oh!
Looks like a loose nail.
Eh, one out of 25 ain't bad.
Your beautiful kitchen, Ned,
just as you remember it.
Was that, uh-Was that toilet always
next to the refrigerator?
[Laughs] Ned, you ever try lugging
a toilet up a flight of stairs?
Lisa and I built your room.
But I don't like this clown.
Uh, I wouldn't take it down
if I were you.
It's a load-bearing poster.
[Electricity Buzzing]
Now, this is a room
with electricity...
but it has
too much electricity.
So I don't know.
You might want to wear a hat.
- Uh-huh.
- [Scraping Sound]
Floor feels
a little gritty here.
Yeah. We ran out of floorboards there,
so we painted the dirt.
Pretty clever!
Oh, something is definitely
wrong with this hallway.
Come on in!
It's your master bedroom!
- Ow! My nose!
- Well, I've seen about enough.
So, Flanders, what do you think
of the house that love built?
- Aw, shoot!
- [Sighs]
[Sighs, Blows]
- [Glass Shatters]
- Ohhh!
Now, calm down,
Neddilly-diddilly-diddilly-diddilly-diddilly.
They did their best.
Shodilly-idilly-iddilly-diddilly.
Gotta be nice.
Hostility-diddilly-diddilly-diddilly-
Aw, hell!
Diddily-ding-dong crap!
Can't you morons
do anything right?
[All Gasping]
- Hey!
- Ned, we meant well.
And everyone here
tried their best.
Well, my family and I can't live
in good intentions, Marge!
Oh, your family's out of control,
but we can't blame you...
because you have
good intentions!
- Hey, back off, man!
- Oh, okay, dude!
I wouldn't want you
to have a cow, man!
Here's a catchphrase you better learn
for your adult years:
"Hey, buddy, got a quarter?"
[All Gasping, Chattering]
- I am shocked and appalled.
- Mr. Flanders, with all due respect...
- Bart didn't do anything.
- [Gasps]
Do I hear the sound of butting in?
It's gotta be little Lisa Simpson...
- Springfield's answer to a question no one asked!
- [Laughing]
What do we have here?
The long flabby arm of the law?
The last case you got to the bottom of
was a case of Mallomars!
Mallomars.
Oh, that's going in the act.
Oh, yeah, the clown.
The only one of you buffoons
who doesn't make me laugh.
And as for you, I don't know you,
but I'm sure you're a jerk!
Hey, I've only been here a few minutes.
What's going on?
You ugly, hate-filled man!
Hey- Hey, I may be
ugly and hate-filled, but I've, um-
What was the third thing
you said?
Homer, you are the worst
human being I have ever met.
- Hey, I got off pretty easy.
- [Murmuring]
Neddy, uh, wait.
Where you goin'?
[Car Radio On]
- ## [Man Singing On Radio]
- ## [Humming Along]
- ## [Continues In Hawaiian]
- ## [Gibberish]
I just attacked all my friends
and neighbors just for trying to help me.
- I'd like to commit myself.
- Very well.
Shall I show you to your room,
or would you prefer...
to be dragged off kicking
and screaming?
Ooh, kicking and screaming,
please.
As you wish.
Noooooo!
Flanders? Ned Flanders?
- I'd better call Dr. Foster.
- [Ringing]
Yes. Dr. Foster here.
Ned Flanders? You're sure?
No, no, no.
I'll come right over.
And may God
have mercy on us all.
Darling, there's an emergency
at the hospital.
- Where are my shoes?
- Oh, I think they're in the den.
In the den?
May God have mercy on us all.
- Well, how are you feeling this evening?
- Uh-
Actually, I'm a little chilly.
Can I have another straitjacket?
Of course.
- Thank you. Dr Foster?
- Hmm.
At least your memory's
not crazy.
Now, Ned,
you may remember...
we spent some time
together 30 years ago.
Do you recall what you
were like back then?
- Oh, sure. I was a good little boy.
- Were you?
- Whee, I'm Dick Tracy! Bam!
- [Yelling]
Take that, Prune Face!
Now I'm Prune Face!
- Take that, Dick Tracy! Now I'm Prune Tracy!
- [Groaning]
- Take that, Dick-
- Ned, stop it at once!
- Stop it!
- [Yelling]
I can't believe
I was such a terror.
Well, neither could your parents.
That's why they brought you to me.
Well, I'm afraid young Ned
is unusually aggressive...
- but I can't seem to find a cause for it.
- [Clattering]
Hey! Hey! Get down
from that bookshelf, please!
Most of those books
haven't been discredited yet.
- Would you please tell your son to stop?
- We can't do it, man!
That's discipline.
That's like telling Gene Krupa not to go-
[Imitating Drums]
- [Drums Continues, Imitates Cymbals]
- Hmm.
Lack of discipline.
I'm beginning to see the problem.
We don't believe in rules.
Like, we gave them up when we started
living like freaky beatniks.
You don't believe in rules,
yet you want to control Ned's anger.
Yeah. You've gotta
help us, Doc.
We've tried nothing,
and we're all out of ideas.
Hmm. There is an
experimental therapy...
that might help Ned
contain his anger.
[Dr. Foster] It was known as the University
of Minnesota Spankelogical Protocol.
And that's just about
eight months, mmm, now.
Well, Ned, how do you feel?
I feel... fine.
You don't feel... angry?
Absotively not-arino!
How do you feel about me?
Pretty darn
diddilly-doodilly good!
The only problem with the treatment
was that it worked too well.
You became unable
to express any anger at all.
From that point on,
any time you felt angry...
you could only respond with a string
of nonsensical jabbering.
- Well, I'll be darn-diddilly-arned!
- Yeah, that's the stuff.
You suppressed your rage
for so long...
it finally erupted as
a massive public explosion.
- It sure did-diddilly-id.
- All right, all right.
Just watch it there.
I'm here to help, you know.
Now, I'd like to try something.
Is there any person who makes you
particularly angry?
- [Ringing]
- Y'ello.
Yes!
Mental hospital?
I don't know any Ned Flanders.
The man who lived next door
until his house blew down?
Oh, him!
Mr Simpson? Dr. Foster.
Please come with me.
You folks are free
to roam the grounds.
Just remember, one of
our patients is a cannibal.
Try to guess which one.
I think you'll be pleasantly surprised.
- [Muttering]
- [Man] Everyone outside of this
room is against me!
- I can hear you walking by-
- It stinks! It stinks! It stinks!
Yes, Mr. Sherman.
Everything stinks.
- We want to teach Ned to release
his anger in healthy doses.
- [Chewing Loudly]
We need someone so irritating...
that Ned simply will not be able
to repress his rage.
Homer, can you be
that annoying?
l-What?
Get in the booth.
"Ned Flanders,
I mock your value system.
You also appear foolish
in the eyes of others."
[Laughs] Well, howdy, Homer.
Ooh, thanks for dropping by.
Mmm, he's not responding.
Proceed to level two-
antagonism.
"Past instances in which
I professed to like you were fraudulent."
Oh, well, I'll just have to try harder.
Ooh! Thanks for dropping by.
Aw, he's still repressing.
Maximum hostility factor.
"I engaged in intercourse with
your spouse or significant other."
Now, that's psychiatry!
Huh? Huh?
[Laughs]
Very funny, wise guy.
Aw, that's it.
You just can't insult this guy.
You call him a moron, and he just
sits there grinning moronally.
- Hi, neighbor.
- You know what your problem is, Flanders?
- You're afraid to be human.
- Oh, now, why would I be afraid of that?
Because humans are obnoxious sometimes,
humans hate things.
Well, maybe a few of them do...
back east.
I can't find what Homer's saying.
Did you write that?
Um, did you like it?
Come on, Flanders.
There's got to be something you hate.
- What about mosquito bites?
- Mm-mmm. Sure are fun to scratch.
- Mmm, satisfying.
- What about, uh, fluorescent lights?
Ooh, they hum like angels.
You're never lonely
if you got a fluorescent light.
See? You like everything!
N-No, that's not true.
l-l-l-
I don't like the service
at the post office.
You know, it's all rush, rush,
get you in, get you out.
Then they've got those machines in
the lobby. They're faster. No help there.
You might even say...
I hate the post office.
That and my parents.
Lousy beatniks.
Hey, that felt good.
He just said
he hates his parents.
- Do you know what that means?
- Um, what do you think?
- It means he's cured.
- That's what I said.
- [Woman] There he is!
- [People Cheering]
Thanks, everyone.
I'm all better now.
No more storing up the anger
until I explode.
If any of you does something I don't like,
you are gonna hear about it!
- All right!
- [All Cheering]
Yes, that's very healthy,
Ned.
And if you really tick me off,
I'm gonna run you down with my car.
- Yeah, uh- Um-
- Oh! Oh!
[Laughs]
Ned, you're so crazy.
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net