## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
## [Calliope]
[Bottles Rattling]
- [Moans] Hmm?
- [Rattling Continues]
[Man On TV] And now the thrilling conclusion
of Colonel Dracula Joins the Navy.
- [Man #2] Uh, Colonel?
- [Dracula Shouts]
- [Rattling Continues]
- Hmm?
Lisa, what in the heck
are you doing?
Oh. It's for
myJunior Achievers Club.
We're trying to earn
money by recycling.
Ah, recycling is useless, Lise.
Once the sun burns out,
this planet is doomed.
You're just making sure
we spend our last days using inferior products.
Well, I think it's a great idea.
Mom, Mom! You're mixing
polyethylene with polyurethane.
- Marge!
- Well, I'm sorry!
And you have to cut these up first,
otherwise animals get caught in them.
- Only the stupid ones.
- I could still use more paper.
Hey. I know where
there's lots of paper.
[Chuckling]
Dad, you're not supposed to have fun
recycling. This is serious.
Oh. Okay.
[Sobbing]
[Skinner]
What a load of garbage.
I'm ecstatic.
With the money from this...
- we're within striking distance
of our trip to Albany.
- [Cheering]
Super. Now, let's give a big
Junior Achievers welcome to our guest speaker.
I know he can teach us a lot about business.
Mr. C. Montgomery Burns.
I'll keep it short and sweet.
Family, religion, friendship.
These are the three demons you must slay
if you wish to succeed in business.
When opportunity knocks, you don't want to be
driving to the maternity hospital...
or sitting in
some phony-baloney church.
Or synagogue.
Questions?
Well, uh, I'm gonna take advantage
of this rare opportunity...
even if you children
aren't interested.
Uh, which do you think is more important?
Hard work or stick-to-itiveness?
- Are there any real questions?
- Yes.
Um, does your plant
have a recycling program?
Re-cy-cling?
I'm afraid I'm not familiar with that term,
you adorable little ragamuffin.
Hmm. You never heard of recycling?
It means to reuse things
to conserve our natural resources.
Oh, so Mother Nature needs a favor.
Well, maybe she should have thought of that...
when she was besetting us with droughts
and floods and poison monkeys.
Nature started the fight for survival,
and now she wants to quit because she's losing.
Well, I say hard cheese.
- But nature's not our enemy.
- Well, surely you agree we can do without her.
- No, I don't agree.
- No?
How dare you question Mr. Burns.
I'll handle it, Smithers.
[Chuckles] Shut up, little girl.
If I had spent my life
listening to dismal Doras like you...
I wouldn't be worth
$200 million today.
But according to your most recent biography
you only have $100 million today.
I, uh- l-
[Stutters]
Um, actually, sir...
it's, uh,
considerably less than that.
I, um, have to go.
Monty Burns, everybody.
I've called you all here
because I need some honest answers.
- What is my current financial situation?
- [Both] Great.
- I hear "great."
- All right. Let's have a look at my stock portfolio.
Hmm. Confederated Slave Holdings.
How's that doing?
It's, uh, uh, steady.
I'm sure all your stocks are doing well, sir.
After all, you chose them.
- [All] Mm-hmm.
- Well, let's get out the old
stock ticker and have a look.
[Grunts]
Here's where I stopped checking it last time.
September, 1929.
Oh, no. Oh, no. Oh, no.
Smithers, why didn't you
tell me about this market crash?
Um, well, sir,
it happened 25 years before I was born.
Oh, that's your excuse
for everything.
I've got to do something
to get my money back quickly.
This calls for an aggressive
trading strategy.
- [All] Good idea, sir.
- Take 50% of my money,
and put it in the blue chips-
Transatlantic Zeppelin,
Amalgamated Spats...
Congreve's Inflammable Powders,
U.S. Hay...
and sink the rest into that
up-and-coming Baltimore opera hat company.
That should set things
right again, eh, boys?
- Absolutely. Genius.
- Oh, yes, sir. "A" all the way.
- Can't go wrong with Congreve's.
- [All Clearing Throats]
[Grunting]
A half ton of newspaper,
and all we get is 75 cents?
That won't even cover the gas I used to go to
the store to buy the twine to tie up the bundles.
It sounds like you're
working for your car.
- Simplify, man.
- Oh- [Scoffs]
Sorry, kids. The trip to Albany is off,
and there's to be no more recycling.
[All Groaning]
But we didn't do that badly. We collected
enough paper to save one whole tree.
- [All Sobbing]
- [Ralph] Oh, Mommy, help.
Hmm.
Are you saying my money's all gone?
- [All] Mm-hmm.
- But... I made all the right moves, didn't I?
- [All] Yes.
- Every move a right one.
I see it all now.
You're just a bunch of yes-men.
I was making the wrong moves, and you were
too gutless to tell me. Isn't that right?
- [All] Yes.
- Dead on, sir.
Then I'll fix this myself. Smithers,
take out another mortgage on the plant.
Well, the bank has already
foreclosed on the plant.
- A-And your house, sir.
- But... what will I do?
Well, the first thing you'll have to do
is move out of the bank's house.
- I'll help you pack.
- [Whimpers] Oh.
[Faucet Squeaks]
- Go on. Get out of here.
- [Squawking]
And I'm sure a pro wrestler such as yourself
will appreciate all the closet space, Hitman.
[Sniffs]
Ew. This place has got old man stink.
- Ooh.
- Oh, don't listen to him, sir.
You've got an enchanting musk.
And you wouldn't even be
the only wrestler in the neighborhood.
- The Shrieking Sheik lives just three doors away.
- [Man Shrieking]
[Laughs]
Hey! I'll take it.
Uh, would it be all right
if I kept this portrait?
To remind me of better times.
Why would I want a picture
of a pitiful pencil-neck geek?
[Sighs]
Why indeed.
I'll make sure he forwards
your social security check, sir.
[Burns]
Mmm. Excellent.
Homer! You didn't tell me Mr. Burns
went broke and lost the nuclear power plant!
Now, I can't remember
every little thing that happens in my day.
You told me about
that candy bar you found three times.
- You found a candy bar?
- Oh, yes. Gather round, my son...
and I shall tell you a tale.
I normally don't laugh at
other people's misfortunes...
but on behalf of
the recycling community, ha!
Couldn't happen to anyone
more deserving.
They're not going to
close the plant, are they?
No. The bank put Lenny in charge.
[Clock Ticking]
Uh, attention, everybody.
Uh-
[Sighs]
Oh-Work harder. Bye.
- [Knuckles Crack]
- [Sighs]
Well, sir, I have to get to work.
Lenny's a real bear on tardiness.
Are there any chores I can do?
- [Smashing]
- Uh, no, no. Uh...
you just stay here
and maintain your dignity.
[Door Closes]
[Water Dripping]
Ah. Here's a chance to earn my keep.
I will go out and get these items
from the food jobber.
Grocery store, please.
- I am riding on a bus.
- Hey. Aren't you that guy everybody hates?
Oh, my, no.
I'm Monty Burns.
[Wheels Squeaking]
## [Muzak]
I'm shopping.
Hmm. Cer-
Oh, my. I wonder
which is the cereal for me.
Um- Oh, excuse me. Could you tell me
where I might find the Burns O's?
Sorry, pops.
They don't put nobodies on cereal boxes.
Hmm. Well...
I suppose this one
looks a bit like me.
Oh. Thank you, shoppie. l-
I ventured in to search for milk
when the door snapped shut behind me.
Yeah. Those dairy cases
are death traps.
[Burns]
"Ketchup."
"Catsup."
"Ketchup." "Catsup."
K- K-
Oh, I'm in way over my head.
He's, uh, talking
to the ketchup now.
- Burns is sure acting nutty.
- Maybe going broke and losing
his plant destroyed his brain.
Could you come along with us, sir?
Are you here to solve
my ketchup problem?
Yes. That's right.
Wh-Where are you taking me?
- What's happening?
- Relax. You've gone off your nut...
so we're stuffing you
into an old folks' home.
- Those, uh, store guys
signed the commitment papers.
- But I'm shopping.
[Homer Glugging]
[Sighs]
Here you go, honey.
That's about all the recycling-
[Hiccups] I can handle today.
Dad, if you just drink one more
I'll have a full bag.
Oh, but Daddy doesn't feel so good.
[Groans] There's gotta be
more trash around here somewhere.
Hey. Why don't you try
the old folks' home?
They practically live
in their own filth.
- Thanks, Dad.
- You're welcome, honey.
That's the activity room.
We're not allowed in there.
That's the library.
Not allowed in there either.
And don't even think about
going in the game room.
Egad, man.
How are we supposed to pass the time?
Best bet is to stake yourself out
a good spot at the starin' window.
[Groans]
## [Man Singing]
- ## [Stops]
- Come on, Mr. Burns. Join the fun.
- [Chuckles Nervously] That's the spirit.
- ## [Resumes]
So this is how
the Monty Burns saga ends.
[Sighs]
If I hadn't surrounded myself
with those spineless yes-men.
[Lisa] What do you mean
you don't have anything to recycle?
You must have some
magazines or newspapers.
That voice. That shrill,
disagreeable voice.
It's her!
Sorry. We're not allowed
to read newspapers.
- They angry up the blood.
- You! The troublemaking girl.
My name is Lisa, Mr. Burns.
- Lisa Simpson.
- It doesn't matter what your name is, you idiot.
What I want to know
is will you help me get my money back?
Ha. I'd never help you.
You're the worst man in the world.
Yes. That's the kind
of moxie I'm looking for.
- You're hired.
- No, I'm not.
Sir, I'm so sorry
my grocer committed you.
- We'll never shop there again.
- Not now, Smithers.
I've got an empire to rebuild. And the person
who's going to help me is... that girl.
[Panting]
Please.
No.
- Please.
- No.
[Doorbell Rings]
Sir, we've never met before,
but my name is Mr. Burns...
and I want your daughter
to help make me rich again.
You mean Maggie?
Ah. The baby who shot me.
No. I was referring to your other daughter.
Lisa. You have a guest.
So, uh...
- how's life in the gutter?
- You again?
I've realized the error
of my ways, Lisa.
I need someone
with your integrity to help me.
Please don't refuse
this poor old man.
[Murmurs]
Well, if I did agree to help you...
you could only earn money by doing good,
socially responsible things.
- Nothing evil.
That's exactly the kind of
radical thinking I need. It's a deal.
See that, boy?
Why aren't you making any business deals?
[Whining]
I'll do it this afternoon.
You mean there are
actually people...
who will pay good money for garbage?
Not good money really.
Each can'll get you a nickel.
Oh, don't pooh-pooh a nickel, Lisa.
A nickel will buy you
a steak and kidney pie...
a cup of coffee, a slice of cheesecake
and a newsreel-
with enough change left over
to ride the trolley...
from Battery Park
to the Polo Grounds.
There's a can.
You have to cut these six-pack holders up,
otherwise fish get trapped in them.
I see.
Ha-ha!
My first dollar!
Thanks to you, Lisa-
and our hemp-smoking friend.
Shine on, you crazy diamond.
Sounds like somebody's
living in the past.
Contemporize, man!
Well, Lisa, as my adviser,
you're entitled to 10%.
Oh, I'm not doing this
for the money.
I'm just happy knowing
that future generations...
will enjoy unspoiled median strips
and pristine highway embankments.
There's a can.
[Kent Brockman] And from our
"it's funny when it happens to them" file...
remember millionaire
C. Montgomery Burns...
the man who blocked out our sun, ran over a local
boy and stole Christmas from 1981 to 1985?
Well, guess who's flat broke
and picking up trash for a living.
Please be Flanders.
Please be Flanders. Please be Flanders.
Excuse me, Mr. Burns. Now that you're
completely ruined, how do you feel?
Excellent. I'm on my way
back to the top.
I've turned these cans
into "can do."
Well, you smell terrible.
Good luck to you, sir.
Wow. He went from stinking rich
to just plain stinking.
[All Laughing]
- Good one, Mom.
- Oh, you're so bad, honey.
You guys shouldn't laugh at him.
Mr. Burns has changed. He's different now.
- Yeah. He's broke.
- [Laughing]
- Two in a row!
- [Groans]
Oh, you've really turned my life around
these past few weeks, Lisa.
I've got my own business again,
my beloved employees.
Oh, consarn it.
Uh, come on! Let's pick up the pace,
you neglected old nincompoops.
Mr. Burns, if you want people
to do a good job, you can't bully them.
You have to show them
they're appreciated.
Oh. Capital idea, partner.
People, if we meet
this week's quota...
I'll take you to the most
duck-filled pond you ever sat by.
Oh, hot diggety! That's how they got me
to vote for Lyndon LaRouche.
Wow. Even I didn't know
he was so committed to recycling.
See? I told you
Mr. Burns has changed. See?
- Lisa, nobody likes a gloater. Right, Homie?
- Uh-huh.
See?
[Applause]
Yes. Thank you, everyone.
But... 10% of your applause...
should go to my little
partner, Lisa Simpson.
For, if it were not for her infectious
moralizing, we would not be here today...
to witness the unveiling of...
the Li'I Lisa Recycling Plant.
Oh, ain't that cute?
Makes Li'I Debbie
look like a pile of puke.
Would you like to be the first
to take a tour of the plant, Li'I Lisa?
I'd love to, partner.
The whole plant
is environmentally sound.
It's powered by old newspapers,
the machinery is made entirely of used cans...
and the windows are from
the old liquor bottles we collected.
Hey! I thought I told you
to stop licking my windows.
I know. You told me.
And when I woke up this morning, I said,
"Barney, you're not gonna lick that man's-"
I'm so proud of you, Mr. Burns.
You're getting your fortune back...
and you're doing it without
endangering the planet...
or cozying up to the Aspen crowd.
Oh, hold your accolades
till the end of the tour.
You haven't seen the best part.
I couldn't watch your demonstration
of the fish caught in the plastic rings...
without getting an idea.
Look out over the water.
I figured if one six-pack
holder will catch one fish...
a million sewn together
will catch a million fish.
Watch.
- What's going on?
- [Chuckles]
I call it the Burns Omni-Net.
It sweeps the sea clean.
[Gasps]
Oh, dear God.
I call our product
Li'I Lisa's Patented Animal Slurry.
It's a high-protein feed
for farm animals...
insulation for low-income housing...
a powerful explosive
and a top-notch engine coolant.
And best of all,
it's made from 100% recycled animals.
[Groans]
I think I'm gonna be sick.
Oh, a spoonful of slurry
will cure what ails ya.
Oh! You haven't changed at all!
You're still evil. And when you're trying
to be good, you're even more evil.
I don't understand.
Pigs need food. Engines need coolant.
Dynamiters need dynamite.
I'm supplying it to them at a tidy profit.
And not a single
sea creature was wasted.
- You inspired it all, Li'I Lisa.
- [Gasping]
[Gasps]
Oh!
You-
[Panting]
Stop! Don't recycle! It's murder!
You're helping Mr. Burns!
[Monotone]
But you told us to recycle.
You convinced us it was good.
No. It's evil.
Please! Stop recycling!
[Monotone]
Stop. You can't mix plastic with paper.
[Grunts, Gasps]
Oh! Oh!
[Tires Screech]
[Horns Honking]
[Sobbing]
[Groans]
I can't get the smell of slurry out of my clothes.
Oh, I was a fool to help
that horrible old man.
I hope you learned
your lesson, Lisa.
- Never help anyone.
- [Doorbell Rings]
Simpson, what are you doing here?
Why aren't you at work?
I made a bad mistake and Lenny
sent me home to think about what I did.
But I don't remember what
it was, so I'm watching TV.
Well, Lenny's
reign of terror is over.
Mr. Burns bought the plant back
this morning. And-
Enough chitchat.
I need to see Lisa.
I don't want to
talk to you, Mr. Burns.
Oh, I think you will.
You see, I've just sold
the Li'I Lisa Recycling Plant for $120 million.
- Congratulations.
- Oh, don't congratulate me.
Congratulate Bay State Fish Sticks.
As my adviser,
you're entitled to 10% of the proceeds.
[All Gasp]
Lise, have I told you
lately that I love you?
Wow. I've never seen so much money.
Oh, but I can't accept that,
knowing where it came from.
Can I, Mom?
[Groans] Lisa, you do whatever
your conscience tells you.
[Moans]
[Groans]
Oh, you did the right thing,
sweetheart.
- [Beeping]
- [Laughing]
Well, that's the first case
I've ever seen...
of a man suffering four
simultaneous heart attacks.
I'm sorry, Dad.
It's all right.
I understand.
But we really could have
used that $12,000.
Um, Dad, 10% of $120 million
isn't 12,000.
It's-
- [Rapid Beeping]
- [Woman On P.A.] Code blue. Code blue.
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net