## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[Guffawing]
I hope you enjoyed
my one-man pie fight, kids.
Now it's time for another
"fanschmabulous" episode...
of Itchy and Scratchy.
[Gasps]
[Screams]
- [Screaming]
- [Giggling]
[Sighs]
[Screams]
Kids? Kids?
You're missing
the Itchy and Scratchy Show.
- Don't you like it anymore?
- Sure. We love it.
But how can we watch TV
when it's so beautiful out?
Yeah, Mom. I mean,
we love you and Dad too...
but God knows we don't
need to see you every day.
An occasional hug is all I ask.
Mom! You can hug me
when I'm asleep.
- I do.
- [Screams]
[Krusty Groaning]
Hey, Krusty, you look great.
You get your teeth bleached?
Yeah, it's a new kind of polymer
treatment- Hey, shut up!
You're here 'cause your Itchy and Scratchy
cartoons are stinking up my ratings!
Look at this breakdown
of yesterday's show.
[Muttering]
Kaboom!
What happened here?
Lightning hit the transmitter?
See, that's what I thought at first,
but then- Hey, shut up!
That crater is where your lousy cartoon
crash-landed! It's ratings poison!
But Itchy and Scratchy
is critically acclaimed.
Acclaimed?
[Spits]
I oughta replace it right now
with that Chinese cartoon...
where the robots
turn into blingwads!
But I'm a lazy, lazy man, Roger.
So I'll give you one more chance.
Get out!
Don't come back till you fix
Itchy and Scratchy.
[Woman]
Okay, Mel, you can go in now.
Krusty, I've come to solicit donations
for the Rock 'N' Roll Museum.
And- I'll come back later.
I need to purchase a brassiere. You kids
wait over here in the credit department.
Oh, can't we just wander around
and meet you back here later?
Mmm, okay. Just be careful.
Would you kids
like to come with me?
- Sounds good to me. Let's go.
- Okay. I guess so.
All right, thanks for participating
in our focus group, kids.
Today we're gonna show you
some Itchy and Scratchy cartoons.
- [All Cheering]
- Cool!
We want you to tell us
what you think.
And be honest, because no one
from the show is here spying on you.
- [Man Sneezes]
- Why is that mirror sneezing?
Uh, look, it's just
an old, creaky mirror.
You know, sometimes it sounds
a little like it's sneezing...
or coughing or talking softly.
Now, you each have
a knob in front of you.
- When you like what you see,
turn the knob to the right.
- [Beeps]
- When you don't like what you see, turn it left.
- [Buzzes]
My knob tastes funny.
Please refrain
from tasting the knob.
## [Cartoon Soundtrack]
[Screams, Groans]
- [All Laughing]
- [Knobs Beeping]
[Grunting]
- [Knob Beeping]
- Hey, quit it!
[All Laughing]
They like Itchy.
They like Scratchy.
One kid seems to love the Speedo man.
What more do they want?
Okay, how many of you kids
would like Itchy and Scratchy...
to deal with real-life problems
like the ones you face every day?
- [All Shouting]
- Great idea! Yeah, that's it!
And who would like to see them
do just the opposite-
getting into far-out situations
involving robots and magic powers?
[All Shouting]
So you want a realistic,
down-to-earth show...
that's completely off-the-wall
and swarming with magic robots?
- That's right.
- Yeah, good.
And also you should
win things by watching.
- Huh.
- You kids don't know what you want.
That's why you're still kids-
'cause you're stupid!
Just tell me what's wrong
with the freakin' show!
[Crying]
- [Buzzing]
- Mommy!
Um, excuse me, sir.
The thing is, there's not really anything
wrong with the Itchy and Scratchy Show.
It's as good as ever.
But after so many years...
the characters just can't have
the same impact they once had.
That's it.
That's it, little girl!
You saved Itchy and Scratchy!
Please sign these papers indicating
that you did not save Itchy and Scratchy.
I have figured out
how to rejuvenate the show.
It is so simple, you egghead writers
would've never thought of it.
What we need is...
a new character!
One that today's kids
can relate to!
Are you absolutely sure
that's wise, sir?
I mean, I don't want to sound
pretentious here...
but Itchy and Scratchy
comprise a dramaturgical dyad.
Hey, this ain't art!
It's business!
What do ya got in mind?
Sexy broad? Gangster octopus?
No. No. The animal
chain of command goes...
mouse, cat, dog.
D-O-G.
Uh, a dog?
Isn't that a tad predictable?
In your dreams. We're talking
the original dog from hell.
You mean Cerberus?
We at the network
want a dog with attitude.
He's edgy.
He's in your face.
You've heard the expression
"let's get busy."
Well, this is a dog
who gets "biz-zay."
Consistently and thoroughly.
- So he's proactive, huh?
- Oh, God, yes.
We're talking about
a totally outrageous paradigm.
Excuse me, but
"proactive" and "paradigm"-
aren't these just buzzwords that
dumb people use to sound important?
Not that I'm accusing you
of anything like that.
- I'm fired, aren't I?
- Oh, yes.
The rest of you writers start thinking up
a name for this funky dog.
I don't know. Something
along the lines of, say, Poochie.
- Only more proactive.
- Yeah!
- [Door Slams]
- So, Poochie okay with everybody?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, you know, it's good.
No, no, no.
He was supposed
to have attitude!
Um, wh-wh-what
do you mean exactly?
Oh, you know, attitude!
Attitude! Uh, sunglasses!
Can we put him in more
of a hip-hop context?
Forget context. He's gotta be a surfer.
Give me a nice schmear of surfer.
I feel we should
"rastafy" him by 10% or so.
Hmm. I think he needs
a little more attitude.
- Oh, yeah, bingo! There it is right there!
- Yeah, that works.
- That's it.
- I love it.
Hey, Lise, look. They're adding
a new character to Itchy and Scratchy.
Poochie the Dog?
Adding a new character is often
a desperate attempt to boost low ratings.
Yo, yo.
How's it hangin', everybody?
- Morning, Roy.
- Yeah, hi, Roy.
Hey, they're having open casting
for the voice of Poochie.
You should try out, Dad.
You have a funny voice.
- I do not!
- Haven't you ever listened to
yourself on a tape recorder?
- I prefer to listen to Cheap Trick.
- Well, here. Say something.
Hey, this is Homer Simpson
saying howdy...
to all the girls out there
in radio land.
[Rewinding]
- Hey, this is Homer Simpson saying-
- [Screams]
I don't sound like that, do I?
Oh, I don't like having
such a hilarious voice.
That hilarious voice
could be your ticket to stardom.
Whoa! A talking dog.
[Laughs] What were you guys smokin'
when you came up with that?
We were eating rotisserie chicken.
Can you just read the line, please?
Ruff, ruff. I'm Poochie,
the rockin' dog.
You're perfect! In fact,
you're better than perfect!
Next to you,
perfection is crap!
Ruff, ruff. I'm Poochie,
the rockin' dog.
Hi. I'm Troy McClure. You may
remember me from such cartoons as...
Christmas Ape and Christmas Ape
Goes to Summer Camp.
You're even better than this guy.
- Take a hike, you bum.
- [Groans]
[Clears Throat] Ruff, ruff.
I'm Poochie, the rockin' dog.
Now, that's just bad. You got no attitude,
you're barely outrageous...
and I don't know what you're in,
but it's not my face.
- Next.
- Oh, no attitude, eh? Not in your face, huh?
Well, you can cram it
with walnuts, ugly!
That's it! That's the Poochie attitude!
Do that again.
Huh? I can't. I don't
remember what I did.
Then you don't
get the job. Next.
Oh, I don't get the job, do I?
Well, boo-hoo!
I don't get to be a cartoon dog!
That's it!
You've got the job!
Oh, now I got the job, huh?
Oh, thank you.
Okay, Homer, let's get
a level check on your voice.
She smells sheet smells
by the sheet "shtore."
Wait. Wait.
Let me try it again.
Relax, Homer. You'll do fine.
I'm June Bellamy.
I do the voices
of Itchy and Scratchy.
You? But you're a lady.
[Itchy's Voice]
She's a lady all right.
[Scratchy's Voice]
A beautiful lady.
[Laughing]
Hey, that really is you!
How'd you get to be so good?
Oh, just experience, I suppose.
- I started out as Roadrunner. "Meep."
- You mean "meep-meep"?
No. They only paid me
to say it once.
Then they doubled it up
on the soundtrack. Cheap bastards.
- You folks ready to begin?
- Uh, I guess. Is this episode going on the air live?
No, Homer. Very few cartoons
are broadcast live.
It's a terrible strain
on the animators' wrists.
Hi. Question for Miss Bellamy.
In episode 2F09, when Itchy plays
Scratchy's skeleton like a xylophone...
he strikes the same rib
twice in succession...
yet he produces
two clearly different tones.
I mean, what are we-
to believe that this is some sort of a-
[Chuckles]
a magic xylophone or something?
Boy, I really hope somebody
got fired for that blunder.
- Uh, well, uh-
- I'll field this one. Let me ask you a question.
Why would a man whose shirt
says "genius at work"...
spend all of his time watching
a children's cartoon show?
I withdraw my question.
Uh, excuse me, Mr. Simpson.
On the Itchy and Scratchy
CD-ROM...
is there a way to get out of the dungeon
without using the wizard key?
What the hell are you talking about?
You're a lifesaver, Homer.
I can't deal with these hard-core fans.
[Clears Throat]
Your attention, please.
- Uh, in episode-
- Uh, your attention, please!
Mr. Simpson will now be autographing
8-by-10 glossies of Poochie.
One per customer.
Please form a line.
There will be no cutting.
I'm talking to you, Mr. Cutter.
Pardon me. Look out. Pardon me.
Excuse me. Hot soup.
Hi. Kindly make one out to me...
and three out to my friend
of the same name.
[Marge] I'm so glad you couldjoin us
for Homer's big premiere.
- [Chattering]
- Poochie's based on me.
Is this seat taken, little girl?
- I'm not a girl! Are you blind?
- Yes.
I am stoked, Mr. S.
Shh. Everybody, it's coming on!
Once in a great while, we are privileged
to experience a television event...
so extraordinary, it becomes
part of our shared heritage.
1969-
man walks on the moon.
1971 -
man walks on the moon... again.
Then for a long time,
nothing happened.
Until tonight.
Behold the future of comedy.
Poochie!
[Children Cheering]
## [Singing]
Ah.
Look, Scratchy!
It's our new friend, Poochie!
What's that name again?
I forgot.
## [Rapping]
Ooh, Poochie
is one outrageous dude.
He's totally in my face.
- ## [Electric Guitar]
- Wiggity, wiggity. Word up. Rock on, party.
When are they gonna get
to the fireworks factory? [Whining]
Can somebody tell me what the hell
is going on? Midge, help me out here.
Quiet! You're missing the jokes.
## [Rock]
Catch you on the flip side,
"dudemeisters." Not!
Hey, kids, always recycle...
to the extreme!
- Busted!
- [Tires Screeching]
Ah, that stunk!
Well, what did everybody think?
[All Muttering]
Homer, I can honestly say that was the best
episode of Impy and Chimpy I've ever seen.
Yeah, you should be very proud, Homer.
You, uh, got a beautiful home here.
- [Tires Screeching]
- [Grunts]
So, it was pretty okay, huh?
Mom, can we go to bed
without dinner?
Yes, we can.
- [Door Slamming]
- Well, at least I liked it. Didn't I?
[Thinking] Oh, you don't want
to know what I really think.
Now, look sad and say "d'oh."
D'oh.
I'm the worst Poochie ever.
No, it's not your fault, Dad.
You did fine.
It's just that Poochie was a soulless
by-product of committee thinking.
You can't be cool just by spouting
a bunch of worn-out buzzwords.
- Don't have a cow, Lise.
- Bart's right.
Let's none of us have a cow.
All that matters is that
the fans of the show liked it.
Last night's Itchy and Scratchy
was, without a doubt...
the worst episode ever!
Rest assured that I was
on the Internet within minutes...
registering my disgust
throughout the world.
Hey, I know it wasn't great,
but what right do you have to complain?
As a loyal viewer,
I feel they owe me.
What? They've given you thousands
of hours of entertainment for free.
What could they possibly owe you?
I mean, if anything, you owe them.
Worst episode ever.
It looks like the beginning of the end for
the venerable Itchy and Scratchy program.
For years, TV critics such as
yours truly, Kent Brockman...
have waited impatiently for cracks
to appear in the show's hilarious facade.
Yesterday our prayers
were finally answered...
when Poochie the Dog made
his howlingly unfunny debut.
Far be it from me to gloat
in another's downfall...
but I have a feeling no children
are gonna be crying...
when this puppy is put to sleep.
[Laughing]
[Cries]
What the hell happened?
Well, I'd attribute
the product failure...
to fundamental shifts
in our key demographic...
coupled with the overall
crumminess of Poochie.
[Cries]
Oh, you gotta stop this thing!
[Crying]
Please! I'm gettin' egged on the street!
Do somethin'! Do somethin'!
[Crying Continues]
- [Knocking]
- Uh, hi, Mr. Meyers.
I've been doing some thinking,
and I got some ideas to improve the show.
I got it right here.
Uh, one: Poochie needs to be louder,
angrier and have access to a time machine.
Two: Whenever Poochie's
not on screen...
all the other characters should be asking,
"Where's Poochie?"
- Three-
- Great. Great.
Just leave them right there
on the floor on your way out.
[Chattering]
- [Man] Okay, so, anyway-
- Hmm.
[Chattering Continues]
Listen, guys, we've gotta do
something about Poochie.
[Krusty]
There's only one thing we can do.
Then they said they
were gonna kill Poochie off.
Really?
Oh, how terrible.
Yes, terrible.
It's not your fault, Homer.
It's those lousy writers.
They make me madder
than a, um, yak in heat!
You're right, Marge.
It's not my fault.
I'm not gonna let 'em treat Poochie like dirt
anymore just because he's the new guy.
- Right on, Mr. S.
- Put a sock in it, Roy.
Okay, so here's where Itchy
lunges at Poochie...
with a rusty chain saw.
- Cue sound effects.
- [Chain Saw Sound]
- Rustier!
- [Rustier Sound]
[Itchy's Voice]
Are you prepared to die, Poochie?
No, I am not.
Oh, cut, cut, cut, cut.
Just stick to the script
as written, Homer.
You're supposed to say, " Please cut off
my head. I don't deserve to live."
Never!
[All Gasping, Muttering]
You can't just kill off
a classic TV character.
Poochie could be bigger
than curly fries.
But first he has to
win back the audience.
That's why I'm gonna read these lines
I wrote myself with my own two hands.
Forget it, Homer! We can do this show
without you if we have to.
- But not without me.
- Oh, geez!
Let him try the new lines.
All right. All right.
We'll try them. Action.
[Itchy's Voice] Hi, Poochie. You look
like you've got something to say.
- Do you?
- Yes, I certainly do.
Hello there, Itchy.
I know there's a lot of people who don't
like me and wish I would go away...
and I think we got off on the wrong foot.
I know I can come off a little proactive,
and for that I'm sorry.
But if everyone could find a place in their
hearts for the little dog nobody wanted...
I know we can make 'em laugh...
and cry till we grow old together.
And... cut.
Now, kids, I know you loved
the old Poochie...
but the new one's gonna be
better than 10 Super Bowls!
I don't wanna oversell it.
Judge for yourself.
[Screams]
Well, look who's here.
Hi, Poochie! You look like
you've got something to say.
- Do you?
- Yes, I certainly do.
[Man's Voice]
I have to go now. My planet needs me.
## [Organ]
Wow! Poochie came
from another planet?
Uh, I guess.
Hey, that wasn't supposed to happen!
Those finks double-crossed me!
Poochie's dead!
[Guffawing]
[Cheering]
Well, kids, we all know that sometimes
when cartoon characters die...
they're back again the very next week.
That's why I'm presenting
this sworn affidavit...
that Poochie will never,
ever, ever return!
This document conforms
to all applicable laws and statutes.
[Children Cheering]
- Oh, yeah!
- [TV Switches Off]
Tough break, Dad. I guess people
just weren't ready for Poochie.
- Maybe in a few years.
- Good news, everybody.
I'm movin' into my own apartment
with two sexy ladies.
Oh, then I guess
this is good-bye, Roy.
- Maybe we'll see you in a few years.
- [Clicks Tongue]
Well, I guess I learned my lesson.
The thing is, I lost creative control
of the project.
And I forgot to ask for any money.
Well, live and learn.
## [Instrumental]
Oh!
[Screaming]
[Laughs] It's back to the basics-
classic Itchy and Scratchy.
We should thank our lucky stars
they're still putting on...
a program of this caliber
after so many years.
What else is on?
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net