Spin-off! Is there any word more
thrilling to the human soul?
Hi, I'm Troy McClure.
You may remember me from such TV spin-offs
as Son of Sanford and Son and After Mannix.
I'm here at the Museum
ofTV and Television...
with a real treat
for Simpsons fans, if any...
because tonight we present
The Simpsons Spin-Off Showcase.
- ## [Theme]
- [Applause]
Not long ago, the Fox network approached
the producers of The Simpsons...
with a simple request-
35 new shows to fill a few holes
in their programming lineup.
That's a pretty daunting task.
And the producers weren't up to it.
Instead, they churned out
three Simpsons spin-offs...
transplanting already popular characters
into new locales and situations.
First up, a gritty crime drama...
starring Springfield's
beloved Police Chief Wiggum.
Keep at least one eye open.
'Cause his best friends, the Simpsons,
just might pop in to wish him luck.
Let's us wish him luck too.
Good luck, Wiggum!
## [Theme]
Ah, New Orleans.
The Big Easy.
Sweet Lady Gumbo.
Old... Swampy.
I still don't understand, Clancy.
Why give up your job
as a small-town police chief...
to set up a detective shop
in New Orleans?
Oh, lots of reasons, I suppose.
Got kicked off the force
for one thing.
- For massive corruption.
- For massive- Exactly.
Yeah. As for me, I was born and bred here
on the mean streets of New Orleans.
Oh, sure, I left briefly to take
that principal's job in Springfield.
But, in my heart, I've- I've always
been a small-time hustler.
I know. That's precisely why I hired you
as my legman, Skinny Boy.
I want you to put the word out. Chief Wiggum
is here to clean up this crime dump.
Bleh!
Looks like you've already
got an enemy, Chief.
You know, folks around here
don't much care for law and order types.
Is that right? Well, maybe
they'll change their minds...
once I arrest them
for throwing skulls all over my floor.
Hmm.
Oh, man, what a day.
It's no cakewalk being a single parent...
juggling a career and a family
like so many juggling balls.
- Two, I suppose.
- Daddy, these rubber pants are hot.
You wear 'em
until you learn, Son.
- I guarantee!
- Will you stop saying that?
So, Skinner, who do you figure threw
that skull through my window?
What's the word on the street?
Well, to be honest, Chief,
I haven't lived in New Orleans for 42 years.
Although, uh, according to an article
I read in Parade magazine-
- Mm-hmm.
- a criminal by the name of
"Big Daddy" runs this town.
Big Daddy, eh?
Well, he won't feel so big...
if he messes with
Chief Wiggum, P.I. again.
Which I sincerely doubt he will.
[Snoring]
[Giggling]
Hey! Oh, God!
[Grunting]
Lucky for you this was just a warning gator.
The next one won't be corked.
Listen up, Big Daddy! You don't scare me!
I'm three steps ahead of you!
- [Skinner] Oh, Chief, your boy's been kidnapped.
- Oh, God!
Big Daddy's trademark calling card.
- See? It's right here inside the skull.
- [Rattling]
Looks like we've got our
first case ever, Skinny Boy.
And this time, it's personal.
[Announcer]
Chief Wiggum P.I. will return... right now.
[Rings]
- Who is this?
- It's me, Chief. I'm on the other extension.
Now you listen up, mon ami,
and you listen good, yeah?
The name's Daddy.
Charles Daddy.
Big Daddy! What have you
done with my boy, Daddy?
Ah, the boy is fine, so far.
I taught him to play the spoons.
- [Clinking]
- If you ever want to see that boy again...
I suggest you
leave town today, hear?
- [Dial Tone]
- Huh.
Sounded like some sort of party
going on in the background.
Are there any parties today, Skinner?
Nah, it's not really a party town.
Though, if I remember correctly...
they occasionally hold a function
called Mardi-something.
- [Cheering]
- ## [Jazz]
## [Continues]
- Aah.
- [Sinister Laughing]
- [Screams]
- [Laughing]
Huh?
Well, if it isn't my old friends
from Springfield, the Simpsons!
- What brings you folks to New Orleans?
- Mardi Gras, man.
When The Big Easy calls,
you gotta accept the charges.
Chief Wiggum, I can't wait to hear
about all the exciting, sexy adventures...
you're sure to have
against this colorful backdrop.
Well, golly, I'd love to chat,
but my son's been kidnapped.
You haven't seen him, have you? Caucasian male
between the ages of six and 10, thinning hair.
Over there.
Look, Big Daddy,
it's regular Daddy.
The chief! Ooh,
I suppose I'd best to run!
Lord have mercy,
I wish I weren't so fat.
[Grunting]
Police business!
Hang on, Son.
I'm coming- Ow! Ow!
Gee, my tongue.
[Screaming]
Ha, ha!
Na, na!
## [Whistles] What do you suppose
the rent is on a hideout like that?
Ah, it's not rented, Chief.
It's stolen.
That's the Louisiana Governor's Mansion.
It's been missing for eight months.
[Gasps]
You!
Welcome to ma maison, Chief.
I've been expecting you.
Is that so, Big Daddy? Well, expect this!
The arrest of you by me.
Mes chers,
New Orleans is my town.
Won't nobody gonna mess with me.
I got interests.
And I ain't talking
about stamp collecting.
Though, I do find that
extremely interesting.
Oh, yeah?
Well, that makes two of us.
You know, boys...
- there is an old saying
down on the bayou that, uh-
- Whee!
He's gradually getting away, Chief.
Ah, let him go. I have a feeling
we'll meet again each and every week...
always in more sexy and exciting ways.
Daddy, when I grow up,
I want to be just like you.
Better start eating, kid.
- Start eating?
- [All Laughing]
I didn't mean it that way.
Oh, hi. Welcome back
to our Spin-Off Showcase.
Could The Simpsons ever have maintained
its popularity without Moe the bartender?
Let's hope so, because Moe's
leaving to do his own sitcom.
But don't panic.
He's taking a familiar sidekick with him.
And his best friend Homer might just pop in
to wish him luck. Let's take a peek.
Well-Ahh- I better go.
I got a date with that lady in front of
the drug store who's always yelling things.
She told me she was
washing her hair tonight.
- [Sighs] I'm so desperately lonely.
- [Audience Laughing]
- [Grampa] Oh, quit your
bellyaching, you big loser!
- Wh-Who said that?
I did!
It's me, Abe Simpson!
But you're d-d-d-dead.
I was. But I've come back as
your love testing machine.
- I'm The Love-Matic Grampa!
- [Screams]
## [Singing]
## [Continues]
## [Ends]
Don't be afraid, Moe. I'm here to help you
with your romantic problems.
Hey, I don't need no advice
from no pinball machine.
I'll have you know
I wrote the book on love.
Yeah, All Quiet on
the Western Front.
[Audience Oohs]
- Ah, kiss my dishrag.
- [Audience Laughing]
See? That's your problem.
You're a crab. Ladies like sweet-talkers.
Hey, I'm sweet.
I'm sweeter than Jewish wine.
Then prove it!
I want you to charm...
the next pretty young thing
that walks through that door.
Mmm, greetings!
[Audience Laughing,
Cheering, Applauding]
Son, it's me. I floated up toward heaven
but got lost along the way.
[Gasps]
Dad, is that really you?
Darn tootin', you lousy fink!
You buried me naked and sold my suit
to buy a ping-pong table!
- What kind of a son-
- [Electricity Crackles]
- Call me when you get a karaoke machine.
- [Audience Laughing]
- [Whirs]
- That's the second time he pulled the plug on me.
- [Footsteps Approaching]
- I was just in a car accident. Can I use your phone?
- Uh, using the phone's a four-drink minimum.
- Uh-uh!
What's the matter?
I'm making as nice as I can.
Test lady.
Go ahead, give it a try.
It goes by how clammy your hands are.
Well, I suppose
I could use a laugh after that accident.
[Dinging]
Lovelorn.
You need man.
Moe near now.
Go near Moe.
- What?
- "Go near Moe." I'd say that's
a pretty strong endorsement.
So how about you and me go out sometime?
You know, out back?
- [Imitates Buzzer]
- I mean, uh, out to dinner at
a fancy French restaurant?
- Bing!
- Sounds great.
And if this Love Tester
is as accurate as it looks...
maybe we'll be having
breakfast too.
- [Audience Cheering]
- You did it, Grampa! You really are a love expert!
Dang right.
Fact is, I invented kissing.
It was during World War I, and they were
looking for a new way to spread germs.
[Chattering]
[Audience Laughing]
Sorry, Grampa. But I gotta
stash you in the bathroom...
so Betty won't get wise to us.
- [Whirs]
- This is not the evening I envisioned.
Whoa! She just got here.
Give me some advice, quick.
Uh, you know, just be sweet.
Pour on the honey, you know.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, romantic.
Uh, ain't sunshine pretty? Ain't flowers stupid?
I gotcha.
[Sighs]
I've suffered so long. Why can't I die?
You know what's great about you, Betty,
is you're letting your looks go gracefully.
You're not all hung up on
looking attractive and desirable.
l-It's just so rare and refreshing.
So, Moe, tell me
a little about yourself.
Myself. Uh, geez.
Um, I gotta go to the can again.
- Huh?
- I got the runs.
[Grunting]
Hey, get away from that!
Leave him alone!
- It said I was gay!
- [Audience Laughing]
- You all right, Grampa?
- ## [Singing Slowly]
## [Ends]
Will you quit your clowning?
I need help here.
- [Clanking]
- Ohh!
Tell her her rump's
as big as the queen's...
- and twice as fragrant!
- Okay.
- You are absolutely, positively the dumbest...
- [Audience Laughing]
haunted Love Tester
that I have ever met!
[Gasps]
What is going on in here?
Um, uh, oh, uh,
I might as well come clean with ya.
I ain't too good at talking to women,
and I really wanted to do ya...
so I brought along
the Love Tester to help me.
As you may have guessed, it's inhabited
by the ghost of my friend's dead father.
Why, you conniving, devious...
monstrous, despicable,
sweet little angel.
But, Betty, it you'd just
give me a chance-What?
I can't believe you went to
all that trouble for me.
[Audience Oohing, Whistling]
Ding, ding, ding, ding!
- [Both Laughing]
- [Together] Thanks, Grampa.
Yeah, yeah. Now how's about introducing me
to that cute little pay phone out front?
- [Both Laughing]
- [Audience Laughing, Applauding]
He's horny.
## [Singing]
## [Ends]
Welcome back.
I'm talking with the curator of the museum
ofTV and Television, Mr. John Winslow.
In our final spin-off tonight...
the Simpson family finally gets the chance
to show off the full range of their talents.
Unfortunately, one family member didn't
want that chance and refused to participate.
But thanks to some creative casting,
you won't even notice.
Show us what you got, TV.
Live from Radio City Music Room
in downtown Springfield...
it's The Simpson Family
Smile-Time Variety Hour.
Featuring the Waylon Smithers Dancers...
and the Springfield
Baggy Pants Players.
And now, a family that doesn't know
the meaning of the word "canceled'...
- the Simpsons!
- [Cheering, Applauding]
## [Singing]
Roll call!
Remember me? My name is Marge.
The TV mom whose hair is large.
[Sucking]
Step back, Mom. It's Bart's turn now.
Eat my shorts. Don't have a cow.
I'm Lisa,
peppy, blonde and stunning.
Sophomore prom queen
five years running. Go, Lisa!
Wait a minute! Whoa, whoa!
## [Whistles]
- Stop the music! Where's Dad?
- ## [Stops]
Hmm.
- Here he is!
- I'm hiding from th-th-the ghost!
- Ghost? What ghost?
- B-B-Before the show...
you said we were having
a special "ghost" tonight.
I said we were having a special
"guest" tonight. Mr. Tim Conway!
[Applauding]
- What's a Tim Conway?
- Oh, about a 120 pounds.
[Audience Laughing]
## [Singing]
- ## [Ends]
- [Applauding]
You know, Homer, we've all been busy as
beavers preparing for our very own show.
Marge, have you ever imagined what it
would be like if we really were beavers?
Yes! And it might look
something like this.
- Honey, I'm home!
- [Audience Cheering, Applauding]
Hello, dear.
How was work at the plant?
It's not a plant, Marge, it's a tree.
And I've nearly chewed through it.
Now, remember, my new boss
is coming home for dinner tonight.
I know. And I made
your favorite- "stakes!"
[Audience Groans]
Hey, would you two
close the "dam" door?
- Bart!
- But that's where we live. A dam.
Look, everybody.
Maggie got her first tooth.
- [All Laughing]
- [Audience Ohh's]
Okay. Now,
before my boss comes...
- there's something important you should know.
- [Doorbell Rings]
- In a minute, Homie. I have to get the door.
- But, Marge!
[Gasps]
[Audience Laughing]
Oh, was it something I said?
- Arr! Someone should be keelhauled for that one.
- [Ship's Horn Blows]
I move that the last sketch be stricken from
the record. Now bring in the next offender.
Inflation, trade deficit,
horrible war atrocities.
How are we supposed to do our big musical
number with so many problems in the world?
Well, I know one thing in this world
that's still pure and good.
- Christian love?
- No. Candy!
Sweet, sweet candy!
## [Rock]
## [Singing]
But don't you want to
end world famine?
## [Singing]
Or save the endangered
Alaskan salmon?
## [Singing]
Well, if you won't think
of society's ills...
## [Singing]
at least think of our dentist bills.
## [Rock And Roll]
## [Singing]
## [End]
## [Ends]
Ow!
- ## [New Wave]
- [Singing]
## [Ends]
[Groans]
## [Rock]
## [Singing]
## [Ends]
- [Applause, Cheering]
- [All Panting]
A poem by Hans Moleman.
I think that I shall never see.
My cataracts are blinding me.
- And they thought I stunk.
- [Toots]
Well, it's time to say good night.
I wish our special guest, Tim Conway,
didn't have to leave so soon.
I'm still here. Fox wouldn't spring
for a decent hotel room.
[All Laughing]
[Laughing]
He's just kidding.
We'd like to thank Fox
and the good people at Budget Lodge.
Well, that's all the time we have.
So this is the Simpson family saying,
"As you walk down that road of life"-
- Hitchhike. It's faster.
- [All] Bart!
We're like this all the time.
[Together]
Good night, everybody!
[Cheering, Applauding]
That's it for our
Spin-off Showcase.
But what about the show
that started it all?
How do you keep The Simpsons
fresh and funny after eight long years?
Well, here's what's on tap
for season nine.
Magic powers!
Wedding after wedding after wedding.
And did someone say long-lost triplets?
Sojoin America's favorite TVfamily...
and a tiny green space alien named
Osmodiar that only Homer can see...
on Fox this fall.
It'll be out of this world.
Right, Osmodiar?
Damn straight,
Troy, my man.
[Both]
Good night, America!
- ## [Theme]
- [Applauding, Cheering]
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net