## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[All Gasp]
[Man] Live from Springfield Penitentiary's
fabulous big open area in cell block "D"...
it's the Krusty the Clown Prison Special.
- ## [Country, Upbeat]
- [Prisoners Cheering]
## [Singing]
[All Grumbling]
Hey, hey, I kid.
I kid 'cause I love.
I tell ya, the best folk
in the world are prison folk!
Man, those cons love Krusty.
Inside every hardened criminal
beats the heart of a 10-year-old boy.
And vice versa.
Just remember, Bart. Convicts aren't cool.
They're bad people.
Yeah, maybe so,
but they get the job done.
Hey! Now I know where
my tax dollars are going.
- ## [Rimshot]
- [Chuckles] Huh?
Hey, hey! It's my old
TV sidekick, Sideshow Bob!
Why, I haven't seen you in years!
What have you been doing with yourself, Bob?
Well, Krusty, as you may remember,
after I tried to frame you for armed robbery...
I tried to murder Selma Bouvier.
Let's see. I rigged
the mayoral elections...
I tried to blow up Springfield with
a nuclear device, and I tried to kill you.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
And whenever I could find a spare moment,
I've tried to murder... Bart Simpson.
[Screaming]
- [Door Slamming]
- He said "tried"!
[Groans] Someone should really
go up there and talk to him.
- [Groans]
- [Sighs]
- Homer!
- Ohh, all those stairs.
Oh, you have nothing
to worry about, honey.
Your mother's right, Bart.
Sure, you're the one who ruined
all of Sideshow Bob's criminal schemes.
We're very proud of you,
by the way.
And, sure, he's probably
so insane with rage...
that he'd butcher
you horribly if he could.
But he's safely locked away.
- In a medium-security prison.
- For life!
- Unless he gets out somehow.
- Which is impossible!
Or so you think. Except he's done it
so many times before.
Thanks for trying, guys.
But Sideshow Bob wants me dead.
And Sideshow Bob is
an unstoppable killing machine.
- ## [Organ]
- ## [Singing]
## [Organ Stops]
Well, that was lovely, Robert.
You other cons could benefit
from his shining example.
[All Grumbling]
Really, Reverend, your praise
is gonna get me beaten up.
I'm sorry, Bob, but your transformation
is truly inspiring.
Yes, I'm a good, good man.
You know, it's hard to believe
this model prisoner...
could be the same monstrous fiend
who once ran for mayor.
It's a pleasure to have recommended you
for the work-release program.
Me? I'm touched.
I really am.
But you'll never find anyone willing
to hire a five-time loser like me.
I already have.
Cecil?
Is it really you?
Hello, Brother.
I'm happy to see you.
But it's been 10 years.
We haven't spoken
since the... unpleasantness.
- You mean Arthur Fiedler's wake?
- No, no, no.
I mean our falling out.
Oh, that!
That's ancient history.
Let's make a fresh start.
Come work for me.
But this is wonderful!
You do know I used to have a-
[Clears Throat]
problem with trying
to kill people?
Goodness, I had no idea.
For, you see, I have been on Mars
for the last decade...
in a cave with my eyes shut
and my fingers in my ears.
Touché, Cecil.
I'm aware of your felonious past
but you are still my brother.
And blood is thicker
than bread and water.
You don't have to worry
about me, Brother.
- I'm all murdered out.
- Praise the Lord!
[Crowd Shouting]
Get back in there!
How can you even think
of releasing Sideshow Bob?
He's just faking it to get out of jail!
He's a maniac!
Bob is no maniac.
He explained his reasons
for trying to kill us all.
And I assure you,
they were perfectly sane.
- Oh, you gotta be kidding!
- My friends, please!
I make no secret of my past.
But isn't our system of justice based
on the idea that a man can change?
Uh, have the boys
check into that.
I know I don't deserve another chance.
But this is America.
- And as an American, aren't I entitled to one?
- Probably!
Can't you find it in your hearts
just to let me live and work in peace?
- [Crowd Cheering]
- [Whimpers]
Hi!
Don't you see what you've done?
Sideshow Bob hasn't reformed.
He's pure evil! Oh, if only
you knew what he was thinking!
[Thinking]
I hope they still make that shampoo I like.
Now, make yourself at home.
Perhaps a glass of Bordeaux?
I have the '82 Château Latour
and a rather indifferent Rauzan-Ségla.
I've been in prison, Cecil.
I'll be happy just as long as it doesn't taste
like orange drink fermented under a radiator.
That would be the Latour then.
And God bless Mom and Dad
and Lisa and Maggie.
And please, God,
kill Sideshow Bob.
- Bart, no!
- It's him or me, O Lord!
[Grunts]
You can't ask God to kill someone!
Yeah! You do
your own dirty work.
Well, I suppose I should ask you
what you do if I'm to be working with you.
For me, Bob. For me.
I am Springfield's chief hydrological
and hydrodynamical engineer.
Hydrological and hydrodynamical.
Talk about running the gamut.
- Snigger all you like, Bob.
- Thank you. I believe I shall.
But you'll find one gets more respect
as a humble civil servant...
than as a homicidal maniac
or a clown's sidekick.
Aha! I knew it!
You're still angry that Krusty
picked me instead of you.
- I can't imagine what you mean.
- Oh, come now!
You wanted to be Krusty's sidekick
since you were five!
What about the buffoon lessons?
The four years at clown college?
I'll thank you not to refer
to Princeton that way.
The point is you obviously still blame me
for what happened at your audition.
[Whimpers]
Thanks for driving me,
big brother.
These giant clown mitts are extremely hilarious,
but do make it difficult to shift gears.
That's the title of Erma Bombeck's
latest, isn't it?
Number 73. You're next.
Make with the laugh-laugh.
- ## [Drumroll]
- [Clears Throat]
Hey, children!
Meet me, Sideshow Cecil!
[Krusty Imitating Buzzer]
Next!
Uh, I have prepared
a pie-in-the-face take.
[Groans]
All right.
Knock yourself out, kid. Hal!
Ooh. Ha-ha!
Free comedy tip, slick. The pie gag's
only funny when the sap's got dignity!
Like that guy. Hey, Hal! Pie job
for Lord Autumnbottom there!
Oh, dear.
That guy's a genius!
He's gonna change the way
we think about getting hit by pies!
Chumley, you're hired.
When that pie hit your face, I saw my dreams
explode in a burst of cream and crust.
But I suppose I should thank you.
After all, it led me to my true calling.
Cecil, no civilization
in history has ever considered...
chief hydrological engineer
a calling.
- [Clearing Throat]
- Yes, yes. The Cappadocians. Fine.
There it is. The future site
of the Springfield hydroelectric dam.
Just the thought of that raw, surging power
makes me wonder why the hell I should care.
Because you'll be supervising
the construction crew.
Oh, great.
Whenever a woman passes by...
I suppose it will be my job
to lead the hooting.
Oh, yeah! Shake it, madam.
Capital knockers.
Come on, Bob. This is your chance
to show the people of Springfield...
you can hold down
an honest job.
He's planning something evil,
I know it.
It must have something
to do with the town's water supply.
Maybe he's gonna pee
in the river.
Mmm, nah.
That's not his style.
Who is that?
Why, it's Bart Simpson!
Hello, Bart!
- He's just shy because I've tried
to kill him so many times.
- Ah.
I really must thank you
for this moment of tranquillity, Edna.
You know, I haven't been
on a date in six years.
Oh, the pleasure's mine, Bob.
It's so exciting to be dating a killer.
To be fair, I never
successfully killed anyone.
Oh. I see.
I did once try to kill
the world's greatest lover.
But then I realized
there are laws against suicide.
[Laughing]
- You get my drift.
- Oh, you.
Mrs. Krabappel, no!
That's Sideshow Bob!
Well, that's the last time
I announce my dinner plans in class.
That was Edna Krabappel.
You only get one chance with
Edna Krabappel. I hope you're happy.
I won't be happy until I find out
what you're up to.
Wherever you go and whatever you do,
I'll be there watching and waiting.
He says that, but I bet
he gives up pretty quickly.
Hello, Brother.
All's well I trust?
It most certainly is not!
The workmen you've given me...
don't know their asses from the hole
in the ground they accidentally blew yesterday.
Come now. You speak as if they were
a gaggle of slack-jawed yokels.
Mr. Terwilliger, come quick!
There's trouble down
to the cement mixer, sir!
See, Cousin Merl and me
was playing fetch with Geech.
That's our old smellhound and-
Geech gone to heaven,
Mr. Terwilliger.
Oh, Cousin Merl, really!
Temper, temper. You know
Cousin Merl ain't been quite right lately.
I'm telling you, Cecil,
I can't take much more of this!
Rustic workmen who have turned
the Sanijohn into a smokehouse.
Coveralls that don't quite cover all.
And a psychotic little boy
who will not stop hounding me!
This little boy right here!
Sometimes I wish
this dam would burst...
and bury this cursed town.
Hey! You said
we were going to Dairy Queen.
I lied. Now help me rummage
through Bob's trash for clues.
Then I promise we'll go
to the waterslide.
Okay.
[Screaming]
You again!
Well, that's it.
I'm going to do what
I should have done a long time ago.
[Knocking]
Madam, your children
are no more...
than a pair
of ill-bred troublemakers.
- Lisa too?
- Especially Lisa!
But especially Bart!
If he crosses me one more time,
just once more...
well, I can't be held responsible
for my actions.
Well, I hope Bob fed you
'cause I ate your dinners.
I know it's hard to accept, Bart,
but face it.
Sideshow Bob has changed.
No, he hasn't.
He's more the same than ever.
And I know
where the evidence is.
There's only one place
it could possibly be.
Bob's trailer
at the construction site?
That's even better.
Let's go there.
- What were you thinking?
- The haunted mine.
Blueprints, concrete invoices,
construction schedules.
If I didn't know better,
I'd swear Bob was building a dam.
Oh, yeah?
Then explain this!
[Gasps] Bart, there must be
millions of dollars there.
- What is Sideshow Bob doing with-
- [Doorknob Rattling]
[Growls]
- [Grunting]
- [Both Screaming]
Who left the lights on?
Who's in here? Cletus? Cousin Merl?
Big HungryJoe?
[Bart]
I think he may have spotted us.
[Lisa]
Run!
You two.
Be careful!
There's hydroelectricity in there!
[Bart]
Oops.
Will you children stop
tormenting me!
I've done nothing wrong.
Give it up, Bob.
We found the money.
Where did that come from? I've never
seen that money before in my life.
Then you must have had your eyes
closed when you embezzled it!
I told you,
I'm not a criminal anymore.
You want to know
what I've been up to?
Here's a clue for you, Jack!
One hundred thousand tons
of reinforced concrete.
Oh, my God!
It's completely hollow!
What happened to all
the concrete?
You cut back on building materials
and kept all the money for yourself.
- That's what happened.
- Get him, Lise!
[Shouting]
But I wasn't in charge
of the money. Cecil was.
Now, let's stop bickering
and get out of here.
This dam could collapse
at any minute!
[Cecil]
One minute past sunrise, to be precise.
- Cecil?
- Once I blow up the dam...
there'll be no evidence of missing concrete,
and I walk away with 15 million.
But everyone will know
you did this!
Perhaps. Or perhaps
they'll blame the master criminal.
You know, the one who's been working
at the dam and has a grudge against Springfield.
I know Cousin Merl has had his troubles
with the revenuers, but he's hardly a master-
- Oh. You're referring to me.
- Yes, I'm framing you.
And I'm doing
a really excellent job too.
Wait a minute.
This is all because I got to be Krusty's
sidekick instead of you, isn't it?
Off the record, yes.
But officially, I did it for the money!
Speaking of which,
hand it over.
Ta.
I forgot to mention, I'm planning
to blow up the dam with you inside.
Well, obviously.
[Door Locking]
- Oh, it's hopeless. Utterly, utterly hopeless.
- Oh, I see.
When it's one of my schemes,
you can't foil it fast enough.
But when Cecil
tries to kill you...
"It's hopeless.
Utterly, utterly hopeless."
Well, if you kids aren't going
to foil him, I'll have to do it myself.
Come on! Quickly now!
Bart, for once
I'm not trying to kill you.
I know it's awkward and
I don't like it any more than you do.
But you've got to trust me.
Ah, what the hell.
[All Inhale Deeply]
[All Screaming]
[Coughing]
[Gagging]
- Let's go again! Let's go again!
- No!
Come on, children!
Let's go thwart my brother!
## [Cecil Singing Joyfully]
## [Singing Stops]
Um, do you know
what you're doing?
Lisa, you don't spend 10 years
as a homicidal maniac...
without learning
a few things about dynamite.
Plunger, check.
Hard hat, check.
Fifteen million dollars
and a gun, checkmate.
Good-bye, Bob!
No-o-o!
- Guess who!
- Maris?
[Groaning]
O-O-Oh...
shoot!
- [Bart, Cecil Grunting]
- Bob, look!
At last I'm going to do what Bob
never could- kill Bart Simpson!
By throwing me off a dam? Isn't that
a little crude for a genius like you?
Ooh, I suppose it is. Huh.
If anyone asks, I'll lie.
[Screaming]
[Gasps]
Bart!
[Both Screaming]
- Cecil.
- And now to kill you.
There may be
a slight ringing in your ears.
Fortunately,
you'll be nowhere near them.
I guess this is it.
Thanks, anyway.
You know,
I could snip the wires.
We'd fall to our deaths,
but we'd save the entire town.
Bart, how would you like to
do something incredibly noble?
- Do we have to?
- Yes.
[Both Screaming]
[Screaming Stops,
Both Inhale]
[Screaming Resumes]
[Bob Whimpers]
You-You saved
my life, Bart.
Yeah. I guess this means you can't
ever try to kill me again, huh?
Oh, I don't know about that.
- [Whimpers]
- Joking. Joking.
[Sirens Wailing]
You've brought shame
to this family, Cecil.
Oh, I don't relish having
to write the Christmas letter this year.
Nor I to read it.
You know, Bob, all this time
I thought you were a bungler.
But destroying this city
is far tougher than I thought.
- Here's your man, Chief.
- Cecil? I think not.
This looks like the work
of crazy old Sideshow Bob.
- No, Chief, Bob's innocent. It's the truth.
- The truth, huh?
That sounds like the testimony
of crazy old Lisa Simpson.
But Cecil just voluntarily
confessed, Chief.
That's some good work, Lou.
You'll make sergeant for this.
Uh, I already am sergeant, Chief.
Perhaps you are.
But I say Bob goes back to jail.
But surely-
I mean, I caught Cecil!
Maybe so. But Lou here says
you were resisting arrest.
- No, I didn't, Chief.
- Quiet, Lou...
or I will bust you down to sergeant
so fast it'll make your head spin.
[Chuckles]
Funny, isn't it, Lise?
Those people down there have no idea
how close they came to complete destruction.
Marge, I'm going
to look for the kids!
[Gasps]
[Rumbling]
I think I wet my bed.
But you can't do this!
I saved the children's lives!
- I'm a hero!
- Tell them they'll live to regret this.
You'll live to regret this!
Oh, thanks a lot.
Now I look crazy.
There they go, two criminal geniuses
locked away together.
Who knows what diabolical schemes
they might concoct?
[Both Grunting]
I'm older!
I get the top bunk!
Oh, poppycock! I called it
at the arraignment! Get back!
So, when do they
bring us the menus?
- [Murmuring]
- Shh.
www.tvsubtitles.net