[Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[Chuckling]
Which, if true, means death for us all.
And now, "Kent's People."
Tonight's inspiring story
is about Frank Grimes...
a 35-year-old "Springfieldite" who
has earned everything the hard way...
but never let adversity get him down.
Abandoned by his parents at age four...
Frank never got to go to school.
He spent his childhood years
as a delivery boy...
delivering toys to more fortunate children.
Then, on his 1 (th birthday...
he was blown up in a silo explosion.
During his long recuperation,
he taught himself to hear...
and feel pain again.
As the years passed, he used
his few leisure moments each day...
to study science by mail.
And, last week, Frank Grimes...
the man who had to struggle
for everything he ever got...
received his correspondence school
diploma in nuclear physics-
with a minor in determination.
- [Cawing]
- [Grunting]
That's the kind of man
I need on my team, Smithers-
[Sniffling]
A real scrapper.
A self-made man, like me.
Bring this Grimes fellow to me.
I want to make him
my executive vice president.
Yes, sir.
Smithers, I've just seen
the most heroic dog on television.
He pulled a toddler from
the path of a speeding car...
then pushed a criminal in front of it.
Find this dog. I want to make him
my executive vice president.
Uh, yes, sir.
In the meantime,
here's Frank Grimes.
[Clears Throat]
The self-made man?
What? Oh, yes, that fellow.
Just put him somewhere out of the way.
And find that dog.
Yes, sir.
[Groans]
Chair goes round.
Hey, Homer, you busy?
- Yes.
- There's a new guy at the plant.
Maybe we ought to say hi to him.
I don't know. I'm kind of dizzy.
I should probably go home sick.
Mmm- Hmm.
Mm-hmm.
Mmm... hmm.
- You new?
- Yes. My name is Frank Grimes.
I'm Lenny. This is Carl and Homer.
- I'm Lenny.
- How do you do?
Wow. You've got pencils
with your name on 'em.
Just like a pencil
company executive.
I'd give anything
for one of these.
Any office supply company
can have 'em made up for you.
- Can I have this one?
- No.
- Can... Lenny have it?
Oh, that's my degree
in nuclear physics.
I'm sure you all have one.
Oh, yeah. Carl and I each
have a masters.
Of course, old Homer-
He didn't need a degree.
- Hejust showed up the day they opened the plant.
- [Chuckles]
I didn't even know what
a nuclear "panner" plant was.
Um-
[Chuckles]
Yeah. Well, listen.
I'm sure we all have
a lot of work to do.
- Mm-mmm.
Hey, you seem like a great guy,
so I'll give you a little tip.
If you turn that security camera around...
you can sleep and no one will ever know.
I don't think we're
being paid to sleep.
Oh, yeah. They're always
trying to screw you.
[Groans]
"Marge" is already taken?
- Mmm, how about "Marjorie"?
- [Typing]
- Uh, sorry, ma'am.
- [Groans]
Mmm, how about "Mitzi"?
- [Typing]
- Uh-uh.
Uh, you can have "Nitzi."
- Hmm. "Nitzi."
- I'm out of here.
[Man] Ladies and gentlemen,
our next lot is number 751.
How much am I bid
for Item 751? 7-5-1?
Nothing.
- No bids for item 751?
- A buck.
I have a buck. I have one dollar.
I have one dollar there.
[Babbling]
Do I hear two?
Sold- for a buck.
Cool. What'd I buy?
35 Industry Way.
Looks like my years of hard work
have finally paid off.
[Chomping]
Hiya, stretch.
What's the good word?
My name is Grimes, Simpson, Frank Grimes.
I took the trouble
to learn your name.
The least you can do is learn mine.
[Laughing]
Okay, "Grimey."
- Uh-You're eating my special dietetic lunch.
- Huh?
- Uh- [Clears Throat]
- [Laughs]
Oh, I'm sorry.
The bag was clearly marked.
Please be more careful in the future.
Check.
## [Humming]
Mmm-
[Groans]
Simpson, do you know who chewed my-
[Squeaking]
[Groaning]
- [Chittering]
- Wow.
It's filthy- and it's mine.
[Chuckling]
Whee!
[Groans]
So, how's it going, Grimey?
l-I'd appreciate it if you'd stay
out of my office, Simpson.
[Chuckles]
I wish I had a nickel for every time I heard that.
## [Humming]
[Blows Raspberries]
## [Singing]
So, what's new, Grimey?
- [Alarm Blaring]
- Simpson, you've got a 513.
No, a 513- In your
procedures manual? A 513?
[Alarm Continues]
Look at your control panel.
Oh! A five 13.
I'll handle it.
- [Alarm Stops]
- That got it.
[Whistles]
Hey, Milhouse.
You want a job in my factory?
You don't have a factory.
Hey, I'm a busy man.
You want a job or not?
Okay!
[Chomping]
God, he eats like a pig.
I don't know. Pigs tend to chew.
I'd say he eats more like a duck.
Well, some kind
of farm animal anyway.
And earlier today I saw him
asleep inside a radiation suit.
Can you imagine that?
He was hanging from a coat hook.
[Chuckles]
He had three beers at lunch.
That would make anybody sleepy.
I've never seen him do any work
around here. What is his job?
- Safety inspector.
- That irresponsible oaf?
A man who, by all rights, should have
been killed dozens of times by now?
Uh, 316 times, by my count.
That's the man who's
in charge of our safety?
It boggles the mind.
- It's best not to think about it.
- [Chomping]
Ah! Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah!
You idiot! You nearly drank
a beaker full of sulfuric acid.
Acid, eh? Gee. That would have been stupid.
[Laughs]
Boy, would my face have been red.
Stop laughing, you imbecile.
Don't you realize how close
you just came to killing yourself?
Who did this to my wall?
He did.
- Is this true?
- [Stammering] l-Well-
Technically, it is true, sir, but-
Come with me.
He likes you.
[Dog Barking]
[Burns] How dare you destroy my
valuable wall and spill my priceless acid?
Did you really think you were
going to get away with it?
- [Grimes] I wasn't-
- Silence!
I'm going to give you one more chance-
at a reduced salary.
- So straighten up and fly right.
- But, sir, if I could-
[Dog Barks, Growls]
- Hi, Grimey, old buddy.
- I'm not your buddy, Simpson.
I don't like you.
In fact, I hate you.
Stay the hell away from me-
Because from now on, we're enemies.
Okay.
- Do I have to do anything?
- [Groans]
Oh, I can't believe it.
I got an enemy.
Me-The most beloved man in Springfield.
Aw, it's a weird world, Homer.
As hard as it is to believe, some
people don't care for me neither.
No, I won't accept that.
No, it's true. I got their names
written down right here...
in what I call my, uh, enemies list.
"Jane Fonda, Daniel Schorr,
Jack Anderson"-
Hey! This is Richard Nixon's enemies list.
You just crossed out his name and put yours.
Yeah, okay, gimme that.
Gimme it back.
- "Barney Gumble."
- [Groans]
Oh, what'll I do, Moe?
Why don't you invite him over to dinner-
Turn him from an enemy into a friend?
Then, when he's not expecting it- Bam!
The old fork in the eye.
Do you think it might work
without the fork in the eye?
There's always a first time.
This dinner has to go
absolutely perfect...
if Grimey and me
are going to be friends.
Lisa, be perfect.
- Okay.
- Marge, perfect. Bart, perfect.
Other kid, perfect.
I only have five lobsters. Are you sure
he's not bringing anyone with him?
No. No. He doesn't know
he's coming to dinner.
I didn't think he'd come, so I said I have
something really important to tell him...
- and that I could only tell him about it here.
- [Doorbell Rings]
Oh! It's him! It's him, it's him.
It's him, it's him, it's him...
- it's him, it's him, it's him-
- Calm down, Homer.
Calm down. Answer the door.
[Taking Deep Breaths]
Welcome to the Simpson residence...
or "Casa de Simpson," as I call it.
[Chuckles]
What did you want to see me about,
Simpson? This better be important.
It is, it is, but first let me
introduce you to my family-
My perfect family.
- This is my wife, Marge.
- Hello.
And our beautiful baby.
- My daughter Lisa- I.Q. 156.
- Hi.
- See? And my son Bart.
- [Clicks Tongue]
He owns a factory downtown.
H-How do you do? Homer, I'm late
for my night job at the foundry...
so if you don't mind telling me-
Good heavens! Th-This is a palace!
[Stammering]
H- How in the world can you afford...
to live in a house
like this, Simpson?
I don't know. Don't ask me how
the economy works.
Yeah, but look at the size of this place.
I live in a single room
above a bowling alley...
and below another bowling alley.
- Wow.
- I'm sorry. Isn't that-
Yeah, that's me, all right. And the guy
standing next to me is President Gerald Ford.
And this is when I was on tour
with the Smashing Pumpkins.
Oh! And here's a picture of me
in outer space.
You... went into outer space? You?
Sure. You've never been?
Would you like to see
my Grammy award?
No! I wouldn't. God. I've had
to work hard every day of my life...
and what do I have to show for it?
This briefcase and this haircut.
And what do you have to show for
your lifetime of sloth and ignorance?
- What?
- Everything!
A dream house, two cars,
a beautiful wife...
a son who owns a factory,
fancy clothes and-
[Sniffing]
lobsters for dinner.
And do you deserve any of it? No!
[Gasps]
What are you saying?
[Laughs]
I'm saying...
you're what's wrong
with America, Simpson.
You coast through life,
you do as little as possible...
and you leach off decent,
hard-working people- like me.
[Laughs]
If you lived in any other country in the world...
- you'd have starved to death long ago.
- He's got you there, Dad.
You're a fraud-A total fraud.
It was nice meeting you.
[Door Slams]
[All Groan]
[Milhouse]
Wow! Adding machines.
Industrial waste.
What should we do
with all this stuff, Bart?
I think we both know
the answer to that.
- [Sighs]
- [Pounding]
Get to work!
[Together]
Wacky shack!
Better be careful, Bart.
Look at those warning signs.
- Solve your problem, Milhouse?
- Yep.
[Both Laughing]
Hmm?
Homer? Homer, why aren't you at work?
The car won't start.
I don't feel very good today.
I am at work.
You're afraid to go to work because
Frank Grimes will be there, aren't you?
Well, that's crazy talk.
You're crazy, Marge.
- Get off the road!
- [Honks]
You'll have to face him
sometime, and when you do...
I'm sure he'll be just as anxious
to make up as you are.
- No, he won't. He hates me.
- He doesn't hate you.
He just feels insecure because
you're getting through life so easily...
- and it's been so difficult for him.
- Yeah!
Yeah, that's his problem. He's a nut.
It's not about me being lazy.
It's about him being a crazy nut.
Well, maybe-
But I'll bet he would be less crazy
if you were just a little more...
- mmm, professional in your work.
- [Gasps]
Just a little more.
Then he won't have
any reason to resent you.
I'll do it.
To professionalism.
Good morning, fellow employee.
You'll notice that I am now
a model worker.
We should continue
this conversation later...
during a designated break period.
Sincerely, Homer Simpson.
[Alarm Blaring]
Can you believe that guy?
He's in his office making a pathetic
attempt to look professional.
- Hey, what do you got against Homer anyway?
- Are you kidding?
Does this whole plant
have some disease...
where it can't see that
he's an idiot? Look here.
Accidents have doubled every year
since he became safety inspector.
And meltdowns have tripled.
Has he been fired? No.
Has he been disciplined? No, no.
Aw, everybody makes mistakes.
That's why they put
erasers on pencils.
Yeah, Homer's okay.
Give him a break.
No! Homer is not okay-
And I want everyone
in this plant to realize it.
I would die a happy man
if I could prove to you...
that Homer Simpson has
the intelligence of a six-year-old.
- So. How you doin'?
- [Groans]
Hmm?
Oh, here we go.
Mm-hmm.
Oh!
"Design your own power plant," eh?
This is my chance to show
everyone how professional I am.
Lenny, tell Mr. Burns I'm going
home to work on the contest.
[Snickering]
[Snickering Continues]
Oh, God!
[Power Tool Whining]
[Homer Shouting, Indistinct]
Ow!
[Shouting]
Can I go downstairs
and see what Dad's doing?
I wouldn't bother him, honey.
He's making some kind
of model for a contest.
He says it's really high-tech stuff
that we wouldn't understand.
Marge, do we have any elbow macaroni
and glue-on sparkles?
- [Pounding]
- [Grunting]
- [Whistling]
- Oh, boy! Quittin' time!
Just a minute, Van Houten. Somebody
needs to guard this place tonight...
so it doesn't get trashed.
- How'd you like to be night watchman?
- But I'm sleepy.
Oh, no problemo.
Here's a nickel for the coffee machine.
[Squeaking]
So this is my life.
At least I've done
better than Dad.
[Whistling, Gasps]
Aw, geez!
Milhouse, how could you
let this happen?
You were supposed to be
the night watchman.
I was watching.
I saw the whole thing.
First it started falling over,
and then it fell over.
Wow. I wonder where
all the rats are gonna go.
[Chittering]
[Moe] Okay, everybody tuck
your pants into your socks.
And the bold new ideas these
tiny tykes unveil for us today...
could make thousands
of jobs like yours...
obsolete.
[Scattered Applause]
Our first little genius
is Ralph Wiggum.
[Chuckles]
It's pretty good, sir.
Hot tub, media room-
It's supposed to be a power plant,
not Aunt Beulah's bordello.
Thank you. Get out.
Next.
[Wiggum]
Uh, Ralphie, get off the stage, sweetheart.
Behold-The power plant of the future...
today.
[Groans]
Too cold and sterile.
Where's the heart?
But it really generates power.
It's lighting this room right now.
[Electronic Whine]
You lose. Get off my property.
Let's have the next child.
Look, everybody.
Simpson's in a contest with children.
- Hey, shh!
- You're making us miss the contest.
Could you explain
your model, young man?
- What's to explain? He's an idiot!
- [Lenny] Pipe down!
Well, basically, I just
copied the plant we have now.
- Hmm.
- Then I added some fins to lower wind resistance-
And this racing stripe here,
I feel is pretty sharp.
Agreed. First prize.
- What?
- Way to go, Homer.
- You're number one, Homer.
- But this was a contest for children!
Yeah-And Homer
beat their brains out.
[Cheers, Applause]
I can't stand it any longer.
This whole plant is insane.
Insane, I tell you!
[Stammers, Screams]
[Whimpering]
I can be lazy too. Look at me.
Hi. I'm a worthless employee,
just like Homer Simpson.
Give me a promotion.
Ooh, I eat like a slob,
but nobody minds.
[Chomping]
I'm peeing on the seat.
Give me a raise.
Now I'm returning to work
without washing my hands-
But it doesn't matter,
because I'm Homer Simpson.
I don't need to do my work,
'cause someone else will do it for me.
D'oh, d'oh, d'oh.
- Hey, you okay, Grimey?
- I'm better than okay.
- I'm Homer Simpson.
- [Laughs] You wish.
Oh, hi, Mr. Burns.
I'm the worst worker in the world.
Time to go home to my mansion
and eat my lobster.
What's this?
"Extremely high voltage."
Well, I don't need safety gloves,
because I'm Homer Simp-
Frank Grimes-
or "Grimey," as he liked to be called-
taught us that a man
can triumph over adversity...
and even though Frank's...
agonizing struggle through life
was tragically cut short...
- I am sure he's looking down...
- [Snoring]
from heaven right now-
[Continues, Indistinct]
Change the channel, Marge.
[Mourners Laughing]
That's our Homer.
[Laughter Continues]
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net