## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
[Squeaking, Popping]
[Skinner On P.A.]
And, finally...
the bake sale to raise
money for the car wash...
has been canceled
due to confusion.
Well, that concludes this morning's
announcements. I'm Seymour Skinner.
And stand by
to resume learning in five...
- four, three, two-
- Ugh!
It's hard enough to keep
the kids awake without you, Seymour.
- [Firecrackers Exploding]
- [Kids Screaming]
Mrs. Krabappel, I also have
an announcement to make!
- Can't it wait till I retire?
- Um- [Clears Throat]
I want one and all to
join me in celebrating...
the anniversary of
my portentous birth!
- Here you are, Nelson.
- A birthday party?
[Blows Raspberry]
- Here you are, Nelson!
- [Blows Raspberry]
- I said- [Blows Raspberry]
[Engine Rewing]
All right, men,
get ready to blast off.
Whoo! We're in orbit now!
What's that? A call
from the president? Hello?
[Imitating Richard Nixon]
Uh, yes. Let me just say this about that.
- Okay, Mr. President.
- Bart, this is boring.
[Homer] There's some dangerous
crab grass growing here.
- I guess we could go to Martin's party.
- I don't know.
If we're seen there, it'll definitely
take our social standing down a notch.
- We're what now? Three?
- Three-and-a-half.
We get beat up,
but we get an explanation.
Beautiful colors.
Never has- [Muffled]
Mayday! Mayday!
## [Dixieland]
[Dings]
- Hmm.
- [Snapping]
- Bart!
- [Swallowing] Uh, Mrs. K?
Hey, it's Saturday!
Your powers are useless against me.
Relax. I'm just here to have fun
like everybody else. [Chuckles]
- Don't think of me as a teacher.
- Okay.
- So.
- Mm-hmm?
- [Slurping]
- [Laughing]
Excuse me.
Hmm.
- [Laughing]
- [Crying] Mama!
Hey, Houdini!
Why don't you saw Martin in half?
Oh, I'm not the kind
of magician who does tricks.
- I'm a mathemagician!
- [Groaning]
- Oh, man!
- Now, prepare to marvel at
the mysteries of the universe...
as I make this remainder-
[Speaking In Deep Voice]
disappear. [Chuckling]
But seven goes into 28
four times.
Uh-
This is a magic seven!
[Children Chattering]
- Edna!
- Seymour.
- Mind if I sit down?
- Eh! It's a free country.
- l-I don't follow you.
- Oh! Just sit down, Seymour.
It might be nice to talk
to a grown-up for a change.
Well, this party is certainly
a break in my routine.
You know, normally I spend
my Saturdays...
carefully laying out my clothes
for the following week.
Then I stroll down to the car wash
to see if Gus is there.
Oh, yeah.
You've gotta keep busy.
I collect matchbooks
from glamorous nightclubs.
It's amazing. If you just write
to them and ask them nicely-
- Is this how you imagined your life, Edna?
- Well, yes.
But then I was
a very depressed child.
- To poor decisions.
- Hear! Hear!
- [Guzzling]
- [Woman] Seymour! I told you...
not to play
in the neighbor's yard!
It's a party, Mother.
I was invited.
Well, then I must
have been invited too.
- [Running Footsteps]
- Help me, Edna.
I know where we can
hole up for a while.
[Crying]
That's it!
Looking good. Getting warm.
[Groans]
I feel queasy.
Don't stop, Milhouse.
You're so close!
I gotta barf!
[Retches]
Where's the bathroom?
- [Vomiting]
- [Children Shrieking]
[Moaning, Groaning]
Oh, my tummy!
I told you we should've served cake
instead of oysters!
I'm ruined!
[Grunts]
Ha-ha-
[Groans]
[Siren Blaring]
[Moaning, Whimpering]
Bart, how come
you're not sick?
Eh, I gave my oysters to the cat.
[Retching]
Hey, why'd you eat 'em?
I thought you were a vegetarian.
[Softly] I didn't.
I just wanted to leave.
- More tea, Edna?
- What kind of little boy has a tea set?
[Chuckles] I think we both know
the answer to that.
- A lucky boy!
- [Chuckles] You know, Seymour...
there's an innocence about you
that can be quite charming.
Oh! Well, I've always
admired your tart honesty...
and ability to be personally offended
by broad social trends.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm. Very much.
- And your laugh.
- You mean, "Ha"?
Mm-hmm. That's the one
that makes me feel-
[Groaning]
Hoo, boy!
[Sneezes]
You have a breath mint I could borrow?
- I've got some menthol cigarettes.
- Oh, the heck with it!
Mm.
[Kissing]
[Whimpers]
## [Romantic Strings]
[Bart] You are never gonna guess what
I saw at Martin's party after you guys left!
- You know that playhouse? Well, l-
- Good gravy!
Oh, thank you.
It's just brown and water.
So I looked in the window and there it was-
the grossest sight I have ever-
[Skinner] Bart Simpson, report
to the principal's office immediately!
Now, Bart, son...
I don't know what you think you saw,
but let me assure you-
What Seymour- Oh! What Principal Skinner
means to say, Bart...
is that sometimes a little boy's
imagination can run away with him.
That's the best you can do?
You could've at least said you were giving
her C.P.R., or rehearsing a play.
Is it too late to say that?
- Mm-hmm.
- [Clears Throat]
We're just a little concerned.
If people were to find out...
the principal was dating a teacher,
they might see it as a conflict of interest.
[Chuckling] There are those who might
use it against us for their own advantage.
- Like me, for one.
- Like you, for-
Bart, if life has taught me one lesson
repeatedly, it's to know when I'm beaten.
Let's talk deal.
[Grunts]
As you know, Bart,
your permanent record will one day...
disqualify you from all but
the hottest and noisiest jobs.
What do you say, son?
You keep our secret...
and some other student can inherit
your gloomy, windblown future.
Deal.
This is a great day
for forbidden love.
Mmm, this dessert is exquisite.
What do you call it?
- Applesauce.
- [Laughs] Of course.
I'm sorry, I don't get out
to restaurants much.
That's okay.
I don't entertain much.
Usually, it's just soup for one,
salad for one, wine for three.
[Laughs]
You know, I always thought...
I'd fall for a woman
just like Mother.
Even though I didn't want to.
And now that I haven't...
I've discovered what
true happiness can be, Edna.
Seymour, swallow that
applesauce and kiss me!
I'm afraid I already swallowed it
while you were talking.
- [Kissing]
- [Spoon Clatters]
Good morning, students.
Way to go there, Wendell!
There's Ralph.
He knows the score!
Jimbo, how's that hat today?
Janie, Janie, Bo-phaney!
"The only way to survive
a deadly blaze is-"
Oh, heck! Life's too short for fire safety.
Let's go outside and pick wildflowers.
[Cheering]
[Skinner On P.A.] Bart Simpson
to the principal's office, posthaste.
## [Humming Classical]
Bart! So good to see you.
I have a little favor to ask you.
I'd like you to give this note to Edna
when you get back to class.
I don't think I have to tell you
it's for her eyes only.
"Dear Edna, I want to-"
[Mumbling]
[Skinner]
I hear reading!
[Neon Tubes Buzzing]
[Chattering]
- Do you think anyone saw us?
- No.
It went just as we planned.
- Except they confiscated
my thermos of cola at the door.
- Ohh-
- Skinner! Krabappel!
- [Gasps]
- What are you two doing here?
- Superintendent Chalmers!
Uh, why, we're-we're on a, uh,
a-a what do you call it? Field trip!
- With a student!
- [Skinner] Yes! He's, uh-
He's purchasing
refreshments in the lobby!
I'll go get him right now.
[Hoarsely] Car keys! Car keys! Car keys!
[Drowsily]
Stop pushing me! What's going on?
Just enjoy the movie.
It has Tom Berenger.
## [Movie Theme]
- [Car Door Slamming]
- You think they actually filmed this in Atlanta?
- I don't know. I don't think it's important.
- Yeah.
[Beeping]
Mother doesn't
approve of me dating.
So, I need you to keep
her busy for a few hours...
while Edna and I sneak out.
- [Door Slams]
- Oh, I can't take much more of this!
I collect pictures of cakes
that I clip out of the magazines.
It all started in 1941, when Good
Housekeeping featured a photo of a lovely cake.
You wouldn't happen to have
any real cakes around here, would you?
Oh, my, no! I don't care for cake.
Too sweet.
Now, this is called
a Lady Baltimore cake.
At my age, I don't have
much saliva left...
so you'll have to lick my thumb
before I can turn the page.
Oh. Can't I just turn
the page for you?
No! But you can pick out any picture
you want to take home with you.
- Okay. That one.
- No!
- Ow!
- You can't have that one! That's a coconut cake!
[Pencils Scratching Paper]
Bart Simpson! How many times
do I have to tell you, no talking?
Report to the principal's office!
- But-but- I wasn't-
- And here. Take this with you.
- [Groans]
- Mrs. Krabappel...
- Bart has something he wants to say to you.
- I won't say it!
- Bart!
- Oh! [Gagging, Swallowing]
- I love you, Edna Krabappel.
- [Laughing]
- Bart's gonna marry the teacher!
- Where are you registered, Simpson?
- [Groans]
- Thank you, Bart. That was very sweet.
You may sit down now.
They're not gonna
get away with this.
I'm going to step out for a few minutes,
class. Martin, you're in charge.
Now, Bart, uh-
[Coughs]
you must promise not
to fall in love with me.
[Students Laughing]
Now Martin's scoring off me.
Oh, that is it!
Listen up, everybody! Follow me!
[Sherri And Terri]
What's going on, huh?
What's happening, Simpson?
Where are we going anyway?
Okay, crew.
Set your faces to stunned.
[Children Gasping]
Um-
Um- School dismissed!
And then Bart opened the door, and Principal
Skinner and Mrs. Krabappel were kissing!
- [Gasping]
- And swearing!
Father! Uncle Apu! A teacher was
in the closet with the principal.
And he had as many arms as Vishnu.
And they were all very busy.
- [Both Gasping]
- Wow.
I was in the library at the time.
ButJanie told me that Principal Skinner
and Bart's teacher, Mrs. What's-Her-Name?
- Krabappel?
- Yeah, Krabappel.
They were naked in the closet together.
- [Gasps] Oh, my goodness!
- Wait a minute.
Bart's teacher is named Krabappel?
I've been calling her Crandall.
Why didn't someone tell me?
Oh, I've been making an idiot out of myself!
Mrs. Krabappel and Principal Skinner
were in the closet making babies.
[Chuckling] And I saw one of the babies.
And the baby looked at me.
The baby looked at you? Sarah,
get me Superintendent Chalmers.
- [Keypad Beeping]
- Thank you, Sarah.
- Skinner!
- Uh- Superintendent Chalmers!
The whole town's in an uproar
about your sleazy shenanigans!
Now, I'm going to give you a choice. You can
give up this tawdry, fulfilling relationship...
or you two will be out of here
so fast your mortarboards will spin!
- And where is your mortarboard anyway?
- [Groans]
Right here, sir.
So, what'll it be, Seymour?
Well, I'm sorry.
But I can't give up the woman I love.
Well, then I'm afraid
you leave me no choice.
I want you out of
the building by 3:00.
You're fired. Edna too.
[Gasps]
It's going to be hard to say good-bye to
all of you. We've had a lot of fun together.
Nelson, Nelson, Nelson. How many kids
have you beaten up this year?
- I don't know, 50?
- Ah, 50.
Where does the time go?
You wanted to see me,
Principal Skinner?
Mm-mmm.
It's Mr. Skinner now.
I'm just a man.
Bart, I want to apologize...
for the awkward position
Edna and I put you in.
Your-Your help
made our love possible.
I don't know what
we'll do without you.
Now, so long.
Wait! You don't have to leave just because
Superintendent Chalmers told you to.
- What are you getting at?
- You've spent your whole life following orders.
From your mother, the army,
Superintendent Chalmers.
Just this once, man,
stand up for yourself.
- Okay, Bart.
- Let's go, Seymour.
Okay, Edna. l- No, wait.
We're not going anywhere! I'm gonna do what
Bart should've told me to do a long time ago!
[Filtered]
Attention, Springfield.
We have barricaded
ourselves in the school...
and are not coming down
until our demands are met.
Willie hears ya.
Willie don't care.
Obviously, you two have no experience
causing a scene.
- [Keypad Beeping]
- I'll be right there.
All right, people, we've got an escaped
octopus on the roof of Springfield Elementary.
- Let's roll! Two cameras!
- [Woman] Let's go! Come on! Come on!
So, once again, I've been had.
But an even more interesting story has
developed high atop this two-story school.
A love story.
Skinner, get off of my school!
No. You get off of my school.
Homer, Bart's up there!
Give me that! [Over Bullhorn]
Bart, this is your father!
Do you know where the remote is?
I looked all over the house.
[Shouting]
Did you check your pocket?
[Bullhorn] It was-
[Turns Off Bullhorn] It was in my pocket.
"Fine. Stay in the school.
We don't want you to come out."
- [Bart] You got it.
- Damn!
All right, boys.
Roll up the sound truck.
- We'll blast them out with music.
- [Brakes Hissing]
- [Feedback Squealing]
- ## [Piano]
## [Big Band]
Oh, Edna, I hope
this siege never ends.
Seymour, you're heaven
in Hush Puppies.
[Groaning]
Turn the music off!
Ha! It's working
like a charm, boys.
Now, cut the power and
hit 'em with the lights!
- [Relays Clicking]
- ## [Continues]
[Groaning]
Ugh!
- [Ringing]
- [Grunting]
- I'll get it.
- [Rings]
- Talk to me.
- You have got to end this thing, Seymour.
We're not coming down until
our jobs are reinstated...
and you acknowledge
and celebrate our love.
No one would like
to celebrate your love more than I.
But I am a public servant, and not permitted
to use my own judgment in any way.
Then let us take our case directly
to the townspeople.
Oh, yeah.
That'll be real productive.
Who do you want to talk to first?
The guy in the bumblebee suit...
or the one with the bone
through his hair?
My opinions are as valid
as the next man's!
- Yeah, all right. Just come on down.
- [Beeps]
Well, this is it.
- What are you going to do?
- I'm going to go out there...
and tell every man, woman and child
that I love Edna Krabappel!
Well, that's nice. But first you gotta grab
their attention. And I think I know how.
I have a bomb!
[All Gasping]
Hey, wait a minute!
Those are hot dogs! Armour Hot Dogs!
What kind of man
wears Armour Hot Dogs?
It was a good idea, Bart.
But it's just not working.
Just speak from
the heart, Seymour.
Tell them how we brought
a little happiness into each other's lives.
Ask them why they're forcing
two dedicated people...
to choose between their
careers and their hearts!
Excuse me, Edna. I don't think
we're talking about love here.
We're talking about S-E-X
in front of the C-H-l-L-D-R-E-N.
Sex Cauldron? I thought
they closed that place down!
What are you people
talking about?
My child told me you two were
having sex in the school janitor's closet.
- You know, making babies!
- Yes! Illicit sex!
Doing "it!" "It!" "It!"
Sordid, public,
sexual congress!
This is absurd! I did not have
relations in that closet!
And the fact is, I haven't-
[Gasps]
Uh-
Yes?
Seymour, I think
you'd better tell them.
It's the only way
to clear our names.
[Clicks Tongue, Exhales]
Well, everyone...
the fact is, I haven't
ever had relations.
I am a virgin.
- Ha-ha!
- [Muttering]
- Hey! Does this mean that
Mrs. Krabappel is a virgin too?
- [Nelson] Ha!
Well, Seymour, it's clear
you've been falsely accused...
because no one, anywhere, ever...
would pretend to be
a 44-year-old virgin.
Oh, that's for sure!
I'm inclined to agree.
Ach! I'll never look
at him the same again.
That was more than
I wanted to know.
[Clearing Throat]
Okay, well, um-
Edna, Seymour, in light
of these, uh, revelations...
I suppose we overreacted.
- Do we have our jobs back?
- What? Oh, yes, yes, yes. Sure.
Just, uh, you know, keep
the lewdness to a minimum.
[Whispering, Indistinct]
I'm outta here!
Skinny, Crabby, catch you later.
Uh, hold on, Bart.
May we have a word with you?
We want to thank you for helping us
through a difficult period.
Oh! No problemo. So, I guess now you'll be
getting married or something, huh?
Well, actually, Seymour and I
have decided to break up.
- Huh?
- We can't continue on like this...
trying to build a private relationship
in public-
the whole town watching our every move
with a fine-tooth comb-
Mm-hmm. I'm used to humiliation.
But not in front of a crowd that size.
Oh, but you seemed
like such a good couple.
Bart, when you get a little older...
you're going to learn that
sometimes romances don't turn out...
exactly the way
you'd like them to.
Hmm.
That's why I love
elementary school, Edna.
The children believe
anything you tell them.
[Laughing]
[Both Laughing]
- [Champagne Cork Pops]
- [Edna] Whoo! Oh, Seymour!
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net