## [Chorus Singing]
[Tires Screeching]
D'oh!
[Screams]
Hmm?
## [Itchy And Scratchy Show Theme]
[Together]
Dad! V-chip, v-chip!
- Sorry, sorry, my fault.
- ## [Resumes]
[Sniffles]
Oh!
[Screams]
[Announcer] We interrupt this cartoon
for a special report.
[Gasps]
Someone found my keys!
Kent Brockman at
the Action News desk.
A massive tanker has run aground
on the central coastline...
spilling millions of gallons
of oil on Baby Seal Beach.
[Gasps]
Oh, no!
It'll be okay, honey.
There's lots more oil where that came from.
Preliminary reports indicated
the ship's captain was drunk at the helm.
Those reports were
later confirmed.
Arr!
I'm in a lot of trouble now.
Hey, I'll give you a hundred
bucks to take the blame.
A cleanup effort is already
under way, and, as always...
the first to pitch in
are those unsung heroes...
Hollywood movie stars.
[Barking]
This isn't about publicity.
This is about
cleaning off gunk.
As a Golden Globe nominee,
I just think it's our duty...
to make the real globe
a little more golden.
[Peeping]
[Lisa]
We'd be doing our part for the environment.
Plus, we'd get to clean up
all those cute animals.
Honey, we don't need to drive
400 miles to clean animals.
You can stay right here
and give the dog a bath...
or trim the cat's nails.
Oh, Mom, please?
You can make this my birthday
and Christmas presents.
You've already used up your birthday and
Christmas presents on that peach tree we got you.
And you hardly ever
play with that anymore.
Yes, I do.
Sure, I do. Look!
[Singsong] La-la, here I am playing
on my peach tree, Mom.
Oh, all right,
we'll go.
- Now, the cat needs
his medication every morning-
- No problem. Can do.
- and the furnace has been giving off-
- Right. Gotcha.
a lot of carbon monoxide,
so keep the window open.
Cat in the furnace.
Uh, you know, I think
I'll take Maggie with us.
And if anything happens,
just use your best judgem-
just do what I would do.
[Together]
Whoo-hoo!
A whole week of just father and son.
See you at dinner.
## [Both Whistling]
- What time?
- I don't know.
Shall we say... 10:00?
All right,
just wake me up.
[Muffled]
You know, Bart, I saw this one.
[Muffled, Indistinct]
[Announcer] Live, from the Grand Ballroom
of the Hapsburg Imperial Palace...
it's the World
Series of Bumper Cars.
- [Cars Bumping]
- More food.
[Bart]
Dad, do I have to brush my teeth?
[Homer]
No, but at least rinse your mouth out with soda.
- [Soda Can Opens]
- [Bart Gargling]
I'm gonna rescue a baby seal,
and then I'm gonna save an otter!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I'm sorry, but all the animals
have already been reserved for celebrities.
[Grunts]
There.
That's 104 pounds
of sandpipers.
You mean there's nothing
left to clean?
Well, there are rocks,
thousands and thousands of rocks.
I've got rocks that
need washing at home.
Geez, look at this place.
We gotta do something.
Hmm.
Garbage angels?
[Both Laughing]
[Homer Snoring]
Dad, I think I need
some fresh air.
- Can I go to the park?
- Do I have to sit up?
- No.
- Knock yourself out.
[Motor Buzzing]
Milhouse, this is boring.
Make it crash or something.
Perfectly level flying is the supreme challenge
of the scale-model pilot.
- Gimme that!
- Hey!
- [Gasps]
- [Gasps] It's gaining on us!
- I'm pedaling backwards.
- Abandon ship!
[Grunts]
I don't like
being outdoors, Smithers.
For one thing, there are too many
fat children.
[Gasps]
Thanks a lot.
Now it's stuck on that haunted house.
I heard a witch
lives there.
- I heard a Frankenstein lives there.
- You guys are way off.
It's a secret lab where they take
the brains out of zombies...
and put 'em in the heads of other zombies
to create a race of super-zombies.
- That's the house?
- [Scoffs] Stand aside, wussies.
[Doorbell Rings]
[Woman On Intercom]
Go away. No children.
Enough talk.
## [Imitates Fanfare]
S-U-C-C-E-E-S!
That's the way you spell succe-
[Screaming]
[Grunts]
[All Gasp]
[Laughing]
N-No. H-Help, help.
I'm gonna die.
[Screams, Grunts]
[Groans]
[Wind Gusting]
- [Yelps]
- [All Gasp]
- Oh, no! The old witch has Bart!
- We've got to hurry!
[All Screaming]
- [Groaning]
- [Doorbell Rings]
[Homer]
Just a minute!
- [Grunting]
- [Paper Rustling]
- Hello?
- Your son was trespassing on my property...
and destroyed a very valuable
stone gargoyle and-
Are you wearing
a grocery bag?
I have misplaced my pants.
I'm not going to press charges,
but I assume you'll want to punish him.
[Laughing]
Yeah, I appreciate the suggestion, lady...
but he hates that,
and I gotta live with him.
You're the man, Homer.
Well, if you
won't discipline him...
I'll come back
and speak with his mother.
[Gasps]
No, wait, wait.
Madam, I run a house
of discipline.
The boy will be disciplined
and disciplined severely. Good day.
Aw, I don't know how to punish you.
What does Marge usually do?
- She makes me taste beer.
- Come on, boy. Give your old man a little credit.
Yeah? Well, I still
get to punish you.
Now you're gonna do chores for that lady
until you work off the damage you did.
It's called "responsibility."
[Screams]
[Doorbell Rings]
- Come on in, Bart.
- [Groans]
I can't believe I gotta
spend all my free time...
dusting doilies in a smelly, run-down dump
for a creepy old witch.
## [Jazz]
Ooh.
Lady, I gotta tell ya...
I have been grossly misinformed
about witches.
## [Ends]
Wow, man,
what is this place?
I prefer not
to be called "man."
My name is Belle,
and this is the Maison Derriere.
That means the, uh,
"Back House."
Are you havin'
a party or somethin'?
Nonstop.
We're a burlesque house-
a private club where gentlemen can play
some cards and see a show-
Miss Belle, we're about to do
our "Around the World" number...
but Monte Carlo
can't find her dice.
Here you go, darlin'.
Normally, we don't allow children in here,
but your father was so insistent.
He's tough but fair. I'll start sorting these bras.
[Chuckles]
That's a bit advanced
for you...
but I know a stopped-up
sink that needs some attention.
Just glad
to be on the team.
When you work the door,
the main things are...
to greet the visitors
and toss out the troublemakers.
Ah, the old greet 'n' toss.
No problemo.
How did I ever get along
without you?
## [Whistling]
Oop.
## [Continues Whistling]
Is your name Bart?
- Mm-hmm.
- What the-
Does your father know
you're working here?
- It was his idea.
- In that case, I'll have a whiskey sour.
Oh, there's something unsatisfying
about scrubbing these rocks...
and I think
I know what it is.
Lisa,
I know it's frustrating...
but we made a commitment,
and we have to see it through...
no matter how unpleasant.
Quitting time. Okay.
Scrub up and head for the communal tarp.
We're having kelp burgers, and we're going
to watch a tape ofJohnny Arvik.
He's the Eskimo comedian.
[Chuckles]
Faster, Mom! Faster!
Oh, that was our emcee,
Mel Zetz.
He got out of bed too fast
and broke his hip.
So who's gonna warm up
the crowd tonight?
- Well, whoever fits Mel's tuxedo.
- Eep.
The jokes are
in the breast pocket.
If you get in trouble,
there's a switch...
- that makes the bow tie spin.
- [Whirring]
Heh, nudist colonies
are everywhere these days.
I'd love to go, but l-
I can't get the wrinkles out of my birthday suit.
- ## [Rim Shot]
- [All Laughing]
But I gotta tell ya, Adam and Eve
must have been the first bookkeepers.
They invented
the loose-leaf system.
- ## [Rim Shot]
- [All Laughing]
[Chuckles] If there's a bad
bookkeeping joke, I haven't heard it.
[Announcer]
It's 11:00. Do you know where your children are?
I told you last night, no!
Where is Bart anyway?
His dinner is getting
all cold and eaten.
Bart, where are you?
Come on. I have to be up at 6:00 a.m.
to swipe Flanders's newspaper.
What the- " President Eisenhower
celebrates 40th wedding anniversary.
Not pictured,
Mrs. Eisenhower."
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
- Bart was filling in for-
- I don't care if he was filling in for Mel Zetz.
He's my son, and
I don't want him working...
so... late... that-
Oh, I agree.
Kids need rules and boundaries.
Yes, everyone loves rules.
It's so tough to be a parent these days,
what with all the gangs and the drugs.
Oh, yeah, drugs.
You gotta have drugs.
Hey, he didn't pay
the cover.
Oh, Bart,
he's your father.
We'll comp him tonight,
start a tab tomorrow.
- Oh, I hope I didn't miss the floor show.
- Nope.
- Is Roxanne back?
- Yep.
- Did she, uh, get my flowers?
- She did.
l-
- Hello, Bart.
- Hello, Principal Skinner.
This is the National Air
and Space Museum, isn't it?
Uh, this isn't gonna
be aboutJesus, is it?
All things are aboutJesus,
Homer, except this.
Your son has been working
in a burlesque house.
Principal Skinner saw him
with his own eyes.
That's true, but I was only in there to get
directions on how to get away from there.
Helen, as a responsible parent,
I was already well aware of that.
Homer, I'm as permissive
as the next parent.
I mean, just yesterday, I let Todd buy some
Red Hots with a cartoon devil on the box...
but you can't possibly
think it's appropriate...
for your 10-year-old son
to work in a burlesque house!
Oh, no? Well, if Homer Simpson wants his
10-year-old son working in a burlesque house...
then Homer Simpson's 10-year-old son
is going to work in a burlesque house!
That's the-
[Laughs] Hi!
Now, Marge, you're gonna hear a lot of crazy
talk about Bart working in a burlesque house.
"Maison Derriere"?
I can't believe there's a place like that
in our wholesome little town.
Homer, did you know it was a burlesque house
when you sent Bart to work there?
No, I only learned that
four days ago.
What were you thinking,
sending Bart to such an awful place?
I was trying to punish
him exactly like you would.
So, in a way, you really
dropped the ball on this one.
This is your mess, and I'll be damned
if I'm gonna clean it up.
- [Groans]
- Please come in, Mrs. Simpson.
How can I be of service?
I have a favor to ask.
Please shut this place down
and move away from Springfield.
Oh, honey,
you can't be serious.
Springfield doesn't want
places like this.
- I think I know what Springfield wants, sugar.
- Oh?
- I've lived in this town for 37 years.
- I've lived here 52 years.
- I'm third generation.
- Sixth.
Get out of my town!
Listen, darlin', we're just as much
a part of Springfield...
as the church,
the library or the crazy house.
- So I think I'll stay right here, neighbor.
- Is that so?
Well, sleazy entertainment
and raunchy jokes...
will never be as popular
as sobriety and self-denial.
You're about to learn
the two most dangerous words...
in the English language
are "Marge Simpson."
It's a light-pink
'87 wagon.
And after visiting the area for, uh,
the past two months...
I have determined it is
not feasible to construct...
a super-train between
Springfield and Aruba.
[All Groan]
Next on the agenda is, uh...
the Citizens' Committee
on Moral Hygiene.
[All Groan]
I'm here to share
my moral outrage.
But this time it's not about that
giant inflatable Dos Equis bottle.
It's about a certain house
in our town.
- What's wrong with this house? Is it the plumbin'?
- No.
It's a house of ill fame.
A house of loose ethics.
Is there a building code violation?
A drainage issue? A surveying error?
The house is
perfectly fine!
- Well, then quit bad-mouthing the house!
- Yeah, leave the house alone!
Oh, geez! It's what's inside the house
that's disgraceful.
Drinking, gambling
and debauchery.
It's right under our noses-
a secret house of burlesque.
- [All Gasp]
- [Marge] That's right.
[Carl]
That's- That's not good.
People, this is an issue that we, as a town,
are strong enough to ignore.
Let us give no more scrutiny
to this bawdy house...
and its small clientele
of loyal perverts.
Oh, I'm afraid this problem goes
far beyond Eugene and Rusty.
- [Both Chuckling]
- Marge, if you please.
Julius!
- Clancy!
- [Chalmers] Skinner!
- Seymour!
- Mother.
- [Selma] Patty?
- [Brandine] Cletus!
Oh, uh, Barney.
- [Mrs. Wiggum] Clancy!
- Hey, come on! You did me twice!
Smithers?
My parents insisted
I give it a try, sir.
[Woman]
Mayor Quimby!
Uh, well, that
could be any mayor.
I rest my case.
Er, uh, well, eh,
in light of these new facts...
of which I now realize I was largely aware,
I must take action.
All in favor of demolishing our beloved
burlesque house, raise your hands.
[Clears Throat]
[Whispering]
Are they talkin' about the bordello?
No, the burlesque house.
So just keep your mouth shut.
[Crowd Chattering]
No, there's no justice
like angry-mob justice.
I'm gonna burn
all the historic "memorabilias."
- I'm gonna take me home a toilet.
- Well, there'd better be two.
[Doorbell Rings]
- [Belle On Intercom] Who is it?
- Uh, it's an angry mob, ma'am.
Could you step outside for a twinkle
while we knock down your house?
Just a minute.
Stand aside, you degenerate
two-bit proprietress.
Don't you call me that.
I'm an entrepreneuse.
Oh, shut up!
You're wasting valuable smashing time.
Dad, we can't let this
happen to Belle. Do something.
Don't you worry, Son.
My friends! Stop!
Please, hurry.
- Sure, we could tear this house down-
- [All Cheer]
No, my friends! Stop!
Let me finish.
We could tear it down...
but we'd be tearing down
a part of ourselves.
## [Singing]
## [Jazz]
## [All Singing]
[Springs]
[Whistles]
## [Ends]
- [Horn Honks]
- [Belches]
Well, I'm convinced.
The house stays.
This house- [Quoting Lyric]
Here I come, everybody!
[All Clamoring]
What are you doing, Marge?
Didn't you hear the song?
No, I had to go
rent the bulldozer.
Well, we all
changed our minds.
Yeah, now we
love the house.
And what about the sleaze
and the depravity?
It was a very
convincing song, Marge.
- Mm-hmm, there were kicks and everything.
- Oh. Can you sing it again?
I'm sorry. It really was one of those
spur-of-the-moment-type things.
- Well, I also have a song to sing.
- [Bowstring Twangs]
Don't make up your mind
until you hear both songs.
[Clears Throat, Coughs]
## [Singing]
[Crash]
Uh, sorry.
Thanks a lot, Marge.
That was our only burlesque house.
I do love it when
you drop by, Marge.
Next time, why don't we
get together at your house?
I'm so sorry.
How can we ever
make this up to you?
Oh, there's a way, Mom.
So, Twiggy, I hear you and your
husband, Woody, just had a baby.
What did you name him?
- Chip.
- [Rim Shot]
Take it off!
- All right, Dad. You've been warned. Let's go.
- Hey!
- Come on.
- Easy.
## [Jazz]
## [Ends]
- [Murmuring]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net