[Chorus]
## TheSimpsons ##
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Thinking ]
Ah, another beautiful day in the womb.
- ####[Classical]
- # La, la, la, la, la #
# La, la, la #
##La, la, la####
[ Gasping ]
Let go! Let go!
I'm all naked and wet!
- Get up, Homer. It's time for church.
- I don't wanna go.
- It's church. You have to go.
- Too cold out.
I'm tired of having this argument
every Sunday. Get dressed.
Oh, stupid, itchy church pants.
[ Grunting ]
One size fits all, my butt!
- Come on. We're going to be late.
- [Pants Tearing]
Forget it. I'm not going.
[ Growls ]
- Hey, where's Homer?
- Your father's... resting.
"Resting" hungover, "resting" got fired?
Help me out here.
Ahhh, I'm just a big,
toasty cinnamon bun.
I never wanna leave this bed.
Uh-oh. Gotta take a whiz.
Think, man. Think.
Think, think, think.
I better get up.
I'm whizzin' with the door open,
and I love it.
## [ Singing ]
[ Blubbering ]
[Man]
It's 1 1 K-BBL degrees below zero.
- I hope you're someplace warm.
- You bet your sweet...
ass!
I'm afraid our furnace isn't working.
[Man]
Yeah, what's the story?
But let's just put it
out of our minds...
and turn to the lamentations
of Jeremiah...
long version.
"Joy is gone from our hearts...
our dancing has turned to mourning. '"
####[Rock And Roll]
####[Girls Singing]
## [ Singing ]
The perfect chance to make
my patented, space-age...
out-of-this-world moon waffles.
Let's see here.
Caramels. Waffle batter.
Liquid smoke.
Oooh, waffle runoff.
Mmm, fattening.
And he was cast into
the fiery cauldron of hell!
The searing heat...
the scalding rivers of molten sulfur!
Ahhh, I'm there.
Uh-oh.
[ Whistling ]
Here, boy.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
The service has ended.
Go in peace.
####[Pipe Organ]
[ Grunting ]
The door's frozen shut,
and it's the only way out!
- [ Chattering ]
- Our Father who art in heaven, hallowed be--
Lisa, this is neither
the time nor the place.
[Man On Radio]
That was Johnny Calhoun with...
"Gonna Find Mea Genie
With a Magic Bikini. '"
[Man #2]Johnny's next record was a spoken
word album of his right-wing political views.
It killed his career. If you can tell me the name
Of that album, call our contest line now.
[ Gasps ]
I know that!
[ Line Ringing ]
- Hello. This is Homer Simpson.
- [ Man ] Homer, can you name that title?
- "This Things I Believe."
- [ Man #2 ] Uh, can we accept that?
- [ Cash Register Ringing ]
- Whoo-hoo!
- How's that door coming, Willy?
- Miracles are your department, Reverend.
Uh, while we're waiting,
Why don't I read from the Sunday bulletin?
Card table for sale.
Top badly damaged. Leg missing.
Otherwise fine.
One dollar or best offer.
[ Woman On TV]
You must be the three chiropractors I sent for.
Now, start manipulating my spine.
[Curly]Hey, Moe, we don't know
nothin' about manipulatin.
- [Moe] You heard the lady.
Grab her spine and get crackin.
- [Punch Landing]
- [ Chuckling ] Moe is their leader.
- [Curly Whooping]
-[Moe] Why, you!
-[Punch Landing]
-[Curly]Hey!
[ Grunting ]
Huzzah!
Plea-Please, Christians, don't push.
Excuse me. Pardon me. Whoop. Coming through.
Howya doing? Love that hat, baby.
Come on, TV. Give me some of that
sweet, sweet pap.
Well, let's define
our terms, gentlemen.
Are we talking about redistricting
or are we talking about reapportionment?
Oh, well, can't win 'em all.
[ Man ] We interrupt this public affairs program
to bring you a football game.
- Yes!
- [ Whistle Blowing ]
- [ Engine Not Turning Over]
- [Marge Imitating Engine]
[ Imitating Engine ]
- Give it a little more gas.
- [Pedal Banging]
No, no, that's too much.
You know what I think would help?
- What? What would help?
- Nothing.
Oh, doctor.
A 98-yard triple reverse...
ties the score at 63-63.
We have seen nothing
but razzle-dazzle here today...
three visits from Morganna
the Kissing Bandit...
and the astonishing return
of Jim Brown.
Whoo-hoo!
Is that what I think it is?
Mm-hmm.
I found... a penny!
Could this be
the best day of my life?
[ Laughing ]
Looks like we have a new champion.
Ah, my beloved family.
- How was church?
- [ Muttering ]
[ Snorting ]
I, on the other hand,
have been having the best day of my life...
and I owe it all
to skipping church.
That's a terrible thing to say!
Kids, your father doesn't really mean that.
Like fun I don't.
Marge, I'm never going to church again!
Homer, are you actually
giving up your faith?
No. No, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, yes.
I can't believe
you're giving up church, Homer.
Hey, what's the big deal about going
to some building every Sunday?
- I mean, isn't God everywhere?
- Amen, brother.
And don't you think that the Almighty
has better things to worry about...
than where one little guy spends
one measly hour of his week?
- Tell it, Daddy.
- And what if we pick the wrong religion?
Every week we're just making
God madder and madder.
Testify!
[ Groaning ]
Lord, my husband
is by no means perfect...
but he's a kind, decent man.
Please show him
the error of his ways.
Marge, come to bed.
No, Homer.
He doesn't mean
to be sacrilegious, Lord.
He just likes to sleep in on Sundays.
Marge. Come to bed, Marge.
[ Whispering ] Lord, please.
He's not a bad person, Lord, really.
- It's good for what ails ya.
- He doesn't mean any harm.
I can wait all--
[ Snoring ]
[Rumbling]
[ Gasps ]
[ Static Humming ]
[ Gulps ]
God?
Thou has forsaken my church!
- Well, kind of, but--
- But what?
I'm not a bad guy.
I work hard and I love my kids.
So why should I spend half my Sunday
hearing about how I'm going to hell?
Hmm, you've got a point there.
You know, sometimes...
even I'd rather be watching football.
Does St. Louis still have a team?
- No, they moved to Phoenix.
- Oh, yeah.
You know what I really hate about church?
Those boring sermons.
Oh, I couldn't agree more.
That Reverend Lovejoy
really displeases me.
I think I'll give him a canker sore.
- Give him one for me.
- I will.
- So I figure I should just try to live right--
- [ Purring ]
and worship you in my own way.
Homer, it's a deal.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to appear on a tortilla in Mexico.
- Dad, can I ask you a question?
- Sure, honey.
Why are you dedicating
your life to blasphemy?
Don't worry, sweetheart.
If I'm wrong, I'll recant on my deathbed.
Hello, my animal friends.
Peace be with you.
Guys, please,
could you give me five minutes?
Reverend Lovejoy, I had a bit
Of an ulterior motive in inviting you to dinner.
- [ Shouts ] What?
- No, it's nothing bad.
I'm just concerned because my husband
hasn't been attending your services lately.
Well, I wasn't sure
I was doing the right thing...
but then God himself told me
I should seek a new path.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah. He appeared before me in a dream...
and I knew that was special because
I usually dream about naked... Marge.
- [ Groans ]
- So, Homer, you saw the big cheese?
- What'd he look like?
- Perfect teeth, nice smell, a class act all the way.
Homer, you're crazy!
Tell him this is all crazy.
Homer, I'd like you
to remember Matthew 7:26.
The foolish man who built
his house on sand.
And you remember...
Matthew 21 :1 7.
"And he left them and went out of the city
into Bethany and he lodged there"?
Yeah. Think about it.
Hello, work?
This is Homer Simpson.
I won't be coming in tomorrow.
Religious holiday.
The, uh, Feast of Maximum Occupancy.
- Pretty slick.
- You should join my religion, Moe.
It's great.
No hell, no kneeling--
Sorry, Homer. I was born a snake handler,
and I'll die a snake handler.
[Doorbell Rings]
Neighbor, I heard about your heresy...
and we've made it our mission
to win you back to the flock.
- No sale.
- Homer, Christian life isn't all praying and sacrifice.
Hey, dig this.
## [ Singing Religious Song ]
- [ Snoring ]
- [Phone Ringing]
## [ Flanders Family Singing ]
## [ Singing ]
- Leave me alone.
- Dad, the heathen's getting away.
I see him, son.
[ Crossing Bells Dinging ]
[ Horn Blaring ]
[ Screams ]
[ Chuckles ]
- Where we going?
- Garbage Island.
[ Horn Blaring ]
Huh?
[ Screaming ]
[ Cheering ]
Let's go, kids.
How come we have to go to church and
Dad gets to stay home and watch cartoons?
[ Groans ]
I have a responsibility
to raise these children right.
And unless you change,
I'll have to tell them their father is...
well, wicked.
Kids, let me tell you about
another so-called "wicked" guy.
He had long hair
and some wild ideas...
and he didn't always do what
other people thought was right.
And that man's name was--
I forget.
But the point is--
I forget that too.
Marge, you know who I'm talking about.
- He used to drive that blue car.
- Kids, could you wait outside for us?
Homer, please don't make me choose
between my man and my god...
because you just can't win.
There you go again.
Always taking someone else's side--
Flanders, the water department, God.
I'm only going to ask you
one last time.
Are you sure you won't
come with us to church?
[ Man On TV]
Coming up next: make your own ladder.
Very sure.
My friends, the devil walks among us!
[ Chattering ]
- I got him!
- No, don't look for the pitchfork and pointy tail.
Today's devil has assumed
a more seductive form...
pleasing to the eye.
Oooh, a interview
with Lorne Michaels.
Oooh. Wait.
That's no good.
Hey, now we're talking.
"Our unabashed dictionary
defines I.U.D. as...
"love springs internal."'
- I don't get it.
- [Doorbell Chimes]
Hello.
I'm collecting for the
Brotherhood of Jewish Clowns.
Last year, tornadoes claimed
the lives of75Jewish clowns.
The worst incident was during
our convention in Lubbock, Texas.
There were floppy shoes
and rainbow wigs everywhere.
It was terrible.
[ Sobbing ]
Wait a minute.
Is this a religious thing?
A religious clown thing, yes.
- Sorry.
- Well, bless you any--
Remember the Sabbath day,
to keep it holy!
Apu, I see you're not in church.
Oh, but I am.
I have a shrine to Ganesha...
the god of worldly wisdom
located in the employee lounge.
- Hey, Ganesha, want a peanut?
- Please do not offer my god a peanut.
No offense, Apu, but when they
were handing out religions...
you must've been out taking a whiz.
Mr. Simpson, please pay for your purchases
and get out and come again.
Pride goeth before destruction!
Boy, everyone is stupid except me.
[Snoring]
Marge, turn down the heat.
That's better.
[ Snoring ]
[ Sniffing, Whines ]
[ Growling ]
[ Screams ]
Fire! What do I do? What do I do?
[ Coughing ]
Oh, the song, the song.
## [ Singing ]
D'oh!
[ Coughing ]
[Apu Gasps]
Fire at the old Simpson place!
- You're on your honor not to steal anything.
- Oh, we won't.
Little Jamshed,
the store is in your hands.
- How I have waited for this day.
- [ Cocks Shotgun ]
[ Siren Wailing ]
[ Quacking ]
You ducks are really
trying my patience!
But you're so cute.
Homer. Homer!
No!
[ Homer Moans ]
Dear Lord, may your loving hand
guide Homer to the mattress, square and true.
Okay.
[Siren Wailing]
[ Coughing ]
Flanders, you saved me.
Why?
Heck, you'd have done
the same for me.
Help! Help!
[ Laughing ]
That's right, old friend.
- [ Bart, Lisa ] Dad!
- Oh, Homie, are you all right?
Our magazines and roach traps,
gone. All gone.
[ Cat Screeching ]
I saved your cat.
Ow! That hurt.
Hey, what are these axes for?
- I don't know. Chopping stuff.
- Gotcha.
Uh, that's some nice chopping.
Truly, this was an act of God.
Hey, wait a minute.
Flanders is a regular Charlie Church...
and God didn't save his house.
- D'oh!
- Any valuables in the house?
Well, the Picasso,
my collection of classic cars--
Sorry. This policy only covers
actual losses, not made-up stuff.
Well, that's just great.
Fire, man's oldest foe.
Insatiable, remorseless, unquenchable.
- Hey, it's out.
- [ Cheering ]
Coming up next,
which work better--
springy clothespins
or the other kind?
You know, I have a feeling
there's a lesson here.
- Yes, the lesson is--
- No, don't tell me. I'll get it.
Oh, I know.
The Lord is vengeful.
O Spiteful One, show me who to smite,
and they shall be "smoten."
Homer, God didn't
Set your house on fire.
No, but he was working in the hearts
Of your friends and neighbors...
when they went to your aid...
be they Christian, Jew
or... miscellaneous.
Hindu. There are
700 million of us.
- Aw, that's super.
- I was rude to every one of you.
And you saved my life when you could have
just left me to fry...
like the proverbial pancake
that I am.
Oh, Homey, I'm so glad
to hear you say that.
Now, would you give church
another try?
I'll be there next Sunday,
front row, center.
[ Snoring Loudly]
####[Harp]
Don't feel bad, Homer. Nine out often
religions fail in their first year.
That's game, Hendrix!
God, I gotta ask you something.
What's the meaning of life?
Homer, I can't tell you that.
- Come on.
- You'll find out when you die.
- I can't wait that long.
- You can't wait six months?
No, tell me now.
Well, okay.
The meaning of life is--
- [ People Chattering ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net