[Chorus]
## The Simpsons ##
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[Announcer]
Products you could only imagine before--
- the S.S. Microwave.
- [ Dings ]
Ah, my crêpes are done.
The Doggie Doorman.
Good evening, Rex.
- And Mobilier-- the chandelier for your car.
- [ Grunts ]
Whoa!
All on I Can't Believe They Invented It!
Hello, everybody.
I'm Troy McClure...
star of such films as "P" Is For Psycho...
and The President's Neck Is Missing.
But now I'm here to tell you
about a remarkable new invention.
[ Grunting ]
Until now, this was the only way
to get juice from an orange.
[ Grunting, Gasps ]
You mean there's a better way?
But that's all changed--
thanks to the Juice Loosener.
Let's meet the inventor,
Dr. Nick Riviera.
Hello, Troy. Hi, everybody.
Hi, Dr. Nick!
Troy, would you like
a glass of orange juice?
I sure would. But won't we have to pay
those outrageous grocery-store prices...
for something the farmer
probably spit in?
Not anymore!
All thanks to the new Juice Loosener.
[Applause]
- [ Whirring Loudly]
- Doctor, are you sure it's on? I can't hear a thing.
It's whisper quiet!
You got all that
from one bag of oranges?
That's right. Order now
and you'll also get Sun 'n' Run...
the suntan lotion
that's also a laxative.
Gotta get a juicer.
Gotta drink juice. Lose weight.
- Won't get chest pains from
answering the phone anymore.
- [ Line Ringing ]
Please don't tell the supervisor
I have the flu.
I've been working with
a shattered pelvis for three weeks.
[ Both Laughing ]
- [ Audible Laughter Stops ]
- [ Coughing ]
Oh, my Juice Loosener's
never gonna come.
- Hey, Dad, this came for you in the mail.
- Whoo-hoo!
[ Screams ]
Mother, get an
extra-special hug ready.
I bought you a new juicer.
[ Gasps ] Good Lord. Flu germs
entering every orifice in my head. Uhh.
- Happy birthday.
[ Both Scream ]
[ Bell Dings ]
## [ Humming ]
Huh? What the--
[ Screams ]
The dreaded Osaka flu has hit Springfield
with over 300 cases now reported.
Now over to Arnie Pie
with "Arnie in the Sky."
Route 401 is going
around and around...
and around and around and around.
And look out at the corner of 12th
and Main because I'm gonna be sick. Whoop.
Okay, Mr. Sun, gimme what you got.
[ Screaming ]
98.6. You're fine. Now hurry up
or you'll miss your bus.
Maybe you better take
that temperature one more time.
Sarge, we keep getting orders
to let the virus win.
Must be a school day.
Lay down your arms.
All right!
Let's make some pus.
- [ Chuckling ]
- [TV Clicks On]
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting, Screams ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Laughing, Coughing ]
And now, for an emergency
announcement from the mayor.
People of Springfield,
because of the epidemic...
I have canceled
my vacation to the Bahamas.
I shall not leave the city--
- Hey, you, get that steel drum
out of the, uh, mayor's office.
- Sorry, "mon."
Smithers, this plague
doesn't scare me.
I've constructed
a germfree chamber for myself.
Not a single microbe
can get in or out.
- Who the devil are you?
- [ Thinking ] Don't panic.
just come up with a good story.
My name is Mr. Burns.
D'oh!
[ Chanting ]
We need a cure! We need a cure!
[ Chuckling ]
Why, the only cure is bed rest.
Anything I give you
would only be a placebo.
- Where do we get these placebos?
- Maybe there's some in this truck!
[ Bees Buzzing ]
I'm cured.
I mean, ouch!
Dad, Todd's speaking in tongues!
[ Speaking Gibberish ]
I wish he were, Rod.
I pray for the day...
but I'm afraid he's just
delirious from fever.
Oh, Neddy,
why has God forsaken us?
I can't imagine what
we could have done to-- Oh.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, no!
Hey, Peg, you gotta take
better care of the house.
These plants are all
lifeless and limp.
Maybe they'd feel more at home
in the bedroom, Al.
[Audience Cheering]
- [ Laughing ]
- [Thunderclap]
Uh-oh.
Oh, the network slogan is true.
Watch Fox and be damned
for all eternity.
[Lisa]
Mom, can you bring me more O.J. ?
[Bart]Can you get me some of those
Flintstones chewable morphine?
- There's no such thing.
- [Homer]Marge, the boy's
wasting valuable time.
Come change the channel
and pat my head.
- In a minute.
- But I'll miss Sheriff Lobo.
And get me a bottle of bourbon.
Grampa, you know you can't
have liquids after 3:00 p.m.
You can stir it into my mush.
Either way, just gimme, gimme, gimme!
- [Lisa]Mom, I need more O.J.
- [Bart]Flintstones chewable morphine.
- [Homer]I'll miss Sheriff Lobo.
- Mom, I need more O.J.
- Flintstones chewable morphine.
- I'll miss Sheriff Lobo.
- O.J.
- Morphine.
- Lobo.
- O.J.
- Morphine.
- Lobo.
And a bottle of aspirin, please.
The aspirin is 24.95.
24.95!
I lowered the price because an escaped
mental patient tampered with the bottle.
[ Groans ]
- [Alarm Blaring]
- [ Gasps ] Hmm?
Oh, dear.
The alarm must be broken.
If you could just move
a bit to your left.
Eight foot, six.
Oh, Sanjay, help Mrs. Simpson
with her bag. And while you're at it--
[ Speaking Hindi ]
Hmm.
[ Gasps ]
Mrs. Simpson!
You did not pay for this bottle of
Colonel Kwik-E-Mart's Kentucky Bourbon.
Uh, no, I-- I guess I didn't.
- [Sirens Wailing]
- [ Gasps ]
All right, come out
with your hands up...
two cups of coffee...
an auto freshener
that says Capricorn...
and something
with coconut on it.
Now, Marge, you've come
to the right place.
By hiring me as your lawyer,
you also get this smoking monkey.
Better cut down there, Smokey.
- Mr. Hutz--
- Look. He's taking another puff!.
Mr. Hutz, this was all
a misunderstanding.
I didn't mean to take anything.
Now don't you worry,
Mrs. Simpson. I--
- Uh-oh. We've drawn Judge Snyder.
- Is that bad?
Well, he's had it in for me
ever since I kinda ran over his dog.
- You did?
- Well, replace the word "kinda"
with the word "repeatedly"...
and the word "dog" with "son."
- [ Groans ]
- Look, Marge.
I'll just talk to Apu and
I'm sure he'll be reasonable.
## [ Singing Indian Song ]
Apu, I'd like you to drop
the charges against my wife.
No offense, but we're putting
that bitch on ice.
Now come on!
I'm your best customer.
I'm sorry, Mr. Homer, but it
is the policy of the Kwik-E-Mart...
and its parent corporation,
Nordyne Defense Dynamics...
to prosecute shoplifters
to the full extent of the law.
## [ Singing ]
Don't tell anyone, but, uh, Marge
Simpson was arrested for shoplifting.
Let the word go forth
from this time and place...
Marge Simpson is a shoplifter.
- Hey!
- In other news, the chick in The Crying Game...
- is really a man.
- [ All ] Boo!
- I mean, man, is that a good movie.
- [ All ] Yea!
And last Christmas,
Marge made us gingerbread men.
And there was a hair in one.
Well, I'll let you in on
a little secret about Marge Simpson.
She's got webbed toes.
- [ Laughing ]
- Ew, that's gross.
- Come on.
- Please.
Now, Marge, don't you worry.
We've all had our brushes with the law.
[Knocking]
- Are you Ed Flanders?
- No, Ned Flanders.
My mistake.
I'll never have that problem again.
Um, will you excuse me
while I go and freshen up?
I'll follow her.
Just wash your hands and get out.
[ Sighs ]
[Man]
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury...
who do you find more attractive--
Tom Cruise or Mel Gibson?
What is the point of all this?
Your Honor, I feel so confident
of Marge Simpson's guilt...
that I can waste the court's time
by rating the super hunks.
- [ Impressed Murmuring ]
- Wow, that's confidence.
- Ooh, he's gonna win.
- Mr. Hutz!
Now, Mrs. Lovejoy, could you tell us
a little about Marge Simpson?
Well, as the wife of the minister...
I'm privy to a lot
of sensitive information.
And here it is. Marge's husband doesn't
earn much, and the family's a mess.
And, quite frankly, I think she, um--
[ Squeaking ]
Let the record show that the witness
made the drinky-drinky motion.
And if we freeze on frame 1 38...
we distinctly see
a puff of blue hair...
coming from the grassy knoll.
Now, Apu, Mrs. Simpson
claims that she forgot...
she was carrying that bottle
of delicious bourbon...
brownest of the brown liquors...
so tempting.
What's that?
You want me to drink you?
But I'm in the middle of a trial.
Excuse me.
- [ Line Ringing ]
- Hello, David. I'm really tempted.
just take it one day at a time,
and know that I love you.
I love you too, man.
So, Mr. Nahasapeemapetilon,
if that is your real name...
have you ever forgotten anything?
No. In fact,
I can recite pi to 40,000 places.
The last digit is one.
Mmm, pie.
Well, if you never
forget anything, tell me this.
What color tie am I wearing?
You are wearing
a red-and-white striped club tie...
in a half Windsor knot.
Oh, I am, am I?
Is that what you think?
Well, if that is what you think...
I have something to tell you.
[ Grunts ]
Something that may shock
and discredit you.
And that thing is as follows.
I'm not wearing a tie at all.
- [ All Gasp ]
- [ Gasps ]
But if I am wrong about that...
maybe I am wrong
about Mrs. Simpson.
No further questions.
Kids, I got a crazy feeling
your mom's not going to prison.
Yea!
You're a latter-day Clarence Darrow.
Uh, was he the black guy
on The Mod Squad?
Mr. Hutz, when I grow up,
I wanna be a lawyer just like you.
Good for you, son.
If there's one thing America needs,
it's more lawyers.
Can you imagine a world
without lawyers?
####[Soft Rock]
[ Shudders ]
And so, ladies and gentlemen
of the jury, I rest my case.
Hmm. Mr. Hutz, do you know
you're not wearing any pants?
What?
[ Screams ]
I move for a bad court thingy.
- You mean a mistrial?
- Yeah.
That's why you're the judge,
and I'm the law-talkin' guy.
- The lawyer.
- Right.
[Judge Snyder] The foreman will pass
the verdict to the bailiff.
This verdict is written
on a cocktail napkin!
- And it still says "guilty."
And "guilty" is spelled wrong!
- [ Squeaks ]
Will the foreman please read
the real verdict?
We find the defendant guilty.
Marge Simpson, I sentence you
to 30 days in prison.
Next case. The National Council
of Churches vs. Lionel Hutz.
- [ All Grumbling ]
- Oh, right. That thing.
[ Crying ]
You're still my hero, Mom.
Now you kids be good
while Mother's in prison.
Don't worry, Mom.
I'll bust you out of there...
just as soon as I get
a cocktail dress and a crowbar.
####[Mambo]
Bartina, until I met you...
I was the loneliest warden
in the penal system.
[ High-pitched ]
Fresh.
Oh, down I go.
I'll be fine, dear.
Marge, I'm gonna miss you so much.
And it's not just the sex.
It's also the food preparation.
Your skill with stains of all kinds.
But mostly, I'll miss how lucky you make
me feel each and every morning.
I'll miss you too, Homey.
With her behind bars,
our store is secure.
I'm taking this thing to Mexico.
[Chuckling]
Knock, knock. I'm Marge Simpson,
your new cell mate.
I'm Phillips. They call me that 'cause I killed
my husband with a Phillips head screwdriver.
[ Sighs ]
It's so nice not to have to cook.
- You mean your husband never cooked for you?
- Well, once.
Homer, I don't think this fish
is quite dead yet.
Marge, please, I'm having
enough trouble with the lobsters.
[ Groaning ]
- Oh, my goodness!
- That's Tattoo Annie.
[Marge] "What kind of slime
would I marry?"
- I don't understand.
- It's one of those Mad Magazine fold-ins.
Amazing!
Now, kids, while your mother's gone...
I don't wanna have to
wash any dishes.
So from now on, drink straight
from the faucet or milk carton...
and we'll eat while standing
over the sink or toilet.
- Who's gonna change Maggie?
- We're gonna let her roam free in the backyard...
and nature will take its course.
Excuse me, but I think
if we all do our fair share...
we can keep this house clean.
[ Screeches ]
[ Growling ]
Dad, we're running
out of clean clothes.
It seems like I've been wearing
this same red dress forever.
Go up to the attic.
There's a whole trunk of clothes up there.
## [ Humming Wedding Song ]
All right! Bologna and cheese!
What do you got, Bart?
A pack of sugar and peanut butter
smeared on a playing card.
Ha-ha! Your mom's a jailbird.
- So's yours.
- Oh, yeah. Let's play.
[Footsteps]
[Lisa]
Oh, Mom, I've missed you so much.
Oh, honey, I've missed you too.
Homer, is that an old
Halloween costume?
Uh, no.
So, how are things at home?
We flushed the gator down the toilet, but it
got stuck halfway. Now we have to feed it.
I'll bet you want a piece of me.
Well, you ain't gonna get it, see?
[ Laughing ]
[Moans]
Doggone it.
[Homer]Honey, I don't know
what you're feelin' right now...
so I don't wanna push anything.
We can just hold hands
or sit and talk.
- [ Growling ]
- Whoo!
Oh, do you have any of those
delicious marshmallow squares?
Sorry. Marge Simpson makes those.
- Oh, darn!
- [ All Sigh ]
Fifteen dollars short.
Exactly what Marge Simpson's
marshmallow squares bring in.
Can we still afford
that statue of Lincoln?
- No, I'm afraid we'll have
to go with something cheaper.
- Ah.
I give you our 39th president,
jimmy Carter.
- Oh, come on!
- He's history's greatest monster!
[ All Shouting ]
- Release the dogs.
- Gee, they look pretty mad.
Yeah, I've been starvin' 'em,
teasin' 'em, singing off-key.
## [ Singing Off-key]
[ Screaming ]
No! Nice doggy.
This never would have happened
if Marge Simpson was here.
Good-bye, Marge.
I'll miss ya.
I hope you find somebody.
Men are such slime. But I'm seeing
this new guy. I think he's different.
Yoo-hoo!
[ Belches ]
- He says his name is Homer,
and he works at the nuclear plant.
- [ Groans ]
We gotta clean this up
before Mom gets back.
No problemo.
We'll just sweep it all under the rug.
[Rumbling]
[Objects Cracking]
[Man]
Hey, watch it.
[ Cheering ]
I didn't expect all this.
Well, we never should
have let you go.
From now on, I'll use my gossip
for good instead of evil.
Three cheers for Marge Simpson!
[ All ]
Hip, hip, hooray! Hip, hip, hooray!
- Hip, hip, hooray!
- [Mayor Quimby]Now, Marge...
we have a special treat for you.
Uh, it's beautiful.
- [ People Chattering ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net