[Chorus]
## The Simpsons ##
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[Troy McClure]
Live from beautiful Laughlin, Nevada...
it's the Miss American Girl Pageant.
Brought to you by:
Smell like Streep
For cheap!
I'm your host, Troy McClure.
And now, here come the ladies!
- [ Applause ]
- ## [ Singing ]
[ Troy]
Like Miss South Dakota.
Miss North Carolina.
Miss Indiana.
Miss Alaska.
Kids, I won't be home tonight, so I'm leaving
you some low-cal microwavable TV dinners.
- Uh--
- Okay.
I'm auditioning for a play.
It's a musical version
Of A Street car Named Desire.
Isn't that exciting?
[ Troy] If you ask me,
they're all winners!
We'll be cutting our first
40 contestants right after this.
Let's take a minute to meet our
distinguished panel of judges.
Skin-care consultant, Roweena.
Syndicated columnist,
William F. George.
Token black panelist,
Drederick Tatum.
And Mr. Boswell, the man behind
those infamous worst-dressed lists.
Mr. Boswell, can you give us
a sneak peek at this year's list?
Memo to Goldie Hawn:
cheerleading tryouts were 30 years ago.
Let's grow up, shall we?
- [ All Laughing ]
- He's such a bitch.
I haven't been in a play
since high school...
and I thought it would be a good chance
to meet some other adults.
- Sounds interesting.
- You know, I spend all day alone with Maggie...
and sometimes it's like
I don't even exist.
- Sounds interesting.
- [ Groans ]
It's time to name
our five finalists...
starting with...
Miss Montana.
- [Applause]
- A beaut from Butte.
- Miss South Carolina.
- Nothin' could be finer.
- Miss Delaware.
- She, uh--
- Good for her.
- ## [ Singing Scales ]
Marge, keep it
down in there!
Homer, my audition
is in half--
Hey, look, it's last year's winner,
Debra Jo Smallwood!
Tonight, my reign
as Miss American Girl comes to an end.
And I'd like to apologize
one last time...
for my unfortunate remarks
at the United Nations.
## [ Classical ]
Maggie, cut that racket!
And where exactly
Are you going?
I'm auditioning for a play.
- Well, this is the first I've heard about it.
- I told you several times.
It's a musical version
Of A Streetcar Na--
Excuse me, Marge! I think
that if you told me, I would remember.
I mean, I'm not an idiot!
- Hm. Well, I-I thought I told you.
- Kids, back me up.
- He's right, Mom.
- Sorry.
Match point-- Homer.
- I'm sorry, honey.
- It's okay. We're none of us perfect.
- ####[Piano]
- ####[Singers Warming Up]
## [ Vocalizing ]
- Well, howdy-do, neighbor.
- Hi, Ned.
- I didn't know you were an actor.
- Oh, indeedily-doodily.
Uh, I've even been in
Streetcar once before.
I played Blanche DuBois.
Mm-hmm. Just part of the fun
Of going to an all-male school.
Hello! I am Llewellyn Sinclair.
I have directed three plays
in my career...
and I have had
three heart attacks.
That's how much I care.
I'm planning for a fourth.
Maybe I should have taken
a nice calligraphy class.
Oh, forget about it.
That Mr. Takahashi's a lunatic.
- Quiet!
- Sorry.
I am not an easy man
to work for.
While directing
Hats Off to Hanukkah...
I reduced more than one
cast member to tears.
Did I expect too much
from fourth graders?
The review, "Play Enjoyed By All, '"
speaks for itself.
Hm.
Those auditioning
for the role of Stanley...
take off your shirts.
Take off your shirts!
[ Repeating In French ]
Schnell! Schnell! Schnell!
Uh-uh. Nope.
Try joining a gym.
Oh, ye gods!
Hey, man, if you like that,
you should see my butt.
You. You're my Stanley.
Hot diggity!
How 'bout that, Marge?
Little ol' Stanley me.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Weakly] "Stella. Stella!"
[ Laughs ]
- ## [ Singing ]
- Next!
- Thank you for nothing.
You're all terrible!
What you ladies don't understand
is that Blanche...
is a delicate flower being trampled
by an uncouth lout--
[ Sighs ] Forget it!
just strike the sets.
Clear the stage.
This production is--
Homie, I didn't
get the part.
You were right.
Outside interests are stupid.
Wait a minute.
[ Groans ]
I'll come home right away.
All right. I'll pick up a bucket
Of fried chicken, extra skin...
rolls,
chocolate cream parfait--
- [ Gasps ]
- Stop bothering my Blanche!
Oh!
I play an aging Southern beauty
who's driven to insanity...
by her brutish
brother-in-law, Stanley.
Wow!
My mother the actress.
I feel like
Lucie Arnaz Luckinbill.
Are there any jive-talking
robots in this play?
I don't think so.
Bart, don't ask
stupid questions.
- Is there any frontal nudity?
- No, Homer.
My name is Helen Lovejoy,
and I'll be playing Stella.
I am Apu Nahasapeemapetilon.
I play Steve.
My name is "Ot-to!"
I'm playing "Pab-lo!"
Lionel Hutz,
attorney-at-law.
I'm filing a class-action suit
against the director...
on behalf of everyone who was
cut from the play.
- I also play Mitch.
- I'm Marge Simpson.
I'll be playing Blanche. I made some
peanut butter brownies for everyone.
- Well, would anyone else like a bite of banality?
- I would.
- Stanley--
- Yeah?
You're pulsing with animal lust!
You take Blanche and you fling her
roughly to the bed.
Roger-dodger.
Grr.
Aww, isn't that cute!
And me without a camera.
Here. My sister
runs a day care center.
Hmm. I guess a few weeks
wouldn't hurt her.
Maggie is allergic
To strained pears...
and she likes a bottle
of warm milk before nap time.
A bottle?
[ Laughs ]
Mrs. Simpson, do you know what a baby's
saying when she reaches for a bottle?
- "Ba-ba?"
- She's saying, "I am a leech."
Our aim here is to develop
the bottle within.
That sounds awfully harsh.
Mrs. Simpson, I don't like
to toot my own horn...
but we're the only
day care center in town...
that's not currently
under investigation by the state.
Oh. Well,
be a good girl, Maggie.
I'm sorry, Maggie.
We don't allow these here.
#You're a dame
and I'm a fella #
# Stanley, stop
or I'll tell Stella #
Passion,
Mrs. Simpson. Anger.
- This man disgusts you!
- #All I want is one embrace #
# I'll twist this bottle
in your face #
Mm. Mm. Mm!
[ Chuckles ] Here, Marge, let me.
Hate to be an armchair Blanche...
but I always gave it
one of these--
- There. There's the ol' face-shredder.
- Oh.
Mrs. Simpson, if you set out to push
the bile to the tip of my throat...
mission accomplished!
I'm, uh-- I'm gonna crawl
into bed with a bottle of amaretto.
Good day.
[ Homer] Easy, easy. Yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes-- D'oh!
[ Electronic Voice ]
7-1 0 split.
Homer, can you run
some lines with me?
- Make Bart do it.
- It'll just take a sec.
- Gutter ball!
- D'oh!
You see, Marge, while you're
Off in your own little world...
you forgot that other people
have problems too.
[ Sighs ]
####[Action Movie Theme]
[ Objects Crashing ]
Don't like to nap, eh? We have
a place for babies like you-- the box!
All right, let "ham-ateur" night
in Dixie commence.
I'm sorry, Llewellyn,
I just--
I just don't see why Blanche should shove
a broken bottle in Stanley's face.
Couldn't she just take his abuse
with gentle good humor?
Marge, your ride's here.
Homer, it'll just be
a few minutes more!
#You're a dame
and I'm a fella #
# Stanley, stop
or I'll tell Stella #
Marge. Marge! I'm asking
For white-hot rage...
and you're giving me
a hissy fit.
Marge, can I get some change
for the candy machine?
- Oh, here!
- [ Clattering ]
Hey, there's
some quarters in here.
I just don't see
what's so bad about Stanley.
[ Grunting ]
Stanley is thoughtless,
violent and loud.
Marge, every second
you spend with this man...
he is crushing
your fragile spirit.
You can't let that happen.
[Yelling]
Whoo-hoo!
Come to papa.
Marge, I'll be
out in the car.
#All I want is one embrace #
- [Car Horn Honking]
- Marge, move it or lose it.
# I'll twist this bottle
in your face #
Aaah!
Hallelujah!
I've done it again!
Ned, you're supposed
to overpower her.
I'm trying. I'm trying.
[ Straining ]
- Salt me.
- [ Southern Accent ] Here you are, Homer.
What the-- Why are you
talking like that?
The play's tomorrow night.
[ With Accent ] I've got to stay in character.
- [ With Accent ]
Would it help if I talked like this too?
- It might.
[ Cockney Accent ]
An' I'll talk like 'is. Bob's yer uncle, mate.
That really
doesn't help, Bart.
Big Daddy, would y'all mind passin'
a lil' ol' biscuit?
Can I slog off school tomorrow?
Got a pain in me gulliver.
I'm livin'
in a cuckoo clock!
Oh, see you later, kids.
I've got to go rehearse with Ned.
But, Marge,
what about dessert?
For God's sakes, you can pull the lid off
your own can of pudding!
Fine. I will!
[ Screeches ]
Oh, no.
My pudding
is trapped forever!
So I can open my own can
Of pudding, can I?
Shows what you know, Marge.
Marge!
Hey, Marge!
Keep yelling,
you big ape.
Aren't you being
a little hard on old Homie?
Oh, forget about him.
Let's rehearse the bottle scene.
Oh! Let's not
and say we did. Hmm?
- [ Muttering Lines ]
- So, what time does this play start?
- Why? Are you going?
- Well, I gotta go, don't I?
I'm sure you won't enjoy it.
There's nothing about bowling in the play.
- Oh, wait, there is.
- Probably not much of it.
Why can't you be
a little more supportive?
'Cause I don't care, okay?
I can't fake an interest in this...
and I'm an expert at faking
an interest in your kooky projects.
- What "kooky projects"?
- You know, the painting class...
the first aid course,
the whole Lamaze thing.
Why didn't you tell me
you felt this way?
You know I would never do anything
to hurt your feelings.
Good night.
[ Snores ]
[ Groans ]
Playing nicely, little humans?
Good, good.
Hello, Maggie.
Poor little "dummard."
####[Action Movie Theme]
Hey, kids!
I'm flame-retardant.
[ Laughs ]
[Footsteps Approaching]
[ Gasps ]
If I break, buy a new one.
[Laughs]
- [Shatters]
- [ Gasps ]
[ Squealing ]
Maggie, time to go to the--
[Screeches]
[ Loud Sucking ]
[ Shudders ]
Babies.
Perhaps we are all
A little mad...
we who don the cap and bells
and tread beneath the proscenium arch.
But tonight, you will all be transformed
from dead-eyed suburbanites...
into white-hot grease fires
of pure entertainment!
Except you.
You're not working out.
- I'll be playing your part.
- Drag.
- [Murmuring]
- ####[Piano: Intro]
# Long before the Superdome #
#Where the Saints
of football play#
# Lived a city
that the damned call home #
# Hear their hellish #
# Rondelet #
[ Creaking ]
####[Orchestra]
# New Orleans #
# Home of pirates
drunks and whores #
# New Orleans #
# Tacky, overpriced
souvenir stores #
# If you wanna go to hell
you should take that trip #
#To the Sodom and Gomorrah
on the "Mississip" #
# New Orleans #
# Stinking, rotten
"vomity" vile #
# New Orleans #
# Putrid, brackish
maggoty, foul #
# New Orleans##
# Crummy, lousy
rancid and rank#
# New Orleans #
[Woman]
What's the matter, honey? Are you lost?
[Marge]
I'm lookin' for my sister, Stella.
- [Lisa] It's Mom!
- Huh?
My name
is Blanche DuBois.
####[Jazz]
# I thought my life
would be a Mardi Gras #
#A never-ending party#
Ha!
# I'm a faded Southern dame #
#Without a dime ##
I'm collecting
for the Evening Star.
Come here.
I want to kiss you...
just once, softly
and sweetly on your mouth.
####[Orchestra]
# I am just
a simple paperboy#
# No romance do I seek#
# I just wanted 40 cents #
# For my deliveries
last week#
#Will this
bewitching floozy#
# Seduce this humble newsie #
# Oh, what's a paperboy to #
- # Do #
- ####[Ends]
Whoo-hoo!
- ####[Orchestra]
- Stella!
Stella!
# Can't you hear me yell-a #
#You're puttin' me
through hell-a #
# Stella ##
Stella!
Oh! Oh!
Cool.
She can fly.
I think it's supposed to symbolize
her descent into madness.
- Oh! Oh! Oh!
- ####[Fades]
Whoever you are,
I have always depended...
on the kindness
of strangers.
- ####[Orchestra]
- #You can always depend on
the kindness of strangers #
#To buck up your spirits
and shield you from dangers #
# Now here's a tip from Blanche
you won't regret #
#A stranger's just
a friend you haven't met #
#You haven't met ##
- Streetcar!
- ####[Ends]
Yea!
Ah!
[ Chuckles ]
[ Together]
Yea!
You people out there,
you're the stars.
Cool!
Hey, look at me.
I'm Blanche DuBois.
- Mom!
- [ Grunts ]
- Way to go, Mom!
- Everybody was cheering for you!
- Almost everybody.
- Kids, wait in the car.
I want to talk to your mother
about this play thing.
[ With Accent ] Lookin' for a spot off un
with the missus, hey, guv'nor?
Shut up, boy.
Marge, you were terrific.
Oh, come on, Homer.
By the end, you were so bored...
you could barely
keep your selfish head up.
I wasn't bored.
I was sad.
It really got to me
how that lady, uh, um--
- You know which one I mean. You played her.
- Blanche.
Yeah.
How Blanche was sad.
And how that guy Stanley
should have been nice to her.
Yeah?
Go on.
I mean,
it made me feel bad.
The poor thing ends up being
hauled to the nuthouse...
when all she needed was for that big slob
to show her some respect.
Well, at least that's
what I thought.
I have a history of missing
the point of stuff like this.
No, Homer,
you got it just right.
Hey, you know,
I'm a lot like that guy.
- Really?
- Yeah, like when I pick my teeth
with the mail and stuff.
Well, maybe just a little.
- [ People Chattering ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net