[Chorus]
## The Simpsons ##
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Revving ]
-[Crowd Gasps]
- Hey! Hey--
- [ Groans ]
- [Man]Hey, Lance Murdock...
you just jumped
16 blazing school buses.
What are you going
to do now?
[ Straining ]
I'm goin' to Duff Gardens!
[Announcer]
Duff Gardens! Home of the Whiplash!
[Man #2]
To be completed in 1994.
[ Groaning, Screams ]
[ Shrieking ]
[Announcer Continues]
And the Washing Machine!
[ Gurgling, Choking ]
[ All ]
Wow!
See the happiest fish
in the world...
at our fabulous Beerquarium!
[ Thump ]
[ Moaning ]
[ Belches ]
Bart, warm up the car.
We're going to Duff Gardens!
[ Bart, Lisa ]
Yea!
Now, what do we say when
we get to the ticket booth?
[ Bart, Lisa ]
"We're under six."
And I'm a college student.
Heh, heh!
Kids, I have
some bad news.
Your Great-Aunt Gladys has...
passed on.
Gladys. Gladys.
'Bout yay high, blue hair,
big dent in her forehead?
No, honey. Gladys looked
more like your Aunt Patty.
[ Shudders ]
Oh, yeah. There she is.
The funeral's in Littleneck Falls.
Looks like we'll have
to go to Duff Gardens another time.
- We understand.
- No use complainin' about
something you can't change.
[ Whining ] But I wanna go
to Duff Gardens right now!
- Oh, Homer, quit pouting.
- [ Whining ] I'm not pouting.
I'm mourning.
Stupid dead woman.
## [ Singing Children's Song ]
- ## [ Continue Singing ]
- If you don't mind!
We're on our way
to a funeral.
## [ Sings Macabre Song ]
- ## [ Singing ]
Homer!
- [ Engine Stops ]
- [ Door Opens, Closes ]
Patty, Selma, I'm sorry.
Mm! He's hugging us.
What do we do?
just close your eyes
and think of MacGyver.
[ Straining, Grunts ]
- [ Grunts ]
- Hey, Homer! This luggage is crushing me.
Hey, you don't hear
Lisa complaining.
[ Muffled Whimpering ]
I can't believe
Aunty Gladys is really gone.
Her legend will live forever.
[ Thinking ] Yeah. The legend
of the dog-faced woman.
[ Laughing ] Legend
- Oh, that's good!
- Homer! That's very rude of you.
- What? D'oh!
- Can we please stop somewhere? My butt's asleep.
[ Buzzing ]
[ Tires Screech ]
[Utensil Clatters]
[ Slurping ]
All right.
I'm almost there.
It-- Ohh!
- Another place mat, sir?
- Please.
While we're waiting
for our pie...
let's take a minute
to remember Great-Aunt Gladys.
Wait a minute.
That was Prince of Tides.
Five, six...
seven, eight.
- What are you kids playing?
- Counting game.
- Oh, that's nice.
- Nine...
1 0.
[Minister]He was a good man.
He was a kind man.
He gave to his community...
- and asked little in return.
- [Footsteps]
- He never--
- [ Whispering, Indistinct ]
That's a woman?
Dear Lord!
[ Embarrassed Chuckle ]
Well, I guess...
most of what I said
can be salvaged.
Take a seat, bozo.
And that eulogy better not
show up on the bill.
I'll keep this short.
Gladys lived alone,
died alone.
I guess you could say
she was a role model for Selma and me.
- She wasn't a rich woman--
- [ People Muttering ]
but she was rich in spirit.
Forgot my hat.
Don't hassle the dead, boy.
They have eerie powers.
- [ Scoffs ]
- [ Thinking] I thought this thing
was gonna be catered.
Boy, am I hungry.
I mean I'm really,
really hungry.
It's just not fair, damn it!
[ Sobbing ]
[ Comforting Sigh ]
Good-bye, Great-Aunt Gladys.
I wish I'd made
more of an effort...
to get to know you
these last few years.
[Throaty Voice]
Don't worry about it.
[ Screaming ]
[ Laughing ]
- [Door Opens]
- I'm Lionel Hutz...
executor of Ms. Bouvier's estate.
She left a video will,
so I earn my fee...
simply by pressing
this "Play" button.
Pretty sweet, hey?
I would like to start by reading
a passage from Robert Frost.
"Two roads diverged
in a yellow wood, and--"
- [ Tape Squealing On Fast-forward ]
- Homer!
All in favor
of skipping the poem.
- Thank you.
- [ Tape Squealing ]
"And that has made
all the difference."
Now let's get down
to business.
[Hutz's Voice]
To my executor, Lionel Hutz...
I leave $50,000.
Mr. Hutz!
You'd be surprised how often that works.
You really would.
To Marge,
I leave my collection...
of potato chips
that resemble celebrities.
They're all here--
Otto von Bismarck...
Maurice Chevalier,
right up to Jay Leno.
These chips were my children,
Marjorie.
- Take special care of them.
- [ Crunching ]
Uh-oh.
To my sister, Jackie, I leave
my pet iguana, JubJub.
Why didn't she just leave me
the bowel obstruction that killed her?
To my dear childless nieces,
Patty and Selma...
I leave my grandfather clock
and these words:
Don't die lonely like me.
Raise a family,
and do it now.
[Echoing]
Now! Now! Now!
Hey, a grandfather clock.
Not bad.
[Chiming, Ticking]
- [Snoring]
- Aunt Gladys was right.
There's something missing
in our lives.
Don't worry. We'll get
that "barking dog" record tomorrow.
Patty, I want a baby.
[ Rattling ]
- What do I do here?
-Just tell us about yourself.
Well, I wanna have a baby
before it's too late.
You're lookin' at
a free lunch, boys.
Come and get it.
[ Imitates Tiger Snarl ]
- [ Scottish Accent ] Ach! Back
to the loch with you, Nessie.
- [Cassette Clatters]
[Gypsy Accent]
One drop of this love potion...
and you will have
any man you desire.
Really? What are
the magical ingredients?
[ Without Accent ]
Mostly corn syrup, a little rubbing alcohol.
You'll be lucky if it doesn't
Make your hair fall out actually.
Oh!
- [Cash Register Clicking]
- [ Beeps ]
- [ Squeaky, Breaking Voice ] Paper or plastic?
- You decide.
So, wearing a belt, are ya?
- Yep.
- No suspenders for you.
I guess not.
Orange is really your color.
- They make us wear this.
- Shall we continue this conversation over dinner?
Uh, I'm not allowed
to date customers.
- It's store policy.
- No, it isn't. Ow!
- Shut up, Arnold.
- No. Go for it, man.
"R," "Q," "G."
- [Pointer Tapping]
- Question mark. Smiley face.
Next. Wait a minute.
It says here you're single.
Did I do wrong?
- ####[Romantic Violin]
- Cold biscuits...
chicken...
yellow... mailman.
- You're reading the wine list, sir.
- Very good.
I don't know how
to thank you for dinner.
Use your imagination.
Mmm!
[ Children Whimpering, Grunting ]
- Aah!
- [Thump]
Ew! Get outta my car.
This isn't my house.
- [ Announcer] Come to Duff Gardens...
- [ Riders Shrieking ]
where roaming gangs aren't
a big problem anymore.
Now featuring
the clean-shaven sounds...
of Hooray For Everything.
- [ All ] Hey, kids! Take a walk on the wild side!
- ## [ Singing Pop ]
## [ Vocalizing ]
Yeah!
Can we go to Duff Gardens
this weekend?
Sure.
Unless another aunt dies.
- [Door Slams]
- Selma, your date's over already?
Yeah.
I was so depressed.
I ate ajar of expired olives.
[ Sighs ]
I guess I'll never have a baby.
Aunt Selma,
this may be presumptuous...
but have you ever considered
artificial insemination?
[ Wheezing Laugh ]
Boy, I don't know.
You gotta be pretty desperate
to make it with a robot.
- [ Whispering, Indistinct ]
- I knew that.
How do I know
I'm getting quality?
Don't worry. Our donors have to pass
a rigorous screening process.
All done!
- Thank you.
- Always a pleasure.
- What a beautiful little girl.
- [ Loud Belch ]
[ Babies Belching ]
[Belching Continues, Echoing]
[Marge]
"101 Frozen Pops. "
A Nobel Prize winner!
An NBA All-Star!
Ooh! One of the Sweathogs.
I checked.
It's not Horshack.
- Oh. Are you sure you wanna have a baby this way?
- Yeah.
You've had some pretty bad experiences
ordering out of catalogs.
Remember that mail order husband?
[Knocking]
Ooh! You look just
like your picture.
Sorry. My mind's made up.
I wanna have a kid, and this is
the only way I can do it.
Why do you wanna
have a baby so bad?
I got a lotta love to give...
and, right now,
my only outlet is my ham radio.
- [ Static ]
- [ Man Speaking Foreign Language ]
- Are you sure you've thought this through?
- [ Slurping ]
A child can really
Change your life.
- You'll have to give up smoking.
- I'll chew.
- No man will want you.
- All I got now is sperm in a cup.
- [ Groaning ]
- [Footsteps Running]
- Come on! Come on! Time to get up!
- We wanna go to Duff Gardens!
- [Lisa] Time to go to Duff Gardens!
Oh, great.
Dad's dead.
[ Groaning ]
[ Gasps ] Have you been eating
that sandwich again?
Sandwich.
Geez, we hardly made a dent
in that 1 0-foot hoagie.
Well, I'll give it a good home.
Mm!
You've been
eating that thing for a week.
I think the mayonnaise
is starting to turn.
Two more feet, and I can
fit it in the fridge.
Homer, I found this
behind the radiator.
I really think
you should throw it away.
Suggestion noted.
Marge, I'd like to be alone
with the sandwich for a moment.
Are you going to eat it?
Yes.
- [ Groaning ]
- You look terrible.
I don't care.
I'm going to Duff Gardens.
[Body Thuds On Floor]
S-S-So cold!
Your lips are turning blue.
I think you better stay home.
No! Duff Gardens.
- Hurrah!
- [ Horn Honking ]
We really appreciate you
taking the children on such short notice.
We'll have fun,
won't we, kids?
To get to Duff Gardens,
I'd ride with Satan himself.
That's the spirit.
See ya tonight.
- Good-bye, Dad. Don't eat any solids.
- But I love solids.
- Won't be any fun without ya, Dad.
- [ Engine Starts ]
[ Bart, Lisa, ]
Yea!
This is all your fault!
It--
Oh, how can I
stay mad at you?
- Mm!
- [ Whimpers ]
- There it is!
- The Duff Beeramid.
"The Beeramid contains
so much aluminum...
"it would take
five men to lift it.
Twenty-two immigrant laborers
died during its construction."
[ Scoffs ] Plenty more
where that came from.
[ People Chattering ]
- [Children Cheering]
- [ Gasps ] Look! It's the Seven Duffs!
[Bart] There's Tipsy,
and there's Queasy.
[Lisa] There's Surly
and Remorseful!
Hey! Take a picture. It'll last longer.
Get outta here.
[ Mechanism Humming ]
Fourscore and seven years ago...
we took the finest
hops and barley...
to brew a refreshing,
full-bodied lager.
Ahh!
## [ Imitating Hip-hop Beat ]
## [ Rapping ]
## [ Ends Rapping ]
## [ Imitating Hip-hop Beat ]
- This is a disgrace.
- Settle down.
Anything this bad
has to be educational. Bart!
Let's see if they wore
underwear back then.
- Yeah!
- [ Electricity Crackling ]
- Do you feel any better?
- No.
- [ Slurping ]
- What are the odds of getting
sick on a Saturday? 1 ,000-to-1 .
Well, to cheer you up,
I rented a couple of videos.
"Boxing's Greatest Weigh-Ins"
and "Yentl. "
- Yentl? What's that?
- It deals with a bookish young woman's efforts...
to enter rabbinical school.
- Sounds great!
- Oh, my God! You're delirious.
Hmm.
"Beer goggles. See the world
through the eyes of a drunk!"
Wow!
[ Sultry Voice ]
You're charming the pants off of me.
- What did you say, Aunt Selma?
- I said take off those damn glasses!
Oh! This looks like fun.
A bench.
Kids, what do ya say...
you go get your Aunt Selma
a beer smoothie?
- A beer smoothie? Not again.
- We gotta go.
- We got more stuff to do.
- You've already had four of 'em.
[ Chattering ]
[ Growling Sigh ]
Hey, man, if the line's this long,
it's gotta be good.
Get bent.
[Man In Movie]
What's going on here?
Oh, Yentl.
I might have known.
That Yentl
puts the "she" in yeshiva.
Hmm. Well,
you've cooled down.
That's what you think.
[ Imitates Tiger Growl ]
[ Chuckling ]
You know,
I rented another tape...
in case you felt better.
"The Erotic Adventures
of Hercules. "
- With Norman Fell as Zeus.
- Whoo-hoo!
## [ Animatronic Dolls
Singing Repetitious Theme ]
## [ Continue Singing ]
- I wanna get off!.
- You can't get off.
We have five more
continents to visit.
Hey, Lise, I dareya
to drink the water.
I'm not sure
that is water.
Chicken.
[ Clucking ]
- Quit it, Bart. Quit it!
- [ Continues Clucking ]
- Quit it! Quit it!
- Bart, be quiet!
Lisa, drink the water!
[ Groaning ]
####[Dolls Singing]
####[Song Echoing]
They're all around me!
No way out!
[ Hysterical Laugh ]
- No way out, I tell you!
- What's wrong?
Now, you just
Put your head right here.
[ Growling ]
Aaaaah!
Ha-ha! Ha-ha!
- Hercules! The Cyclops tore off my clothes.
- [ Laughing ]
[ Marge, Homer Giggling ]
- ####[Dolls Singing]
- [ Gibbering ]
####[Singing Continues]
Bart! Lisa!
####[Festive]
Ahh!
## [ Humming ]
I can see the music.
Mitch, you're doin'
a bang-up job.
[ Squeaky, Breaking Voice ]
Thank you, sir.
[ Laughing ]
Whoa. That isn't good.
[ Screaming ]
Stop the ride!
I'll have to ask my supervisor.
- Better stop it.
- [ Ride Stops ]
- Can't you do something?
- Hey. Surly only looks out for one guy-- Surly.
- Hmm. Sorry, Surly.
- Shut up.
- [ No Audible Dialogue ]
- [Selma]Don't blame these kids.
[ Sighs ]
It's not their fault.
I think their father
is missing a chromosome.
Miss Bouvier, while we
were rescuing this boy...
hoodlums made off
with three bumper cars!
- [ Electricity Crackling ]
- [ All Laughing ]
[ Bumping ]
And I don't think George Washington
will ever be the same.
[Jabbering ]
We found this one swimming naked
in the Fermentarium.
I am the Lizard Queen!
Give her this...
and this...
- [ Teeth Chattering ]
- and then these.
- Oh, thank you, Doctor.
- Oh, I'm not a doctor.
Come to Homercles!
[ Giggling ]
I can't. The beans will burn.
Homercles cares not for beans.
- [ Grunts ]
- Oh!
Hi, kids.
How was Duff Gardens?
Can't talk.
Comin' down.
[ Groans ]
How do you do it, Homer?
You take an ordinary bed sheet,
fold it around like this--
No. I mean raising kids.
I just couldn't cut it today.
All I wanted was
a little version of me...
that I could
hold in my arms.
Oh, JubJub.
When I went to pick him up, Mom was
trying to stab him with a hat pin.
Shh!
## [ Singing Pop Ballad ]
## [ Continues Singing ]
## [ Finishes Singing ]
####[Woman Singing Pop Ballad]
####[Continues]
####[Ends]
[Selma]
Oh, yeah!
- [ People Chattering ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net