[Chorus]
## The Simpsons ##
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[Troy McClure]
Live from Hawai's beautiful Molokai Island.
We're not just
For lepers anymore.
It's Carnival of the Stars.
I'm your host, Troy McClure.
You may remember me
from such film s as...
The Erotic Adventures
of Hercules...
and Dial "M" for Murderousness.
Tonight we'll see Angela Lansbury
walk on hot coals.
Excitement, she wrote.
[ Whimpering ]
How could someone
abuse their body that way?
[ Gasps ]
Moe, don't throw out that brine.
But first, a man whose inspiring battle
with Percodan addiction...
is soon to be
a movie of the week--
Krusty the Clown!
I'll be played by Jimmy Smits.
[ Chortles ]
Now he faces
his toughest audience--
three Siberian tigers.
Simba, on the ball.
- [ Growling ]
- Aaah!
- [Krusty]Not the face!
- Ah, they'll be chewing on him for a while.
## [ Up-tempo ]
¡Ay, ay, ay!
¡Lapolicía!
Hey, Homer.
Phone call.
Hi, Homie. It's really starting to snow.
I think you should come home.
But, Marge, Alan Thicke
is throwing knives at Ricardo Montalban.
- [Man On TV]Ow.
- [Chuckles]Sorry, Ricardo.
[Man On Radio]
Take it easy, folks. It's "snow" picnic out there.
[Man #2 Chuckles]
I "snow" what you mean.
[Man #1 Chuckles]
You're dead weight, Marty.
- [ Yelps, Groans ]
- [Crash]
D'oh!
Well, I got him
as good as he got me.
D'oh!
Now, before I give you the check,
one more question.
Uh, this place, Moe's, you left
just before the accident...
this is a business of some kind?
[ Thinking ]
Don't tell him you were at a bar.
[ Gasps ]
But what else is open at night?
It's a pornography store.
I was buying pornography.
[ Thinking ]
Heh-heh-heh. I would've never thought of that.
[ Snorts ]
'Fraid old Zeke,
he rides up here with me.
Can't trust a pig
with watermelons, you know.
[ Slurping ]
She'll go 300 hectares
on a single tank of kerosene.
What country
is this car from?
It no longer exists, but take her
for a test-drive and you'll agree--
[ Speaking Slavic Language ]
Put it in "H."
[Homer]Kids, if we buy a new car,
we get our parking validated for free.
Do you come with
the car?
Oh, you.
[ Giggles ]
- Do you come with the car?
- Oh, you. [ Giggles ]
[ Imitating Gunfire ]
[ Whistling, Imitates Explosion ]
Bart! That car belonged to Bonnie and Clyde.
Show a little respect.
Mm-hmm.
[ German Accent ] Our tireless safety engineers
crash-test over 1 ,000 cars a year.
Hey, wait,
That's not a dummy.
This exhibit is closed.
[ Gasps ]
The Batmobile.
Adam West!
Hey, kids. Batman.
Dad, that's not
the real Batman.
Of course I'm Batman.
- See, here's a picture of me with Robin.
- Who the hell's Robin?
Oh, I guess you're only familiar with
the new Batman movies.
Michelle Pfeiffer. Ha.
The only true Catwoman is Julie Newmar,
Lee Meriwether or Eartha Kitt.
And I didn't need molded plastic
to improve my physique.
Pure West.
And how come Batman
doesn't dance anymore?
Remember the Batusi?
[ Grunting ]
Nice meetin' ya. Just keep moving.
Don't make eye contact.
Ooh. [ Gasps ]
Wow!
just think what I could do
with that plow.
[ Chattering ]
Homer, I've got to sneak these valuable
artworks out of the White House...
but I can't get out of my driveway
because of these protesters.
Mr. President, those young people
are about to get a dose of reality.
[ Screaming ]
Ah, I can't afford it.
Pally, this doesn't cost money.
It makes money.
You make the payments
by plowing driveways on the side.
Well, I really should
discuss this with my wife.
Your wife?
[ Imitates Whipcrack]
What, you think I'm gonna buy a $20,000 truck
just because you make that noise?
[ Imitates Whipcracks ]
I'll take it!
I can't believe you bought that plow.
We can't afford it.
If you're gonna get mad at me
every time I do something stupid...
then I guess I'll just have to
stop doing stupid things.
- Good.
- Fine. I'll never ever do another stupid thing.
Good night.
- Oh, Homie. Didn't that hurt?
- [ Weakly] No.
[Homer]
Marge didn't reckon with these flyers...
and this flashy jacket.
[Wind Howling]
[ Gasping ]
- Oh!
- Forget it, Homer.
People don't
read these things. Watch.
Twenty percent off at Lullabuys.
just tell 'em
Big Baby sent you.
I know you can hear me.
I'm talkin' to you.
You sicken me.
I guess guys like us
just can't get a break.
Well, at least I can't
sink any lower.
Come back, diaper.
Come back.
Hi, Ma.
- ####[Organ]
- And now, to read from the Epistles of Saint Paul...
Homer Simpson.
[ Clears Throat ]
Dear Lord, in your infinite wisdom...
you know the number to call
when you need a plow is Klondike 5-3226.
Homer, this is really low.
Not as low
as my low, low prices.
- ####[Organ]
- [ Homer Grunting ] That's Mr. Plow.
Oh, I'm gonna lose my plow.
Dad, have you considered buying
cheap commercial time on Channel 92?
- Check it out.
- Arr!
Ninety sea chanteys
on three compact discs.
## [ Singing ]
Act now and get a bonus C.D.
Hornpipe Fever. Arr.
Hmm.
- Almost time for our commercial.
- Dad, who's watching TV at 3:1 7 a.m.?
Alcoholics, the unemployable,
angry loners.
[ Snoring ]
[ Gasps ]
Look! There we are!
It may be on a lousy channel,
but the Simpsons are on TV.
[ Gasps ]
Our driveway's snowed in.
[ Together]
Old Man Winter!
[ Cackling ]
That's right. I fill your driveways
with ice and snow.
What are you gonna
do about it?
Nothin'. That's what.
- [ Grunting ]
- Stop!
Mr. Plow!
Get out, you lousy... season.
All right. I'm going.
My head hurts.
I have to lie down for a while.
Yea!
Hello, I'm Mr. Plow.
Are you tired of having your hands
cut off by snowblowers...
and the inevitable heart attacks
that come with shoveling snow?
- Uh-huh.
- Then call Klondike 5-3226.
Call now and receive
a free T-shirt.
He could still surprise ya.
But I'm a real tightwad.
Can I afford this remarkable system?
Absolutely. My prices are so low,
you'll think I've suffered brain damage.
You are fully bonded and licensed
by the city, aren't you, Mr. Plow?
- Shut up, boy.
- [ Growls ]
- So, remember--
- ## [ Synthesizer]
## [ Singing ]
[ Steady Beep ]
[Homer]
Well, John Q. Driveway has our number.
Now we play the waiting game.
Ah, the waiting game sucks.
Let's play Hungry Hungry Hippos.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Plow.
Now my store can remain open.
Let's do it.
We're not prisoners anymore.
We're free!
We can go anywhere we want.
I'm cold and frightened.
Hmm. Hmm.
- Hmm.
- [ Groans ]
I'm afraid classes
maybe canceled today.
Look!
We won't miss a minute of school
thanks to your father.
Say your prayers, plow boy!
[ Groaning ]
Mr. Plow, for making it possible
for people to get where they're going...
without resorting to public
transportation or carpooling...
I give you the key to the city.
[Moe]
Here you go, Mr. Plow.
- A beer on the house.
- Wow, Moe!
You didn't even give a beer
to those freed Iranian hostages.
Ah, they shouldn't have
been there in the first place.
But Homer is a real hero.
I wish I was a hero.
Well, wishing
won't make it so.
You gotta pull up your diaper,
get out there...
and be the best damn Barney
you can be.
Here I come, world!
[ Yelling ]
- [Grunts]
- [Crash]
[Can Rattling]
- How do you think he'll do, Moe?
- I think he'll do just fine.
I was wrong about you
buying that truck.
I'm very proud of you...
Mr. Plow.
[ Chuckles ]
This might sound silly,
but just for a change, would you mind--
Cutting my nails?
Brushing my teeth?
No, no.
Could you wear
the Mr. Plow jacket?
just, uh, for fun.
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
## [ Singing ]
[ Low Chuckle ]
[ Alarm Buzzing ]
Ah, white gold.
[ Gasps, Stammering ]
[ Horn Blowing ]
Hiya, Homer.
Say hello to the Plow King.
Barney, you stole my idea.
Don't worry, Homer. There's nothing wrong
with a little healthy competition.
[Gunshots]
[ Cackling ]
Well, well,
If it isn't Mr. Plow.
[ Grunting ]
[ Yelling ]
Hey, Plow King,
save some for me.
Wow! Linda Ronstadt!
[ Grunting ]
Linda Ronstadt?
How'd you get her?
Ah, we've been looking for a project
to do together for a while.
## [ Country]
## [ Singing ]
[ Burps ]
How could you, Barney?
After all I've done for you.
"Lachrymose is to dyspeptic
as ebullient is to--"
Effervescent.
All right!
- Harvard, here I come.
- Psst, Barney.
- My dad's asleep. Want a beer?
- I don't know. The S.A.T.'s are tomorrow.
I've got two words for you.
Mellow out, man.
- Hmm? Hmm?
- All right. Just one--
if it'll get you off my back.
Hey! Where have you been
all my life?
[ Sighs ]
Thank you, Plow Kingaly-ding.
[ Chuckles ]
Flanders, I thought
I was your plowman.
Uh, Homer,
why don't you plow it again?
Forget it, pal.
I don't need your phony-baloney job.
I'll take your money,
but I'm not gonna plow your driveway.
Mr. West, you said
there was a job for me.
There was. When I called you--
45 minutes ago.
So long, Superman.
Your secret identity is safe with me.
[ Sputters ]
[Homer]
Ring, damn you. Ring.
- [ Rings ]
- Mr. Plow. That name again is Mr. Plow.
[ Man ] Hello, I'm calling from
Delinquent Accounts at Kumatsu Motors.
Oh, you want the Mr. Plow
who plows driveways.
This is Tony Plow.
You know, from Leave It to Beaver.
Yeah. They were gay.
- Oh, what am I gonna do?
- I think you should do a new ad...
one that's fresh and original.
I know. I'll do a rap.
## [ Imitating Beat Box ]
## [ Rapping ]
[ Lisa Groans ]
[ Bart Groaning ]
- Please.
- ## [ Ends ]
- Stop it right now.
- Promise you'll never do that again.
All right.
Mr. Simpson, I guarantee you...
we'll come up with a commercial
that can save your business.
You know those radio ads where two people
with annoying voices yammer back and forth?
I invented those. Ow!
Happens all the time.
## [ Singing Aria ]
Dad, was that your commercial?
I don't know.
The torch has been passed...
to a new generation of, uh...
snowplow people.
Come on. Give me the key.
- These look like teeth marks.
- I thought there was chocolate inside.
- Well, why was it wrapped in foil?
- It was never wrapped in foil.
Hardest hit by the blizzard
is Springfield's forbidding Widow's Peak.
Our own Arnie Pie
is on the scene.
Everything's snowed in.
All I can see is white.
Arnie, please.
The ski conditions.
Mayday, Mayday.
I think I'm flying into a mountain.
Tell my wife I love--
[ Chuckles ]
That's great, Arnie.
Hmm.
[ Disguises Voice ]
Hello. Plow King?
I was wondering if you could plow my driveway
on top of forbidding Widow's Peak.
I don't know.
I'd be up there all day.
I wouldn't be able to plow
any other driveways.
There's a $1 0,000 bill
in it for you.
Oh, yeah?
Which president's on it?
Uh, all of them.
They're having a party.
jimmy Carter's passed out on the couch.
Wow! I'll be right there.
Barney, I'd like to put a Spanish version
Of your jingle on my next album.
## [ Singing In Spanish ]
Yeah, you do that.
Well, I guess
you can plow my driveway.
But I wonder what happened
to the Plow King.
Well, I guess he just doesn't
respect his customers.
Oh, could you make sure
not to scrape my asphalt.
[ Softly]
Kiss my asphalt.
So I says, "Kiss my asphalt."
Hmm? Hmm?
Springfield's beloved Plow King...
is trapped.
- [ All Gasp ]
- Barney Gumble, shown here donating...
$50,000 to the Shelbyville
Dance Theater...
was caught in a sudden avalanche
on Widow's Peak earlier today.
It was captured on film by a camera crew
making the upcoming Fox special...
In Search of Bigfoot.
[ Man ]
Hold it, Bob. We can see your wristwatch.
- Oh, damn it.
- Hey, what's that?
- [ Burps ]
- [Rumbling]
Aaah!
This is all my fault.
I've gotta save him.
Homie, please,
don't go.
Hey, this old girl's as sure-footed
as a mountain goat.
[ Baaing ]
- [Thudding]
- [Baaing]
- [Loud Thud]
- [Weak Baa]
[ Groans ]
D'oh!
Oh!
[ Gasping, Yelling ]
[Whimpering]
Easy. Easy.
[ Inhales Deeply, Sighs ]
Ah, dying's not so bad.
I'll be reunited
with my loved ones--
my dad and that plant
I never watered.
[Rumbling]
Barney!
Homer, you saved my life,
and I'm not gonna forget it.
From now on,
we'll be partners.
Barney, that's great.
When two best friends work together...
not even God himself
can stop them.
[Booming Male Voice]
Oh, no?
The snow's melted.
We can go outside again.
I don't like the looks
Of those teenagers.
Could this record-breaking heat wave
be the result of the dreaded greenhouse effect?
Well, if70° days in the middle of winter
are the price of car pollution...
you'll forgive me if I keep my old Pontiac.
[ Chuckles ]
- [ Rings ]
- Y'ello.
[ Man ]
Hello. This is the Repo Depot.
I'm just calling to distract you
while we repossess your plow.
Oh, yeah?
How dumb do you think I--
- Oh.
- Oh, now, Homie, you have your health...
you have your best friend back...
and you do have that
certain special something.
- You mean--
- Mm-hmm.
## [ Singing Suggestively]
Our forecast calls
for flurries of passion...
followed by extended periods
of gettin' it on.
[Marge Chuckles]
- [ People Chattering ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net