[Chorus]
## The Simpsons ##
[Bell Ringing]
[Whistle Blowing]
[ Beeping ]
## [Jazzy Solo ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
D'oh!
[ Screams ]
[ Ringing ]
Oh, no! I can't see.
I'm blind. Blind!
Ha, ha! April Fools'.
[Rooster Crowing]
- Yeah. Yeah.
- [ Gagging ]
Ha, ha! April Fools'.
I've been keeping that carton of milk
next to the furnace for six weeks. Sucker!
You're goin' down, Homer.
I'm gonna fool you.
You talk better than you fool.
I'll fool you up real nice.
You couldn't fool your mother
on the foolingest day of your life...
if you had an electrified
fooling machine.
P.U!
[ Groans ]
Ah, what noble visionary
thought up April Fools' Day?
Like Halloween and Christmas, April Fools'
Day traces its origins to pagan ritual.
God bless those pagans.
April first used to be
the pagan new year.
- [Drums Drumming]
- [Chanting]Blood for Baal!
Blood for Baal!
[Lisa's Voice] The Christians changed their
calendar and ridiculed those who didn't.
- Happy New Year!
- Hi-ho, pagans.
New Year's was three months ago,
but here's a present anyhoo.
It's ram's blood
for your godless ceremony.
- [ Both Screaming ]
- [Ned Laughing]
- April Fools'!
- [ Laughing ]
[ Growls ]
[ Chanting ]
Now who's laughing? Now who's laughing?
And that's the story
of April Fools' Day.
- Dad, I was telling the story.
- Oh, right.
[ Neon Buzzing ]
Thar she blows.
The catch of the day.
Arr, har, har, har,
har, har, har, har.
Why, ye mutinous dogs.
From this day,
I be requiring hairnets.
- Arr.
Got to fool him before the day is out.
But how?
He must have a weakness.
Ah, beer, my one weakness.
My Achilles' heel, if you will.
Beer. Beer is the cheese.
But how to use it?
Whoo! It's a good thing that beer
wasn't shaken up any more...
or I'd have looked quite the fool,
an April fool, as it were.
- [Homer Chuckling]
- [ Evil Laugh ]
[Machine Rattling]
Hey, kid, that's for customers only.
Uh, did you know there's a guy outside
handing out free Stri-Dex pads?
- Wow! I'm in pizza-face paradise!
- Moron.
[ Rattling ]
¡Ay! No es bueno.
So thirsty.
Eh, what are you gonna do?
[ Growls ]
[ Water Boiling ]
[ Announcer] The following is
a public service announcement.
Excessive alcohol consumption
can cause liver damage...
and cancer of the rectum.
Mmm, beer.
[ Tearing ]
Hmm.
[ Chuckles ]
April Foo--
That sounded like an explosion
at the old Simpson place.
Forget it.
That's two blocks away.
Looks like there's beer
coming out of the chimney.
I am proceeding on foot.
Call in a code eight.
We need pretzels.
Repeat-- pretzels.
[ Panting ]
[Door Closes]
- Mrs. Simpson, I'm afraid your husband is dead.
- [ Gasps ]
[ Laughing ]
April Fools'. He's very much alive...
- although I'm afraid he may never walk again.
- [ All Gasping ]
## [ Singing ]
- Homie!
- Marge!
Mmm-mmm!
Homer has many, many
horrible problems.
These shadows are brain lesions
resulting from numerous blows to the head.
[ Grunts ]
Ohh!
[ Snoring ]
Wow!
Huh?
[ Screams ]
[ Gurgling ]
And his brain waves
are disturbingly erratic.
[Man] You are wired in
to the rest of your family.
You have the ability to shock them
and they have the ability to shock--
just testing-- Whoa!
Bart, how could you
shock your little sister?
My finger slipped-- Ahh!
So did mine--
[ Yelps ]
Bart, Lisa, stop that!
[Man]No, no! No!
No, wait a minute!
Wait! Wait! Folks!
Folks, if I could-- Uh, uh--
This is not the way to get healthy!
[Yelling Continues]
[Simpsons Yelling]
Mrs. Simpson, can you think of
anything to account for all this?
Mm, I have no idea.
Unless it was that time
he kept falling down the cliff.
I won't jump anymore.
I promise.
Oh, thank God!
Thank God! Thank God!
- I love you, Dad.
- I love you too, son.
You know, boy, I don't think I've ever felt
as close to you as I do right-- Huh?
Wha-Wha-- Huh? Huh?
[ Yelling ]
- Uhh!
- [ All Oohing ]
I'm gonna make it.
I'm gonna make it!
This is the greatest thrill of my life!
I'm king of the world!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
I-- [ Yelling ]
[Grunting, Groaning]
[Groaning]
[ Moaning ]
Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
[ Siren Blaring ]
[Yelling, Groaning]
Ahh-- Ow!
Hmm. That still wouldn't
explain what I'm seeing here.
- You look familiar. Have we met before?
- Um--
Clear! Clear!
Doctor, he's gone.
Oh! This is the part of the job I hate.
[ Gasps ]
You're a veterinarian?
That's right.
And for an extra $20...
I'll give Homer a tick bath
and then spay him.
- Here you go, Doc.
- Bart!
Shop around.
You can't beat that price.
You guys must have been
pretty worried about me?
Hey, we know you're tough, Dad.
Remember that time
you got lost in the forest?
This is a trap. It's gonna catch us
our dinner. Come on, boy.
Shh! Just watch.
Ooh!
Aha! Got 'em!
[Thud]
Okay, okay. This time I'll just go
into the bushes over there...
make a lot of noise
and flush out a rabbit.
- And when he comes out, you step on him.
- Right, Dad.
- [Chittering]
- Ahh! Get 'em off me!
Get 'em off me! Get 'em off me!
- [ Yelling ]
- [ Growling, Chittering ]
It's true.
You have good coping skills.
Your burgers are getting cold, guys--
Holy Moly!
[ Screaming ]
- [ Screaming ]
Huh?
And there's one Itchy and Scratchy cartoon
I don't think we'll ever forget.
[ Screams ]
- Why'd you bring that up?
- It was an amusing episode... of our lives.
Thanks for coming to visit me, Moe.
- I, uh, brought you a little present.
- No! No! Beer bring pain!
I can't stand to see him like this!
- [ Yelling ]
- [ Muffled Yelling ]
[ Grunting ]
He really needs a girlfriend.
Oh, Marge, what if I wind up
as some vegetable...
watching TV on the couch?
My important work
will never be completed.
Society's loss, I suppose.
But our marriage has been through
hard times, and we always pull through.
Huh? Huh? Hmm?
Marge! What a lovely surprise.
- You're here to see me, right?
- Of course.
- [Men Cheering, Applauding]
- [ Kiss ]
Hey, way to go, Homer!
Way to go!
Hey, what'll I tell the boss?
Tell him I'm going to the backseat
of my car with the woman I love...
and I won't be back
for 1 0 minutes!
[Cheering, Applauding]
- You can do it, Homer. Standup.
- I can't.
[ Sighs ]
He just won't budge.
I've tried everything.
Nothing can reach him.
Mmm. Chocolate.
[Thinking]
Chocolate. Chocolate.
Mmm!
[ Barks, Whimpering ]
Wow! Chocolate. Half price.
[ Moaning ]
Chocolate.
[Moaning]
[ Growls, Yelling ]
Can't breathe.
Sweet chocolate... cutting off air.
[ Gagging ]
Mmm! Nuts.
[Gagging Continues]
[Swallows]
Oh, yeah!
Poor Homer.
This world was never meant
for one as beautiful as you.
[ Drooling ]
[ Yells ]
Kill it! Kill it!
- Grampa, please. He's in a coma.
- Coma? Pfftt.
Why, I go in and out of comas
all the-- [ Snores ]
French toast, please.
- Is a coma painful?
- Oh, heck no!
You relive long-lost summers,
kiss girls from high school.
It's like one of those TV shows where they
show a bunch of clips from old episodes.
Mm. Yeah, well, anyway,
I wonder what he's thinking now?
[ Snoring ]
This man is costing
my health plan $5,000 a day.
I demand that
he die with dignity.
- [ Grunts ]
- Now, look, I'm the doctor here.
Well, I demand a second opinion.
- Hi, everybody!
- [ All ] Hi, Dr. Nick.
- [ Whimpers ]
- Oh, dear. I see no signs of life.
-Just to be safe, we better pull the plug.
- Yoink!
Mr. Burns, how can
you be so coldhearted?
You have no idea, woman,
what that man's put me through.
Uh, Mr. Burns,
I need to borrow some money.
- Oh, please, do go on.
- I know you're a good man.
And I have a dog that's very sick.
Oh, please, continue.
I thought maybe you-- Oh.
- Well, thanks for your time.
- Hmm.
I have an unorthodox solution--
a fantastic voyage, if you will.
[ Chuckles ] Three scientists--
one a beautiful woman--
will be shrunk
to microscopic size.
- They will then rendezvous
in Mr. Simpson's lower colon.
- [ All ] Ew!
Well, we have had a little trouble
finding volunteers. [ Chuckles ]
I wish I'd gotten
to know you better, Dad.
But there were times
when we really connected.
####[Saxophone]
Hi, Dad. Want me to cut out
this infernal racket?
- Oh, let me hear you play.
- Why?
Does a father have to explain?
Let's just share your gift, okay?
## [ Blues ]
Oh.
[ Sobbing ]
- ## [ Upbeat Jazz ]
- Huh?
Yeah! That's more like it!
Ho ho. Whoo!
## [ Singing ]
####[Singing Continues]
I wrote this for you, Dad.
## [ Mellow Jazz ]
Dad, I'm so sorry.
I know I haven't been
a perfect kid.
- [Rumbling]
- [ Gasps ]
- Why, you little--
- ## [ Action Movie Theme ]
What the-- D'oh!
- [Horn Honking]
- [ Laughing ]
[Jabbering Incoherently]
I know that I got you
mad once in a while.
D'oh! D'oh!
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
D'oh! D'oh! D'oh! D'oh!
And sometimes I got into trouble.
[Clanking]
- Bart, you can't go on like this.
- I know. [ Coughs ]
But you always
looked out for me.
[Marge]Homer, it's really coming down!
Could you check on the boys?
- [ Thunderclap ]
- They're fine.
And no matter what happens,
I'll never forget the advice you gave me.
Now come on, you're gonna
learn how to shave.
And finally, the little spot
under your nose.
Next, we take some toilet paper...
tear off some teensy little squares...
and stick one there and there
and anyplace you're bleeding.
There and there. Don't worry.
The blood'll hold it right on your face.
And now, some aftershave.
[ Yelling ]
Son of a-- Ohh!
And that's how we shave.
Dad, it's all my fault.
I shook up that can of beer.
It was just an April Fools' joke.
[ Beeping ]
[ Growling ]
[ Beeping Faster]
- Why, you little--
- [ Gagging ]
- Homie, you're all right!
- We're a family again!
- [ Gagging ]
- [ Growling ]
This calls for a celebration.
- We're all going to Hawaii.
- [ All Gasping ]
[ Laughing ] Gotcha!
It's April Fools' for two more minutes.
Dad, it's May 1 6.
You were in that coma
for seven weeks.
Uh-huh.
[ All Laughing ]
You lost five percent of your brain.
Me lose brain? Uh-oh!
[ All Laughing ]
Why I laugh?
- [ People Chattering ]
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net