Now to our own pie in the sky--
Bill Pie in the KBBL trafficcopter.
- So come in, Bill.
- Bad news, drivers.
There's an overturned melon truck
on the interstate. Oh, it's a mess.
There's lots of rubber neck in gandmelon
wrestling going on, so expect delays--
- Hey, doughnuts!
- Bart, there's one left, and it's mine.
Oh!
- Aw, Homer!
- Aw, Dad!
- Uh-oh, schoolbus!
Cool your jets, man. We're comin'.
You forgot the special lunches I made.
- That's okay, Mom!
- We got money!
- Now, just a darn--
- Aah!
Mmm.
Oh.
- This is Bill Pie, your pie
in the sky, saying good-bye.
-KBBL
Well, Maggie,
it's just you and me again.
This is KBBL,
K-Babble, all talk, 24 hours a day.
If you'd like to share your
embarrassing problem with our audience,
we invite you to call our therapist
of the airwaves, Dr. Marvin Monroe.
Our number is 555-PAI N.
Don't be afraid. Call now.
- Hello.
I'd like to talk to Dr. Monroe.
- First name, age, problem?
I'm Marge, 34,
and my problem is my husband.
He doesn't listen to me.
He doesn't appreciate me.
I don't know how much more
of this I can--
Save your whining for when
you're on the air, okay?
Okay, let's see.
Next we have Marge.
She's 34 and trapped in
a loveless sham of a marriage.
Hey, turn it up.
I love hearing those wackos.
- Tell me 'bout your husband, Marge.
- Well--
When we were dating,
he was sweeter...
and more romantic and 40 pounds thinner,
and he had hair,
and he ate with utensils.
-What was that last thing you said? Ah.
Isn't that your wife, Homer?
Don't be ridiculous.
My wife worships the ground I walk on.
Marge,
it's what I call "harsh reality time."
Your husband sees you as nothing.
- Oh. Okay. Well, thank you.
- No, no, no, don't hang up.
The pig has made you
into his mother.
You are not the hot love object
you deserve to be.
- Really?
- I'm as sure of it as I'm sure
my voice is annoying.
Tonight, the second
he comes through that front door,
you've got to tell him you're fed up,
and if he doesn't start loving,
you will be leaving.
Leave Homer?
- Don't use his real name!
- Leave Pedro?
- Can you be that honest?
- Yeah.
- You'll tell him right when
he comes home from work.
- Yeah!
- Say it likeyou mean it.
- Attagirl.
Come on, Bart. Not again.
- Where's your sense of humor?
- Moe's Tavern.
- Hello. Is Al there?
- Al?
- Yeah, Al. Last name, Coholic.
Lemme check.
Phone call for Al, Al Coholic!
- Is there an Al Coholic here?
Wait a minute. Listen,
you little yellow-bellied rat jackass.
If I ever find out who you are,
I'll kill ya!
I hope you do find
that punk someday, Moe. Fill 'er up.
Is eveything okay?
Usually you have a quick one,
some peanuts, beefjerky,
pickled eggs, and you're outta here.
Let's just say I don't feel
like goin' home tonight. Jar, please.
Hey, you can level with me.
- You got a domestic situation?
- You might say that.
My wife's gonna leave me
'cause she thinks I'm a pig.
- Homer.
- What?
- Marge is right. You are a pig.
You can ask anyone in this bar.
- What?
Hey, Barney, am I a pig?
You're no more of a pig than I am.
- Oh, no!
- See? You're a pig.
Barney's a pig. Lary's a pig.
We're all pigs.
Except for one difference.
Once in a while,
we can crawl out of the slop,
hose ourselves off
and act like human beings.
Homer, buy your wife some flowers and
take her out for a night on the town.
Candles, table cloth,
the whole nine yards.
Gee, a romantic evening.
Nah, she's too smart to fall for that.
I'm not done. After dinner,
the two of you are going to check
into the fanciest motel in town...
and not check out until
the next morning, if you get my drift.
I read you loud and clear.
Heh, heh, heh, heh!
- Wow, a quarter past 6:00.
- What's keeping Dad?
- Yeah, who'd possibly be late
on meatloaf night?
Uh, I'd like some flowers.
- What kind of flowers?
- You know, pretty ones, not dead.
We have some beautiful
long-stem roses.
- They're $55 a dozen.
- One, please.
- Hey, Mom.
- How 'bout some grub?
- Aaah!
Your
husband sees you as nothing, as nothing.
The pig has made you
into his mother, his mother.
You are not the hot love object
you deserve to be,
deserve to be,
deserve to be.
If he doesn't start loving, leave him,
leave him, leave him, leave him.
Marge, I, uh--
love you.
No, that's not good.
Marge, honey, I love you.
Oh. Um--
Marge, I love ya, baby.
Marge, sweetie,"hooney," honey--
Ah, this'll never work.
- I love you, Marjorie.
- Oh, Homer.
I love you too.
Mmmwha!
- A little predinner entertainment.
- Moe's Tavern.
- Is Oliver there?
- Who?
- Oliver Klozoff.
Hold on. I'll check. Oliver Klozoff!
- Call for Oliver Klozoff!
And I made reservations
at the Chez Paree.
But, Homer, it's so expensive.
It matters not, mon frere.
And after desserts,
we'll adjourn to our second-floor room
at the Offramp Inn.
Oh, Homer!
I feel giddy!
Wait. What about a baby-sitter?
- Oops.
- Not to wory.
Listen, ya lousy bum.
If I ever get a hold of you,
I'll cut your belly open.
Goodness. Must be a crossed wire.
- Rubber Baby Buggy
Bumper Baby-sitting Service.
- This is Marge Simpson.
- I'd like a baby-sitter for the evening.
- Wait a minute.
The Simpsons.
Lady, you've gotta be kidding!
- Rubber Baby Buggy Bumper
Baby-sitting Service.
Hello. This is Mr. S-Sampson.
Did your wife just call a second ago?
- No, I said Sampson, not Simpson.
- Thank God!
Those Simpsons,
what a bunch of savages!
- Especially that big-ape father.
- Doh!
Actually, the Simpsons
are neighbors of ours,
and we've found them to be a quite
misunderstood and underrated family.
Mom, you look so glamorous.
Well, tonight is a vey special night.
Your father is taking me out
for dinner and dancing.
- Dad dances?
- Like an angel.
Ba, ba
Ba-ba, ba-ba, ba-ba
ba-ba, ba, ba
Ba, ba, ba, ba-ba
- Ba-ba, ba-ba, ba, ba
ba, ba, ba-ba
- Work that body, Homer.
- You know, one day you'll learn
to move like your old man.
- Not if l can help it.
Son, there's not a woman alive...
who can resist a man
who knows how to mambo.
- You don't have a clue, do you, Dad?
- Out, boy.
- Out!
- What a grump.
Hm. Hm.
Hmm! Hm, hm.
Hmm? Hee.
Smooth as a baby's behind!
Ba, ba, ba-ba, ba-ba
ba-ba, ba-ba, ba, ba
- Precious, I think I hear the doorbell.
I think you're right, dumplin'.
Bart! Get the door!
Aye, aye, mambo man.
Oof!
- Ba, ba, ba-ba, ba-ba
ba-ba, ba, ba
- You must be the baby-sitter.
- Yes. I am Miss Botz.
- Just don't stand there, boy.
- Help Miss Botz with her suitcases.
- I can handle my own luggage.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
Here are the phone numbers of
the restaurant where we'll be dining...
and the motel where we'll
be spending the night.
You'll have to put Maggie to bed now,
but Bart and Lisa can stay up
for another hour.
Until then, they can watch
a tape from our video libray.
Oh, boy! The Happy Little Elves
Meet the Curious Bear Cub.
Oh, the Elves! The Elves!
- Bye, kids! Watch out for the boy.
Mmmwha! Bye, now.
Mmmwha! Be good.
- Mmmwha! Gotta go.
- Ba, ba
Ba, ba, ba-ba, ba-ba
ba-ba, ba, ba
Come, children.
Let's go watch The Happy Little Elves.
We've seen The Crappy Little Elves
about 14 billion times.
- Maybe we can watch some real TV.
- We're gonna watch the tape.
Aw! That's merely suggested
viewing matter, lady.
Mom lets us watch
whatever the hell we want.
I said you're gonna watch this tape.
And you're gonna do what I say,
or I'm gonna do something to you.
And I don't know what that is, because
everybody has always done what I say.
They all look so tasty,
but I think I'll eat
this one right there.
- Why don't you pick one
that's a little more frisky, sir.
- Why?
Well, when you choose one
that's floating upside down,
it somewhat defeats the purpose
ofselecting a live lobster.
Oh, okay. Then I'll take
that one there with the beady eyes.
Excellent choice, sir.
May I lead you to your table?
Oui, oui. After you.
And I'll be seeing you later.
Help! Help!
Faster, faster!
We gotta save Bubbles.
Oh, man, I can't take it anymore.
- But I want to see what happens!
- You know what happens.
They find Captain Kook's treasure.
All the elves dance around
like idiots. I puke. The end.
Bart, you're just like Chilly,
the elf who cannot love.
- Now for some real TV.
All right!
America's Most Armed and Dangerous.
Oh, no! Bart!
We'll have nightmares!
Relax. This is cinema verite.
When the brutal, slow-motion killing
starts, I'll tell you to shut your eyes.
The Cue Ball Killer should be considered
extremely armed and dangerous.
if you think you've seen him,
call 1 -800-U-SQUEAL.
Homer, you look just like a little boy.
- 'Cause I'm so care free?
- No, because you're wearing a bib.
- More champagne?
- Mmm.
Whoops. Time for a fill-up.
Garcon! Another bottle of
your second-least-expensive champagne.
The defenseless youngsters were tied up
and gagged in the living room...
while the bandit roamed
through the house at will,
stealing the valuable objects it took
the family a lifetime to shop for.
You know, Marge,
this is just like when we were dating.
Except for one thing--
no chaperone.
Ho, ho, hoo!
The Baby-sitter Bandit has left a trail
ofher daring nighttime robberies...
across the continental
United States.
She could be lurking anywhere,
about to descend upon another house
full of unsuspecting dupes.
- Eee!
- Wow!
In a moment, we will show you a picture
of the real Baby-sitter Bandit,
Miss Lucille Botzcowski.
- Remember, she may be using
a clever alias...
- Botz!
and should be considered
armed and dangerous!
- Aaah!
Run for it!
1 -800-U-SNITCH. No, U-SQUEAL.
- Oh, no!
Don't forget to tell me
when you see the Offramp.
Oh, thereit--
went.
No problemo.
We'll just get off at the next exit.
Bart.
Bart. Bart.
Hmm.
Time to brush your teeth,
wash your face...
and say your prayers.
Are you in... here?
Oh! Homemade pickled beets.
Go ahead. Take 'em all.
Seeing as no one was hurt, I think it
would be really silly to dwell on this.
- Come on! Come on!
- Finally!
Hello, vigilant viewer.
You have reached
America's Most Armed and Dangerous.
I'm calling to report the Baby-sitter
Bandit! She's in our house right--
Come on, Marge.
Let me carry you over the threshold.
Okay, but watch out.
Don't slam my head like last time.
Sheesh! Eleven years ago,
and you've never forgotten it!
- Don't muss my hair!
- Ohh! Oh! Oh!
Yi! Oh! Yeow!
- Whee! This is fun!
We know who you are, Miss Botz.
Or should I say Miss Botzcowski?
- You're the Baby-sitter Bandit.
- You're a smart, young man, Bart.
- I hope you're smart enough
to keep your mouth shut.
- He isn't.
You're crazy if you think you're gonna
get awaywith this. You can't--
I'm really not a bad person.
Here. While I finish up,
you guys can watch the rest
of your favorite videocassette.
Quiet, Bart!
Let's make the best of this.
Maybe I'll go slip into something
a little more comfortable.
Oh! Your blue thing with the things?
- You'll see.
- Well, shake a leg, mama.
Kidstuff!
Hardly worth it.
Lottajunk.
Soileds.
Stupid Sampsons.
- Maggie! Maggie!
Come here!
- Good-bye!
- Good-bye, eveybody!
- Bye!
- Yea!
Maggie,
wanna watch
The Happy Little Elves again?
Okay, but you have
to untie me first.
Oh, Homer!
Oh, ho, ho, ho.
- Oh, so you got out of your crib.
I guess you need
to be tied up too.
- Maggie, where are you?
- Maggie! Maggie!
- Heh, heh, heh.
Homer, would it spoil the mood
if I called home,
you know, just to check on the kids?
Homer, wake up!
There's no answer at home.
- So?
- So I'm worried.
I think we should go home.
All right.
I suppose my work here is done.
Heh, heh, heh, heh!
Hello, vigilant viewer.
How may we help you?
We caught her!
We caught the Baby-sitter Bandit!
She's tied up at our house right now.
- Ask if there's a reward.
- Is there a reward?
- If she's convicted, we get T-shirts!
- Yeah!
- How come all the lights are on?
- I don't like the looks of this.
- Miss Botz!
- Good Lord!
What have those little
hellions done now?
We're so sorry.
We're so sorry!
Please turn off the TV.
I can't tell you how chagrined we are
about all of this.
Oh, these things are heavy.
Just so there's no hard feelings,
here's double your pay.
- No, no, triple.
- Thank you.
- Mr. Sampson,
can I give you a bit of advice?
- Sure.
- Don't turn your back
on that boy for a second.
Ain't that the truth?
You know, one time he--
- Huh?
This way to the scene of the crime,
men! I got her tied up in the den.
Just a minute, young man!
I don't know what kind of shenanigans
you've been pulling this time,
but I just had to untie your baby-sitter
and pay her off so that--
Excuse me. Are you saying to the world
that you just aided and abetted...
the escape of the notorious
Baby-sitter Bandit?
- The what?
- The Baby-sitter Bandit.
Oh, uh, a-are you sure
this microphone works?
Uh, well, I wouldn't say I aided her.
This is on, right?
Because actually
it was quite a struggle.
Oh, Homer!
Have you ever seen a kung fu movie?
It was just like that.
But now I know her moves.
So, if you're listening to me, lady,
you'd better think long and hard
before tying something like this
on Homer Simpson again!
- Lord, help me.
I'm just not that bright.
Oh, Homer, don't say that.
The way I see it,
if you raise three children...
who can knock out
and hogtie a perfect stranger,
you must be doing something right.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Mmmmwha!
Honey, can we make up again?
Oh, my goodness!
- Shh!
www.tvsubtitles.net