Simpson and Delilah
The capital of North Dakota is
named after what German ruler?
-Hitler!
-North Dakota?
Bismarck.
-Hitler?
-I'm still beating you, boy.
The colors of the Italian flag
are red, white and what?
-Blue. Red.
-Green.
-Black, green.
-I was right!
We'll be right back with more
Grade School Challenge.
I used to think hair loss
was inevitable.
I found Dimoxinil,
the breakthrough in hair regrowth.
Breakthrough?
There's been a breakthrough?!
Dimoxinil can help me grow as
much or as little hair as I want to.
Hey, today I'm gonna do it.
For your free brochure,
send $5 to Dimoxinil.
Hair. Hair.
Just like everybody else.
Some women find bald men
quite virile.
Weren't you listening?
This is a breakthrough.
Not one of
these cheap-o sucker deals.
Allow me to present the Dimoxinil
action set.
A six-month supply of the drug, gravity
boots, scalp massager and a T-shirt.
-Great. How much?
-$1000.
A thousand bucks? I can't afford that!
We do have a product which
is more in your price range.
However, any hair growth
while using it will be coincidental.
A thousand bucks. Of all the rip-off
screw job, cheap joint....
Forget you, pal.
Thanks for nothing.
So I say, "Forget you, pal.
Thanks for nothing."
-I storm right out.
-That's telling them.
Out of tartar sauce.
They call this a portion?
Are you gonna use your sauce?
Dry fish sticks! This sucks.
-Stop whining, chrome dome.
-lf I had hair, you wouldn't say that.
Homer, don't be a sap.
Fill out some insurance forms.
Charge Dimoxinil to the company.
It's $1000.
Burns would can my butt.
Oh, $1000. So what?
So he has one less ivory
back scratcher.
You pay into the insurance fund.
What do you get?
Nothing. The newsletter.
Why get nothing while a guy who
loses a finger hits the jackpot?
You got me.
I'd like to charge that Dimoxinil
stuff to my health insurance.
I don't know who
put you up to this...
...but no insurance plan covers
something as frivolous as Dimoxinil!
Meet me in the alley in 15 minutes.
Come alone.
Dear God, give a bald guy a break.
Amen.
I have hair. I have hair!
I have hair!
Look, look!
Morning, Springfield.
Morning, Mr. and Mrs. Winfield.
Get a haircut, you hippie!
-Good morning, Moe's Tavern!
-It's the president.
-Good morning, everybody.
-Good morning.
Good morning, everybody!
Good morning, Springfield!
Dimoxinil!
Homer Simpson!
You haven't been here in 20 years.
-You got rid of the sideburns.
-Give me the usual.
He's much happier at work.
Just between us girls,
he hasn't been this frisky in years.
-I don't want to think about it.
-Daddy's home, sugar.
Come here, you.
Homie, my sisters are here.
Dinner with three beautiful women.
I must be in heaven.
This is Homer?
-Patty, stop drooling.
-Look who's talking.
You look different, Homer.
Lose weight?
You got a tan.
I know what it is, a new tie.
Pathetic morons in my employ,
stealing my precious money.
None of these cretins
deserves a promotion.
It's in the union contract.
One token promotion per year.
Wait. Who is that young go-getter?
Looks like Homer Simpson,
only more dynamic and resourceful.
Simpson? An unspoiled lump
of clay to mold in my own image.
Our new junior executive!
Bring him to me.
Homer Simpson, you've been
promoted. You're now an executive.
Take three minutes to say goodbye...
...and report to room 503
for reassignment to a better life.
Your "resume" seems in order.
Do you have any specialties?
Backrubs for harried executives.
I'll show you.
No, that will be fine.
Thank you, goodbye.
-Hello.
-How's my big, important executive?
Oh, Marge. Every woman I interview
makes kissy faces at me.
Hello, Mr. Simpson. I'm Karl.
-Hire him.
-I'll call you back.
Meeting in the board room
tomorrow at 2.
-Sit there and keep your mouth shut.
-Yes.
He thinks he's so big.
You don't belong here.
You're a fraud and a phony,
and they'll find you out.
-Who told you?
-You did.
With the way you talk
into your chest...
...the way you smother
yourself in lime-green polyester.
I want you to say to
yourself, "I deserve this.
I love it.
I am nature's greatest miracle."
Go ahead, say it.
Trust me, Homer.
-Say it!
-I deserve it.
-Louder.
-I deserve it!
-Shout it.
-I am nature's greatest miracle!
-Three weeks' vacation plus expenses.
-You got it!
Let's go shopping.
Beauty.
A man's suit should
make him a prince.
It should cry out:
"Here I am. Don't judge me,
love me."
-Do any of these suits do that?
-No.
I like this.
No, no. Stand naturally, Mr. Simpson.
Let it all hang out.
You, conceal it.
-Mom and Dad have been kissing.
-Gotta run.
-Happy anniversary, Homer.
-Our anniversary, are you sure?
Don't worry, this year you
have an excuse.
-With your job and--
-Happy anniversary.
Homer!
-Hello?
-Mr. Simpson, it's Karl.
Sounds like everything's arrived.
Wonderful.
-You did this?
-I didn't overstep my bounds?
-I love you, Homer!
-I love you, Karl-- Marge.
-Proceed, Smithers.
-Our first issue is low productivity...
-...and high accident rate.
-Any suggestions?
-A round of layoffs.
-Caffeine in the water cooler.
Those are my ideas.
You people don't think!
I promoted someone in touch
with workers.
-You!
-You mean him.
You. How would you
improve the situation?
Well, sir, for one thing...
...we had a problem with
fish sticks at lunch.
-What are you talking about?
-They chop up the fish into sticks--
I know what they are!
Get to the point.
You only get this tiny cup of sauce,
and I always run out.
-Stop wasting our time.
-Shut up!
Can't you see?
A happy worker is a busy worker.
Three cents' worth of sauce could
save us hours in labor.
I like the cut of your jib.
Let the fools have their tartar sauce.
Enjoy your tartar sauce, boys.
Give me your plate. Don't crowd.
Plenty for everybody!
Brilliant!
Who could've imagined that
reforms would pay off so quickly?
Accidents decreased by the number
Simpson is known to have caused.
Output is just as
high during his last holiday.
My dear, tired old Smithers.
Do I detect a note of jealousy?
It is time.
Give Simpson...
...the key.
Don't sit on that filthy
thing one second longer.
They've given you the key.
The key!
Stunning. Absolutely stunning.
I was watching the DuMont last night
and I caught a documentary on Rommel.
A man who got things done.
Towel, Simpson.
-Allow me.
-I said Simpson.
Sure thing, Mr. Burns.
Well done, Simpson.
Now, walk behind me.
Can do, sir.
" $1000. Dimoxinil.
To keep brain from freezing."
Now I've got you, Simpson.
Between your hair care and wardrobe,
we're not saving for a rainy day.
Rainy day? There's never
gonna be one.
There's not a cloud in the sky.
What does my little girl want?
An absence of mood swings
and stability in my life.
-How about a pony?
-Okay!
I want you to weave your
magic with my executives.
-A short speech, "Work. Work. Work."
-Okay.
Excellent. Set you
to your task, Simpson.
It's my sad duty to report...
...an executive has
bilked you out of $1000.
What? Blast his hide to Hades!
And I was going to buy
that ivory backscratcher.
-How?
-He charged Dimoxinil.
-It's a baldness cure.
-Thank you, professor.
I know what it is.
Make an example of this hooligan.
With pleasure, sir.
You've got to help me. Mr. Burns
wants me to make a speech.
-What do you want?
-I came by to tell you you're fired.
Our company doesn't look kindly upon
insurance fraud.
Clean out your desk by noon.
Wait, Mr. Smithers. Homer Simpson
is innocent. I did this.
What are you saying?
Mr. Simpson was unaware.
I take full responsibility.
Really? Well then, you're fired.
Whoever you are.
Here's your $1000.
-What do you care if this guy's bald?
-My reasons are my own.
Karl, you saved me. Why?
Have I done something extraordinary
here today? No.
I did what any soldier would do when
a grenade threatens his commander.
I threw myself upon it and bore its
terrible brunt.
Thanks, Karl.
I don't know what to say.
Just walk me to my car.
-Bye, Karl. I'm gonna miss you.
-Bye, Mr. Simpson.
-Did you bring an umbrella today?
-D'oh! No.
Here.
You're broke. You don't have Karl.
He's not here.
But you've got your hair.
Oh, that big speech!
-Hey, what's happening, hepcats?
-No way.
It's gotta be a fake.
It's like reals-ville, daddy-o.
What are you doing?
You little--!
Now I've got you!
Boy must die!
I love you, Dad.
Dirty trick. I won't kill you.
But I'll tell you three
things that will haunt you forever.
You've ruined me, you've crippled your
family and baldness is hereditary!
It is?
-Why don't you call the pharmacy?
-I don't have $1000!
But you do.
You've been squirreling it away.
Saving it for a rainy day, right?
Dad's taking this in a
less than heroic fashion.
Oh, Homie. I'm so sorry.
Got that speech in five minutes.
You're not going to hang yourself?
Dear Mr. Simpson...
...I've prepared your speech
on 3-by-5 cards.
-The big words are spelled phonetically.
-"Phonetically."
God bless you. You are one of
Springfield's special creatures.
Your obedient servant, Karl.
Good luck, sir.
That wasn't just a voice
inside my head.
-Why are you here?
-I came to say bye to the gals.
Thanks for the speech.
But I can't give it. Look at me.
-I haven't taught you anything!
-What?
The tartar sauce, the bathroom key,
drying your boss's hands.
It was never the hair. You did it,
because you believed you could.
-I'm a big fool.
-No, you're not.
-How do you know?
-Mother taught me never to kiss a fool.
-Karl.
-Now go get them, tiger.
And now with some insights, one
of the stars of our nuclear family...
...Homer Simpson.
Who is that old geezer?
What's he done with Homer Simpson?
He is Homer Simpson, sir.
You'd think I was crazy if I did this.
-He's crazy!
-Yet this company does this every day.
Bloated inventory,
outmoded production methods.
I can save this company millions
a year. How?
Jiko Kanri, the art
of self-management.
-This bald man has no ideas.
-lf it's a joke, I'm not laughing.
Telling us how to run things.
He doesn't have hair.
Mining uranium that could be
purchased on foreign markets.
The long-term benefits more than...
...offsetting the one-time cost,
for a net savings of $5--
Lots of money.
Mr. Burns' office, right now.
Dead man coming through.
Well, well. Our dashing, young
junior executive.
You made a mockery of our meeting.
I should fire you on the spot!
-But I'm not going to.
-Why?
-How old do you think I am?
-I don't know. 102?
I'm only 81.
You may find this hard
to believe, but in my salad days...
...my glory was a bright
shock of strawberry blond curls.
I was big man on campus until
my senior year...
...when I became as bald
as a plucked chicken.
I too know the sting
of male pattern baldness.
That's why I'm giving you
your old job back.
What? Oh, thank you.
Get out of here before I reconsider.
Better hurry up.
-Are you still awake?
-I've never been more awake in my life.
-What's wrong?
-Are you kidding?
I'm stuck in a dead-end job again.
The kids will hate me...
...because I can't buy the stuff
I promised.
And you're not going to love
me because I'm ugly and bald.
Oh, Homer. Your job has always put
food on our table.
-And the kids will get over it.
-And? What about loving me?
-Oh, Homer. Come here.
-What?
Come here.
www.tvsubtitles.net