Bart vs. Australia
Go, toothpaste. Go!
Move your pasty, white butt!
Come on, shampoo!
You can do it!
I won your stupid
bathroom-products race!
No fair. You only won
because you had the inside track.
If the water had spun
the other way...
It never spins the other way.
In the Northern Hemisphere...
...water always drains
counter-clockwise.
It's called the Coriolis effect.
No way.
Water doesn't obey your rules.
It goes where it wants.
Like me, babe.
Yes, Bart.
Why don't you try it and see.
I know I've seen it go the other way.
Ah, faithful toilet.
You'll prove me right.
I'm singing in the show...
Hot! Cold!
Hot! Cold! Hot!
Who's doing that?
Oh, for Pete's sake, Bart,
use the plunger.
Bart, water will only go the other way
in the Southern Hemisphere.
What the hell
is the Southern Hemisphere?
Haven't you ever looked at your globe?
See? The Southern Hemisphere is made
up of everything below the equa...
This line.
So down there in, say, Argentina...
...or Rand McNally,
all their water runs backwards?
In fact, in Rand McNally,
they wear hats on their feet...
...and hamburgers eat people.
- Cool.
Hello, Southern Hemisphere?
Which way does the water go
in your toilet?
Just a minute, I'll check.
Nuts.
Please to repeat again, and I will
translating for the el presidente.
Which way does the water turn
in your toilet?
I can't get a straight answer
out of this crazy hemisphere.
- Nuisance phone.
Bart, you can't actually call
these places.
Don't you know how expensive
international calls are?
Hello, operator,
I'd like to make a collect call...
...to Australia.
This is the international operator.
Will you accept a collect call from...?
Yes, this is Dr. Bart Simpson of
the International Drainage Commission.
- It's an emergency.
- If it's an emergency...
We understand drains in your area
have malfunctioned...
...sucking in people and whatnot.
- Willikers! That's awful!
Indeed. We need you to check
your sinks and toilets...
...and tell us which way the water
is going. And please stand clear!
The fixtures, they're all
draining clockwise, sir.
She was right.
Stupid Lisa, science queen.
Well, why don't you just check
your neighbors' drains. I'll hold.
Hey, Bart, the bakery caught fire
and all of downtown smells like cookies.
Want to go smell?
Yes. Yes, I do.
Hello, sir? Sir?
I've returned from the Quilamaguery's
place. They're draining clockwise too.
Draining?
I don't care about that anymore.
Are we in any dang...
"Burkina Faso"? "Disputed Zone"?
Who called all these weird places?
Quiet, it might be you.
I can 't remember.
- No, I'm gonna ask Marge.
- No! No! Why embarrass us both?
Just write a check and I'll release
some more endorphins.
Nine hundred dollary-doos?! Tobias!
Did you accept a six-hour collect call
from the States?
It was an emergency call...
...from the International Drainage
Commission in Springfield.
Oh, my God! There's nothing wrong
with the bidet, is there?
- Hello?
- Right, I'm calling all the way...
...from Squatter's Crog, Australia.
And I want to speak
to Dr. Bart Simpson right now.
- Hold, please.
- All right, but I don't...
Hello. Burt Stanton speaking.
I said, Bart Simpson!
What kind of company is this?
Bart Simpson's office.
Thank the great, good Lord.
Look, I was just saying...
One moment, please.
Who do they think I am,
some stupid Aussie drongo?
Bleeding Yanks. I ought to...
This is Bart Simpson.
Can I help you, ma'am?
Yeah...
My name is Bruno Drundridge, right.
You owe me $900, mate!
- No, you owe me $900!
- All right, you...
You're just some punk kid, aren't you?
You picked the wrong guy
to tangle with here, mate.
I don't think so.
You're all the way in Australia.
Hey, I think I hear
a dingo eating your baby.
That's it! I'm gonna report this
to me member of Parliament.
Hey, Gus!
I got something to report to you!
That's a bloody outrage, it is!
I'm gonna take this all the way
to the prime minister!
Hey, Mr. Prime Minister!
Andy!
Aye, mates. What's the good word?
"Mr. Simpson," blah, blah.
"Misrepresentation over telephone..."
"Sincerely," some Australian jerk.
Hey, I need that!
"Office of the Solicitor General"?
"Office of the Prime Minister"?
"Hopping Mad Collection Agency"?
What is all this stuff?
Nothing. Some stupid country
thinks I owe them money.
Bart, you better talk
to Mom and Dad about this.
Hey, guys? Just so you don't hear
any wild rumors, I'm being indicted...
...for fraud in Australia.
- That's no reason to block the TV.
Oh, my.
Bart, did you trick an Australian boy
into accepting a $900 collect call?
Yes'm.
There it is, Australia. I'll be damned.
Look at this country.
"You-are-gay."
Oh, my. Hello. I'm Evan Conover
with the U.S. State Department.
"Undersecretary for International
Protocol, Brat and Punk Division."
Unfortunately, your little escapade
could not have come at a worse time.
Americo-Australianian relations
are at an all-time low.
In the late 1980s, the U.S. Experienced
a short-lived infatuation...
...with Australian culture.
The Aussies thought
this would be permanent.
I know those words,
but that sign makes no sense.
Anyway, the down-under fad fizzled,
and the diplomatic climate...
...turned absolutely frosty.
Let's pretend we didn't see that.
And Bart's childish taunting
agitated the Aussies further.
Oh, he'll agitate you. He sure will.
- What can we do for you?
- It's too late...
...to pay back the money.
But as a sign of good faith
to our Australian friends...
...we'd like to imprison Bart
for five years.
That's tough but fair.
Boy, go with the man.
No, no, no!
I'm not gonna have my son go to jail
over some silly tiff with Australia.
You'll just have to find some
other country to have relations with.
You're sure, now?
The prison train is sailing.
Okay, I'm not hearing a lot
of support for prison.
There is one other option.
They'll drop the charges if Bart
makes a public apology in Australia.
All Bart has to do is apologize
and we get a free trip to Australia?
I can handle that.
I'm an expert at phony apologies.
- Bart!
- I'm sorry.
That's better.
We left at 1:30 p.m., Monday.
What time is it now?
It's 6:45 a.m., next Wednesday.
You may also be interested to know
that it's summer here, not winter.
What does that sign say? I thought
they spoke English in this country.
It says you can't bring in
outside plants or animals.
Any foreign creature you bring in
could upset the environmental balance.
Sorry, girl, I don't want to get in
any more trouble down here.
I'll pick you up on the way home.
Hey, are you, like, one
of those English guards...
...who can't laugh or smile
or anything?
No, sir! U.S. Marine Corps, sir!
Oh, yeah. This is the life.
Boy, next summer can you commit
some fraud in Orlando, Florida?
I'm way ahead of you, Dad.
Knock. Simpsons, I'd like you
to meet our ambassador...
...the Honorable Averil Ward.
Hello. Now, everything is all set
for Bart's apology.
Mr. Conover will meet you
at the Parliament House at 3 p.m.
Any questions?
- Do the toilets go backwards in here?
- No.
To combat homesickness,
we have a device that makes...
...them swirl the correct American way.
Sweet land of liberty
Of thee I sing
Hey, GI Joe, your sign's broken.
We're already in Australia.
Actually, sir, the embassy is considered
American soil, sir.
Really? Look, boy.
Now I'm in Australia.
Now I'm in America.
Australia. America.
- Australia.
- I get it, Dad.
Homer, that's enough.
Here in America,
we don't tolerate that crap, sir.
"Australia was founded as a
settlement for British convicts."
Lisa, watch your camera.
You call that a knife?
This is a knife.
- That's not a knife. That's a spoon.
- All right, all right. You win.
I see you've played
knifie-spoonie before.
Hey, give me one of those famous
giant beers I've heard so much about.
Something wrong, Yank?
No. It's pretty big, I guess.
- I'll just have a cup of coffee.
- Beer it is.
No, I said, coffee.
- Beer?
- Coffee.
Beer?
- C-O...
- B-E...
We'll meet you boys back here
for dinner. Good luck, honey.
Bart, I'm sorry I'm gonna miss
your public humiliation.
But the Walambaloo Dirt Monument
is just too exciting to pass up.
Hear ye! Hear ye!
This session will now come to order.
With the cooperation
of the U.S. Department of State...
...we have present today
one Bart Simpson.
I believe he has something to say.
Bart?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for what I did
to your country.
Well, you're free to go, Bart...
...right after your
additional punishment.
- Punishment!
- A mere apology would be a bit empty.
Let the booting begin!
- Booting?
- It's just a little kick in the bum.
What kind of a sick country would
kick someone with a giant boot?
Mr. Simpson, shush. Disparaging
the boot is a bootable offense.
It's one of their proudest traditions.
You sold us out, Conover!
Stand back or I'll boot
your prime minister! I'll do it.
So help me God, I'll boot him!
When will you Australians learn?
In America,
we stopped using corporal punishment.
And things have never been better.
The streets are safe...
...old people strut confidently through
the darkest alleys...
...and the weak and nerdy are admired
for their computer-programming abilities.
So like us,
let your children run wild and free...
...because, as the old saying goes:
"Let your children run wild and free."
Now, boy, run back to the embassy!
Back to American soil!
I'll stop them.
Oh, no, it's coming back this way.
That throwing stick stunt of yours
has boomeranged on us.
Hey, we can get away
in their pouches.
It's not like in cartoons.
Yeah. There's a lot more mucus.
Mom, you said I could
have one souvenir, right?
Well, I want a didjeridu.
That seems very noisy and expensive
for a souvenir.
Why don't you get this nice cap.
It's clever, just like you.
Get out! Get out! Shoo! Shoo!
Get out of here!
These bloody things are everywhere.
They're in the lift, the lorry...
...in the bon whizzer,
and the Malonga Gilderchuck.
They're like kangaroos.
But they're reptiles, they is.
We have them in America.
They're called bullfrogs.
What? That's an odd name.
I'd have called them chazwazzers.
Lisa!
Marge!
The Simpsons.
Well, they're not getting back in here.
I can't believe our government
would set up Bart like that.
I'm very angry
at the State Department right now.
Yes, but... Please, we're about to reach
a breakthrough with the Aussies.
Then it's agreed. During the bargaining
session, we each get two candy apples.
All right, one candy and one caramel.
Oh, for the love of criminy!
Give me that!
I know Bart did something wrong.
But he's my son...
...and I'm going to punish him myself.
Our countries
may have their differences...
...but as human beings,
I think we can all agree...
...there's no substitute for the discipline
of a loving parent.
He wants to talk to you.
Hello.
So we're in agreement.
She won't be allowed
near the phone again.
We did it.
We've worked out a compromise
that will allow both nations to save face.
We've argued them down to...
...a booting.
- What?
The prime minister just wants
to kick you once through the gate...
...with a regular shoe.
- I believe it's a wingtip.
No deal.
This is my son we're talking about.
Sure, he's not perfect,
but who is in this workaday world?
No. Mom, wait.
It's time for me to bend over
and receive my destiny.
Thank you, Bart. I promise
I won't make fun of you later for this.
Show them what American butts
are made of, son.
That's it, lad.
This is for the
Commonwealth of Australia.
And this is
for the United States of America.
I'm glad you're okay, honey.
But I wish you'd chosen a more
tasteful way to be patriotic.
I'm impressed you were able
to write so legibly on your own butt.
All right, mates, let them have it!
Hey, do we get to land
on an aircraft carrier?
No, sir. The closest vessel
is the USS Walter Mondale.
It's a laundry ship.
They'll take you the rest of the way.
Hey, look.
Those frogs are eating all their crops.
Well, that's what happens
when you introduce foreign species...
...into an ecosystem
that can't handle them.
www.tvsubtitles.net