Homer vs. Patty and Selma
This place is gonna smell classy
all week.
To Homer, the Wall Street genius!
Hey, Homer, how come you got
money to burn? Or singe, anyway.
- Yeah, what's your secret investment?
- Take a guess.
Pumpkins?
Yeah, that's right, Barney.
This year, I invested in pumpkins.
They've been going up
the whole month of October.
And I got a feeling they're gonna peak
right around January.
And bang! That's when I'll cash in.
To Homer!
And to Sergeant Pepper...
...who's growing out of
the middle of your back!
Barn, you gotta unwrap the
plastic before you smoke these.
- Hey, Homer.
- Yeah!
- Way to go.
I told you a hundred times, you gotta sell
your pumpkin futures before Halloween.
Let's not panic. I'll make the money back
by selling a liver.
I can get by with one.
Oh, how am I gonna tell Marge
we're broke?
I need a miracle.
My house is on fire!
Insurance to the rescue!
- Hello, Homer.
Marge, we had a deal.
Your sisters don't come here after 6,
and I stop eating your lipstick.
This is a special occasion.
Patty and Selma just got promoted
at the DMV.
Yeah, Homer. Let your wife
have a glimpse of success for once.
All right, that's the last straw.
Time to take out the trash!
But first, I'm going to have to ask you
to leave.
I'm sorry.
Homer doesn't mean to be rude.
He's just a very complicated man.
Wrong!
When are you going to wake up
and smell your husband, Marge?
You got some kids out of him.
But when the seeds have been planted,
you throw away the envelope.
I wish you wouldn't put Homer down.
He may not be a big success like you...
...but I can always count on him
to provide for the family.
Sweet, trusting Marge, I can't let you
down. I'll get some money somehow.
Hello, Vegas?
Give me a hundred bucks on red.
All right. I'll send you a check.
If only I could think of an invention.
Something that would
really make money.
Must concentrate and work
harder than I've ever worked...
Congratulations, Mr. Simpson.
This invention of yours has made us
all rich, especially you.
It's simple, yet ingenious.
And it fits right in the palm of your hand.
Every person in America now owns one
of these. In many cases, three or four.
Can I just get a look at that?
Why would you need to see it? You're
the genius who invented the product.
- But could I just...?
- Don't worry.
You'll get to see it just as soon
as we unveil our new ad campaign.
- Let me see! Out of the way!
- Homer!
Homer, wake up! There's still
a few minutes till our usual bedtime.
No! My invention!
- My money problems could've...
- Money problems?
Homer, are we in some sort
of fiduciary trouble?
Oh, Marge, my loyal wife...
...of course not.
And Lisa, my little princess.
And who could forget dear Rat Boy?
Rat Boy? I resent that.
Bart, I told you before.
Stop gnawing on the drywall.
What a day, eh, Milhouse?
The sun is out, birds are singing...
...bees are trying to have sex
with them, as I understand it.
It is a gorgeously fabulous day.
Marvelous, even.
So, what's your hurry
to get to school?
Nothing. What's your hurry?
That's enough, Bart. Fun is fun,
but if we're late, we'll get in trouble.
You're right, Milhouse.
Fun is fun.
Attention, students. It's time to choose
a gym class for the coming term.
So let's prove how adult we can be...
...by filing to the gym
in a calm, orderly manner.
Even though it's first come, first serve,
and the popular sports fill up fast.
Too many wee ones!
This gets uglier every year.
Any sign of Bart and Milhouse?
No, and if they don't get here soon,
it'll be T.S. For them.
I don't feel right.
Do you hear that, Bart?
That was the tardy bell!
"Truant! Truant! Truant!"
They'll all say!
Who needs him?
I can have fun all by myself.
It's all right? It's all right.
Sure, Homer, I can loan
you the money you need.
However, since you
have no collateral...
...I'm gonna have to break your legs
in advance.
Gosh, Moe.
I use these all the time.
- Couldn't you bash my head in?
- Hey, are you a loan shark?
Do you understand
how finance works?
Now, let's do this thing.
- Oh, no. It's P.E. Sign-up day.
- How could you forget?
They had signs posted
all over the library.
Better sign up for something fast, man.
Baseball just filled up...
So did tae kwon do.
There's only one class left...
...but it happens to be
the coolest one of all.
Ballet? Dancing is for girls.
Well, you should've gotten here earlier.
I need an extension
on my mortgage payments.
I understand, Mr. Simpson,
but according to our computer...
...your credit history is not good.
It says here that you've been
pre-declined for every major credit card.
It also says that you grabbed a dog
by the hind legs...
...and pushed him like a vacuum.
- In the third grade!
It all goes on your permanent record.
Sorry, but if you don't have
that money by tomorrow...
...the bank will take your house.
- Good luck finding it.
- I'll take the numbers off.
- We'll find a house with no numbers.
I'll take off my neighbor's numbers.
So then we'll look for the house next
to the house with no numbers.
All right, you'll get your money.
You're my last, last chance, bottom
of the barrel, Hail Mary, long shot...
...wish you would, but probably won't,
final resort to lend me money.
- We'll take care of you.
- Yes. Care.
Cut him a check
and get him the hell out of here.
What a wonderful dinner.
What a beautiful family.
Get a picture of me with this steak.
You're certainly in a good mood, Dad.
Well, Lisa, I managed to solve
a little problem today.
And to celebrate,
I'm going to tilt my chair.
Slanty.
Patty, Selma.
What are you doing here?
We thought we'd stop by
unexpectedly for dinner.
Now, bring us extra chairs
like a good "blubber"- in-law.
Time to fertilize the lawn.
A couple of 500-pound bags
should do it!
Be careful with my sisters' heads.
Their necks are brittle.
That's okay, Marge.
Nothing's broke.
Except Homer.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means...
It means these two fabulous babes
are staying for dinner.
Now, there's a stink
I could've done without.
This has been such a nice,
peaceful dinner.
It calls for a celebration. I'll make the
most international coffee in the house:
Montreal Morn.
All right, you had your fun,
now get lost.
Our fun hasn't begun yet.
We know something
you don't want Marge to know.
Now we own you,
like Siegfried owns Roy.
I'm sorry. All we have is Nescafé.
- I'm very, very sorry.
- Oh, Marge, Marge. You're just in time.
Homer's getting ready
to give us a foot rub.
- You are?
- No! L...
I'm giving them a foot massage.
At least let me have that.
You can start with the corns.
Then you can move on
to bunion country.
Okay. Steady, Bart.
Taking ballet doesn't make you
any less of a man.
All right, girls. Today we learn
the dance of the fairy queens.
You can either be a fairy or a queen.
It's wide open.
And what have we here?
A young man maybe who thinks
he can be the next Baryshnikov.
I don't wanna be the next anything.
They made me take this stupid class.
So he has fire in the belly.
But it will take more than belly fire...
...to be the next Baryshnikov!
- Look, Boris, I think ballet's for sissies.
Ballet is for the strong,
the fierce, the determined.
But for the sissies, never.
Now, put on this fuchsia-tard.
You are a fairy!
- Quitting time.
- On the way home...
...we'll stop at Moe's for a Zima.
- Maybe I'll stay and work overtime.
My sisters-in-law
are at my house again.
Homer, quit wallowing in self-pity.
Pull yourself together
and come get drunk with us.
- Is something wrong, Mr. Simpson?
- I don't like wearing tights.
But so many of your heroes
wear tights.
- Batman, for example. And Magellan.
- Look, I don't like this cootie platoon...
...and I never will. I'm out of here,
and I'm out of this stupid outfit.
Wait!
Joy of movement, increasing.
Love of dance, impossible to resist.
Toes twinkling. Look at me, girls.
I'm doing ballet. And I love it!
Am I wrong,
or did it just get fatter in here?
- Request permission to slink by.
- Permission pending.
First, light our cigarettes.
But you're already smoking cig...
- You're really pushing it.
- Come on, Homer.
You can't spell "obsequious"
without l-O-U.
- I'll have to trust you on that.
- Marge was always a good speller.
- Let's ask her.
- No! Don't tell Marge!
I'll be good. I'll be good.
Just for that, you have to crawl around
on the floor like the dog you are.
But... Yes, ma'am.
Now say, "I am Homer Simpson,
the lowly dog. " In a dog voice!
- I am Homer Simpson.
- Well, good. Jump, Homer, jump.
- What's going on in here?
- Absolutely nothing, Marge.
- What's that paper?
- What paper?
Homer, is this projection accurate?
- Did you borrow money from my sisters?
- I don't know, Marge.
I can't keep track
of all my wheelings and dealings.
- He blew your savings on jack-o'- lanterns.
- You told!
Sorry, Marge.
I never want to see you again!
You either.
Homer.
Homer, why didn't you tell me?
I was ashamed, Marge.
I failed you as a husband and a provider.
And at best, I was a B-plus dog.
I'll understand if you wanna sleep
on the couch tonight.
- How's Dad today?
- Not too good, Lisa.
- Frankly, he's underneath the table.
- Nobody make me any breakfast.
A man so deeply in debt
doesn't deserve it.
But I like to make you breakfast.
In that case, I'll just have French toast
with double butter and a side of bacon.
But no powdered sugar, I don't deserve it.
Maybe a little powdered sugar.
See that?
I started to do, like, a little arabesque.
But then I just fully went for it
and pulled off the demi-entrechat.
Not that I'm into that kind of thing.
Bravissimo, Bart!
Next week, class gives its first recital.
And you, you will dance the male lead.
Dance in front of my whole school?
What is it with you and ballet?
I know you have great conflict, Bart.
You love ballet.
Yet you feel the boys
will laugh at you, no?
No, I fear the girls
will laugh at me.
I fear the boys will beat
the snot out of me.
- Hey, Dad. What you doing?
- Daddy has very important work to do.
He's looking through the want ads
to find a part-time job.
Dad, that's a gag paper
we got at the carnival.
No wonder I didn't hear about Bart being
elected world's greatest sex machine.
- I'll never pay off that debt!
- Need money fast?
Got no experience?
Step up to elegance.
- Become a limo driver at Classy Joe's.
- That's it!
I'll make money with a chauffeur job!
Good thing you turned on that TV, Lisa.
I didn't turn it on, I thought you did.
No. Well, anyway, turn it off.
It is off.
You have to work hard
to win this crowd over.
- Most of them are here for detention.
- Pretty big crowd.
We even bused in troublemakers
from other schools.
That spiky-haired, masked dancer
is really something.
- I wonder who he is.
- He's graceful, yet masculine.
So it's okay for me to enjoy this.
Oh, wow, I can't believe my very first
passenger is comedy legend Mel Brooks.
I loved that movie Young Frankenstein.
Scared the hell out of me.
- Thanks.
- Let's do that 2000-pound-man thing.
I'll be that Carl Reiner guy,
and you be what's-his-face.
It's not easy.
It takes the genius of Carl Reiner...
...and the timing that only we...
Sir, today, every country
has a national anthem.
Did they have national anthems
2000 years ago?
Sure! Sure we had.
Of course, we was caves.
But every cave had a national anthem.
I'll never forget
my cave's national anthem.
- What was that national anthem?
- Let them all go to hell except Cave 76
What's with the si...?
What's with the siren?
Evening, Simpson.
Got a short in your taillight.
Started blinking
when you made that turn.
- Let's see your chauffeur's license.
- Chauffeur's license, eh?
Mel, buckle your borscht belt!
Since you're trying to make
a getaway in park...
...I'm guessing you don't
have a license.
Better head to the DMV.
These two broads'll help you out.
Wow. Officer, this man
is making me a little edgy.
- Could you give me a ride to the airport?
- Hey, hey! You're Mel Brooks!
- Sure, I'll give you a ride.
- Thank you.
On the way we can do that
2000-dollar-man thing.
You be Carl Reiner,
and I'll be Police Chief Wiggum.
Listen, why don't you play Carl Reiner,
and let me play Police Chief Wiggum.
I hate Carl Reiner!
I haven't been moved like this
since The Joy Luck Club.
They love me. I'm accepted.
I don 't need this mask anymore.
Behold! The masked dancer is me, Bart!
- It is I who have won your acclaim!
- Bart does ballet!
He dances like girls!
Go ahead and laugh. I took a chance
and did what I wanted to do.
And if that makes me a sissy,
well, then, I guess I'm a sissy.
He's a sissy! Let's rush him!
- Yeah!
- Yeah, let's get him, come on!
After him! Go!
- There he is! There, right there!
- Bart, use the ballet. Leap!
Leap like you've never leapt before!
Looks like he took a pretty bad spill.
Well, as long as he's hurt.
Stupid driving test at the stupid DMV...
...where stupid Patty
and stupid Selma work.
Sometimes I think God is teasing me,
just like he teased Moses in the desert.
Tested, Homer. God tested Moses.
And try to be nice to my sisters.
It's very hard on me
to have you always fighting.
Oh, okay, Marge.
I'll get along with them.
Then I will hug some snakes.
Yes! I will hug and kiss
some poisonous snakes!
Now, that's sarcasm.
Well, well, well.
Look who needs us again...
...to get his chauffeur's license.
Look, all I ask is that you be fair.
Did not adjust side mirror.
Minus one point.
Failed to check blind spot.
Minus two points.
You'll be happy when my
family thinks I'm a loser.
You are a loser, Homer!
And we're winners. You gotta learn that.
Seat belt twisted. Minus one point.
Nagging the driver.
Minus 10 points for you!
- Grazed a cone. Minus five.
- Being a jerk. Minus a million!
One more wrong answer, and Homer
flunks another of life's little tests.
And what's this?
Someone didn't fill in a circle
all the way.
- Oh, boy. Oh, that felt good.
- Let me try. Let me try.
Yeah. Oh, boy.
Oh, that was so sweet.
- So, Homer, how'd you do?
- Well, I...
Ladies, please don't tell me
you're smoking in a government building.
Because that is
the kind of infraction...
...that can cost a couple of sisters
their promotion.
- Well...
- What?
- You mean...
- Why...
Oh, you're talking about she...
Who's? What? She... What, this?
I'll never forgive myself for this.
Wait a minute. Those are yours, sir?
Yes. I am in flavor country.
- Both of them?
- It's a big country.
Ladies, I apologize.
And you, sir, are worse than Hitler.
Homer, I'm... I'm speechless.
- You just saved our hides.
- On top of everything else...
...don't make me picture your hides.
- It's a wonderful thing you did...
...for my sisters.
- I didn't do it for them.
I did it for you, Marge. I'd kill for you.
- Please ask me to kill for you.
- No, Homie.
You see? This is the stuff I've been
telling you about that you never see.
Homer.
We're... sorry.
- If there's anything we can do...
- Call off the debt?
Or, say, we could let you pass
your driver's test.
Call off the debt?
- Well...
- Debt's off! Let's go, Marge!
www.tvsubtitles.net