Lisa, will you keep it down?
I'm making a crank call
to Principal Skinner.
As a matter of fact,
my refrigerator wasn't running.
You spared me quite a bit of spoilage.
Thank you, anonymous young man.
It's my room and I can
do what I want.
Oh, yeah? Well, I can do
what I want in my room.
Bart, quit it!
I can keep this up all day.
Lisa, stop the racket. I'm trying
to fix your mother's camera.
Easy. Easy.
I'm gonna need a bigger drill.
My, these seas are certainly heaving.
Well, no more than your
bountiful bosom, my lady.
Does that earring
mean you're a pirate?
Kind of.
The seas have quieted.
And only in the sweet embrace
of quietude can two lovers truly be as...
Such noise! Well, I'm done
for the evening.
Lisa, stop blowing my sex. I mean, stop
blowing your sax. Your sax. Stop it.
Mom, I'm auditioning for first chair
in the school band...
...and I've got to practice.
I'm sorry, but I sacrificed
a very expensive camera...
...just to get some quiet time.
Fine, I'll play outside.
Hey! Why, that sounds
like Gabriel's trumpet.
You know what that means, kids.
Judgment Day!
Forty-five seconds till pencils down.
Lisa, what's the answer
to number seven?
Sorry, Ralph. That would defeat
the purpose of testing...
...as a means of student evaluation.
My cat's name is Mittens.
Three. Two. One.
And that's pencils down.
Now, here's an oral
extra-credit question.
What was Christopher Columbus
actually looking for...
...when he discovered America?
Anyone besides Lisa for a change?
Ralph, this better not be
about your cat.
- Oh, all right.
- He was looking for a passage to India.
Correct, Allison. And on your
very first day in our class.
And during a subsequent voyage,
Columbus found...
...the continent of South America.
I never made Miss Hoover "yow-wee."
Hi, Allison. I'm Lisa Simpson.
It's great to finally meet someone
who converses...
...above the normal 8-year-old level.
Actually, I'm 7.
I was skipped ahead because
I was bored in the first grade.
You're younger than me too?
- Are you hyperventilating?
- No. I just like to smell my lunch.
I never met anyone
who skipped a grade before.
I'm surprised you haven't.
You're obviously smart enough.
Well, I'm sure I could have.
But I'd hate to leave behind
all my wonderful friends.
Out of the way, brain queen!
Hey, Sara.
Well, I gotta go. I have to practice
for band auditions.
Me too. What instrument do you play?
- The sax.
- Me too.
- I'm going for first chair this year.
Wow! We have so much in common.
I'm sure we'll be the best of friends.
- Me too.
Hurry up and finish eating.
You're steering fine, boy.
Hard to the right. Hard to the left.
Cat! Deer! Old man!
Jackknifed sugar truck!
Sugar?
Don't worry. Here's a quarter.
Call for help. I'll keep an eye
on things here.
If only the sugar were
as sweet as you, sir.
That was downright decent of you.
We hit the jackpot here!
White gold! Texas tea!
Sweetener.
Dad, isn't this stealing?
Read your town charter, boy.
If foodstuff should touch the ground...
...said foodstuff shall be turned over
to the village idiot.
Since I don't see him around,
start shoveling!
- Mom?
- What? What?
Why am I rotting away in the second
grade instead of being skipped ahead?
I don't know. I guess that's
the school's decision to make.
Did you talk to anyone at school?
Make a few calls on my behalf?
You could've been nicer to Principal
Skinner, if you know what I mean.
Lisa! I am nice.
Homer, I appreciate you making dinner,
but this food tastes a little strange.
It hurts my teeth.
That's because I've loaded it
with sugar!
Marge, our ship has come in.
I found 500 pounds of sugar
in the forest...
...that I'm gonna sell directly
to the consumer.
And all for a low, low price
of one dollar per pound.
But the store sells sugar
for 35 cents a pound.
And it doesn't have nails
and broken glass in it.
Those are prizes.
A blasting cap.
It's your turn, Jimbo.
Someone's been practicing
over the summer. Welcome aboard.
Yes!
My lute!
Lisa Simpson trying
for first-chair saxophone.
Very nice. Now Allison Taylor,
also trying for first-chair saxophone.
This is a very tough decision, girls.
You're both very good.
Well, I guess that clinches it.
That was a close one, Lisa,
but you made it.
I won first chair?
No, you regained consciousness.
Allison got first chair.
Oh, it was just a dream.
That was a close one, Lisa,
but you made it.
I won first chair?
No, you regained consciousness.
Allison got first chair.
And believe me, this is not a dream!
I need help. There's another girl
at school...
...who's smarter, younger
and a better sax player than me.
- I feel so average.
- You'll always be number one to me.
Hello! First born within earshot.
I meant my number one girl.
Oh, for crying...
Honey, if you get too competitive,
you'll never be happy.
No matter how good you are,
there's always someone better.
I thought I had the tallest hair, but that
trip to Graceland really opened my eyes.
But she's better than me at
everything that makes me special.
Believe me, honey. She's more scared
of you than you are of her.
You're thinking of bears, Mom.
Hey, Allison, what's the answer
to number nine?
- I can't tell you, Ralph.
- I can't tell you either, Ralph.
Leave me alone.
- Brainiac!
- Nerd!
You're such a geekazoid!
Leave me alone.
That used to be my face in the mud.
I can't stand to see you
so miserable, Lis.
Unless it's from a rubber
spider down your dress.
That gives me an idea.
Note for later: Put rubber spider
down Lisa's dress.
Hey, I know! How about if I dig up
some dirt on Allison?
Remember how I got Milhouse
on America 's Most Wanted?
- There he is on the monkey bars.
- Try to take him alive.
Oh, no! Not again!
I appreciate the offer, but it goes against
every moral fiber in my body.
Suit yourself. If you change your mind,
here's my card.
Don't need it.
You live in the room next to me.
Note: Next year, order fewer cards.
And you didn't think
I'd make any money.
I found a dollar while I was
waiting for the bus.
While you were out "earning"
that dollar...
...you lost 40 dollars
by not going to work.
The plant said if you don't come
tomorrow, don't bother coming Monday.
Four-day weekend!
Hey, I am above average.
So what if Allison's ahead of me?
There's no shame in being second.
And now Avis Rent A Car
is proud to present...
...the second-best band in America.
We welcome Garfunkel, Messina,
Oates and Lisa...
...singing their number two hit,
"Born to Runner-Up."
Why would they come
to our concert to boo us?
Lis, I did some checking
on this Allison.
And I know it's against
all your moral fibers...
Give it to me!
Hey, wait. There's nothing bad here.
Yep. She's clean as a bean.
But I did tip off the feds...
...as to the whereabouts
of our good friend Milhouse.
- But I'm telling you, I didn't do anything.
- I don't care.
My glasses!
I've got to stop being so petty.
I should be Allison's friend,
not her competitor.
I mean, she is a wonderful person.
Way to go, Lis. I mean,
why compete with someone...
...who's just gonna kick
your butt anyway.
I prefer my phrasing.
It's great of you to come over.
I really want us to be friends.
You're a wonderful person.
Hi, Lisa. I'm Allison's father,
Professor Taylor.
- I've heard great things about you.
- Oh, really? I...
I'm glad we have someone who can
join us in our anagram games.
We take names and rearrange the letters
to form a description of that person.
Well, like, oh, I don't know...
Alec Guinness.
- Genuine class.
- Very good.
All right, Lisa.
Jeremy Irons.
Jeremy's Iron.
Well, that's very good for a first try.
You know, I have a ball.
Perhaps you'd like to bounce it.
- What's this?
- It's for the school diorama competition.
You're finished already?
But the competition isn't for weeks!
Lisa, we're talking dioramas.
Who could wait?
I chose "The Tell-Tale Heart"
by Edgar Allan Poe.
See, this is the bedroom
where the old man was murdered.
And he's buried here
under the floorboards.
And, look, I used an old metronome
to simulate the heartbeat...
...that drove the killer insane.
Neat, huh?
It's great. It's really great.
Got away from you, huh?
Well, you keep at it.
Must protect sugar.
Thieves everywhere.
The strong must protect the sweet.
The sweet.
- Homer?
- In America...
...first you get the sugar...
...then you get the power...
...then you get the women.
Homer.
- Homer!
- What?
Forget about guarding
the stupid sugar.
You're being completely paranoid.
Oh, am I? Am I really?
Hello.
Where'd you get your
sugar for that tea?
I nipped it when you let your
guard down for that split second.
And I'd do it again.
- Goodbye.
- You see, Marge? You see?
When are you gonna give up
this crazy sugar scheme?
Never! Never, Marge.
I can't live the button-down life
like you.
I want it all. The terrifying lows,
the dizzying highs...
...the creamy middles.
Sure, I might offend a few
of the blue noses...
...with my cocky stride
and musky odors.
Oh, I'll never be the darling
of the so-called city fathers...
...who cluck their tongues,
stroke their beards...
...and talk about, "What's to be done
with this Homer Simpson?"
Look. Just get rid of the sugar, okay?
No!
Hey, get off my sugar! Bad bees! Bad!
Oh, they're defending
themselves somehow.
Look, Bart. It almost killed me...
...but I handcrafted all 75 characters
from Oliver Twist.
And now the coup de grâce:
A bitter snowstorm.
- Is it okay?
- Well...
The important thing
is that we survived.
Who am I kidding? There's no way
I'm ever gonna beat Allison!
Sure there is.
But it involves being a bit underhanded.
A bit devious, a bit...
...as the French say, "Bart-esque."
I'll do whatever it takes.
Then welcome to the nether regions
of the soul.
Now, here's what we do.
Tomorrow, when Allison comes out...
...we spray her with the hose,
soaking her from head to toe.
- Leaving us relatively dry.
- Relatively?
There's bound to be some splashback.
Bart, her being wet won't help me
win the competition!
Well, we could just sabotage
her diorama...
...humiliating her in front of
the students and faculty.
- Perfect!
- Leaving her primed...
...for the most dramatic
hose-soaking of her life!
Enough with the hose!
Well, sure is quiet in here today.
Yes, a little too quiet
if you know what I mean.
- I'm afraid I don't.
- You see...
...bees usually make
a lot of noise. No noise...
...suggests no bees.
I understand now.
Oh, look. There goes one.
- To the Beemobile!
- You mean your Chevy?
Yes.
Very clever, Simpson.
Luring our bees to your sugar...
...and selling them back
at an inflated price.
- Bees are on the what, now?
- Simpson, you diabolical...
We're willing to pay you $2000
for the swarm.
Deal!
Oh, wait a minute.
The bees are leaving.
No! My sugar is melting!
Melting! Oh, what a world!
I'm sorry, Homie.
It's okay, Marge.
I've learned my lesson.
A mountain of sugar
is too much for one man.
It's clear now why God portions it out
in those tiny packets...
...and why he lives
on a plantation in Hawaii.
Diorama-Rama. My favorite school event
next to Hearing Test Thursday.
"The Grapes of Wrath"? I don't get it.
Here's the grapes,
and here's the wrath!
Yes, yes. Very good wrath.
Let's see. Our foreign exchange
student, Uter, has chosen...
...Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
I...
But this is just an empty box.
I begged you to look at mine first.
I begged you!
Lisa, here is, as the French say,
"Le fake diorama."
I'll create a diversion
and you make the switch.
Hey, everybody! Whoa!
Look at me! I'm over here!
Turn this way right now!
- Hey, it's Bart!
- And he's doing stuff!
- Oh, I can't take my eyes off him.
- Look what he's doing.
Bart, stop creating a diversion
and get out of here!
Our next entry is "The Tell-Tale Heart"
from Allison Taylor.
I can't wait. Be ready with the ribbon.
- What is it?
- It's a cow's heart.
Them trying to make a monkey
out of you.
Allison, is this supposed to be
some kind of joke?
I didn't do that.
I made a different one.
Oh, is that so, young lady?
Well, where is this phantom diorama?
I don't know.
Have the guts to take the blame, girl.
- You're compounding your folly by lying.
- Right on!
Young lady, cow hearts belong
in a butcher's window...
...not the classroom. Well, maybe
in an older student's biology classroom...
...but that's none of my business.
Elementary school is where I wound up...
...and it's too late to do
anything about that.
Frankly, I'm starting to regret
skipping you ahead.
It's the beating of that hideous heart!
I mean, I think I hear something.
Why, here's Allison's real diorama.
It got misplaced, or so it would seem.
Oh, well, that changes everything.
Let's have a look. Get the ribbon ready.
Little sterile.
No real insight.
What do you think, Miss Hoover?
This has been
a very disappointing day.
All right, on to Lisa Simpson.
You're a shoo-in now, Lis.
After the way I've behaved,
I don't deserve to win.
- Well, this doesn't deserve to win.
- What?
Now we're into the dregs.
Here's Ralph Wiggum's entry.
Prepackaged Star Wars characters
still in their display box?
Are those limited edition figures?
What's a diorama?
Why, it's Luke and Obi-Wan.
And my favorite, Chewie.
They're all here!
- What do you think?
- It's lunchtime.
We have a winner!
I'm really sorry about
what I did, Allison.
It's no shame being second to you.
Thank you, Lisa.
You know, I'm actually
kind of glad I lost.
Now I know that losing
isn't the end of the world.
Hey, you still think we can be friends?
Only if we're the best.
I beat the smart kids,
I beat the smart ki...
I bent my Wookiee.
Hey, Ralph. Want to come with me
and Allison to play anagrams?
We take names and rearrange the letters
to form a description of that person.
My cat's breath smells like cat food.
www.tvsubtitles.net