And Maggie Makes Three
We now return to
Knightboat: The Crime-Solving Boat.
Faster, Knightboat.
Gotta catch those starfish poachers.
Don't have to yell, Michael.
I'm all around you.
Oh, no. They're headed for land.
- We'll never catch them now.
- Incorrect. Look, a canal.
- Go, Knightboat, go.
- Every week, there's a canal.
- Or an inlet.
- Or a fjord.
Quiet! I won't hear another word
against the boat.
- Okay, TV off. It's family time.
- But, Marge...
...Knightboat: The Crime-Solving Boat.
Homer, you promised,
one night of family time a week.
Besides, that back-talking boat
sets a bad example.
Says you, woman.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Mom.
All right, family time begins now.
- Homer.
- It was Bart.
Why don't we all look
at the photo album.
So many memories.
Oh, look, Knightboat.
And here's our TV next to the mirror.
It looks like we have two.
- Two.
Yeah, yeah, two.
Let's get to the baby pictures.
- Mom.
- That's exciting.
Oh, please.
Here's Bart sleeping.
Here he is dozing.
Here he is after a visit
from the sandman.
Here's nappy time, Bart.
Here's a cute one.
He's all tuckered out.
Why aren't there any pictures
of Maggie?
Well, I'm glad you asked.
It's actually a very interesting story.
It all began about two years ago,
before Maggie was even born.
It was a tumultuous time
for our nation.
The clear-beverage craze gave us all
a reason to live.
The information superhighway
showed the average person...
...what some nerd thinks
about Star Trek.
And the domestication of the dog
continued unabated.
I was at my workstation
when suddenly...
Attention, American workers.
Your plant has been taken over by
an all-star team of freelance terrorists.
Not on my shift!
No, you don't.
Simpson, 10, terrorists, 8.
- Homer, tell the story right.
- Okay.
Homer, you should see a doctor.
I don't think a healthy man
can make that kind of smell.
Your paychecks, gentlemen.
This is it.
With a single glorious check...
...I'm finally completely out of debt.
Yes! With my bills paid off,
I can finally quit this lousy job.
But, Homer, how you gonna
make a living?
Don't worry about Homer J.
I've got a plan.
- A plan that'll fix you good.
- Hey, what did we do?
Sorry, that just slipped out.
I'll miss you.
Did you hear me? I said, I quit, Monty.
And since I quit,
I can do anything I want.
Is that so?
Lovely desk.
It would be too bad if someone...
...oh, I don't know,
didn't use a coaster!
Such a nice, tidy office.
Maybe it's time you started
living like a pig!
Oh, I hope I haven't upset you...
...bongo head!
Oh, I should be resisting this,
but I'm paralyzed with rage...
...and island rhythms.
Go, Homer. Yeah. Yeah.
Way to play the boss's head
like a bongo, Homer.
He's getting a pretty good sound
out of that guy.
That's for employing me
for eight years.
And that is that.
Goodbye, mind-numbing,
backbreaking labor forever.
Hello, dream job in paradise.
And now, the final phase of my plan.
Barney, any chance
you can get me a job?
Hey. Sure, Homer.
I told you, my uncle owns the place.
- Hey, Uncle Al, can Homer have a job?
- Sure.
- Barney, you're fired.
- Okay.
Show up tomorrow. Bring three rags.
Oh, and a change of pants.
- Why?
- When it happens, you'll know.
You're a pin monkey?
Finally, I don't have to be ashamed
of my father's job.
It's romantic, throwing off
the shackles of the workaday world...
...and following a dream, of sorts.
I don't know if it's such a good idea.
Can we get by
on a pin monkey's salary?
Don't worry, Marge.
I've come up with
a perfectly balanced budget.
There will be exactly enough money
for you, me, Bart and Lisa...
...if we make a few small sacrifices.
From now on,
we use regular toilet paper...
...not that fancy quilted kind.
And only one of you kids
can go to college.
- Fine.
That night, your mom and I
went out for a romantic evening...
...to celebrate
the start of our new life.
We began with dinner and dancing.
Followed by a stroll on the beach.
- Marge.
- Homer.
I've got sand in my underpants.
Me too. Let's go home.
I love you, Marge.
I love you too, Homie.
Everything in our lives
is finally perfectly balanced.
I hope things stay exactly
like this forever.
Did you have to be so graphic?
It's okay, Marge. They pave the way
for this kind of filth in school.
Dad, were you excited
that Mom was pregnant?
Actually, your mother
hadn't told me yet.
At that time, I had no idea
Maggie even existed.
- Dad!
Hi, Maggie.
So anyhow, back then
there was no way for me to know...
...your mother was pregnant.
Hey.
Marge, you tie up the bathroom
every morning. I've gotta wash my hair.
The next few weeks at my dream job
were like a wonderful waking coma.
- Hey, Homer.
- Hi there, Homer.
- Hi, Homer.
Hi.
Bowling-fresh.
Urinal-fresh.
Homer, did you polish your head
in the Shine-O Ball-O?
- No.
- Okay, then.
I slowly learned the intricate mysteries
of the alley...
...like where the pins go
after they're knocked down.
I was in heaven.
If horseracing is the sport of kings...
...then surely, bowling...
...is a very good sport as well.
- Hey, great job, Homer.
- Thanks a lot, Homer.
Hey, you're the best.
I'm gonna make it after all
Congratulations, Mrs. Simpson.
You're pregnant.
Am I to take it that this is...
...an unwanted pregnancy?
Oh, no, no. Not exactly.
It's just that I haven't told Homer yet.
With his new job...
...I don't know how we'll
be able to afford this.
Well, you know, a healthy baby
can bring upwards of $60,000.
- What?!
- Of course, that was just a test.
Had you reacted differently, why,
you'd be in jail right now. Simply a test.
So in a few months, both of you
will have a brand-new brother or sister.
- Been there, done that.
- I hope it's a girl.
You know nothing about genetics, Lis.
It goes boy, girl, boy, girl.
- You're worried about telling Dad.
- Why do you say that?
Well, you've been in my room
for about four hours now.
Hey, I'm just hanging.
- Homie, I...
- Can't talk. Praying.
Dear Lord, the gods have been good
to me, and I am thankful.
For the first time in my life,
everything is absolutely perfect...
...just the way it is.
So here's the deal:
You freeze everything as it is...
...and I won't ask for anything more.
If that is okay,
please give me absolutely no sign.
Okay, deal. In gratitude, I present you
this offering of cookies and milk.
If you want me to eat them for you,
give me no sign. Thy will be done.
I've got to tell Homer about this baby
in just the right way...
...and at just the right time.
Until then, please keep this
to yourselves.
If he found out now, it would
probably destroy him, huh?
Oh, yes.
- Gotta go.
Wait a minute. Wait. I know that look.
Now, promise you won't tell Homer.
Oh, we promise we won't tell...
...Homer.
Hello. Is this A. Aaronson?
It might interest you to know that
Marge Simpson is pregnant again.
Just thought you'd like to know,
Mr. Zowkowski.
There. Aaronson and Zowkowski
are the two biggest gossips in town.
In an hour, everyone will know.
Another perfect day in my perfect life
with my perfect job.
Hey, just heard the news
over the squawk box.
- That's nice work, Homer.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
It is nice work.
Oh, Mr. Simpson, I have just heard
about the little bundle of joy.
- Congratulations, sir.
- It's true, the bundle is little...
...but I'm not in it for the money.
Hey, Homer,
way to get Marge pregnant.
This is getting very abstract,
but thank you...
...I do enjoy working
at the bowling alley.
Surprise! Baby shower.
Baby shower?
You know I haven't told Homer yet.
And he'll be home any minute.
- Oh, really?
Man, it's windy as hell out there.
Hey, wait a minute.
What are all these presents?
It looks like you're...
...showering Marge with gifts.
With little, tiny baby-sized gifts.
Well, I'll be in the tub.
By the way, congratulations
on your new job, Homer.
New job? Marge is pregnant?!
No!
Dad, you really threw a tantrum
like a little sissy girl?
Oh, just that one time.
Actually, when I was
about to have Bart...
You're pregnant?!
And then when I told him
about Lisa...
You're pregnant again?!
Who wouldn't be upset?
That new baby in your mother's womb
was a ticking time bomb...
...threatening to blow this family
eight ways from Sunday.
- Where are you going?
- You can't expect a person...
...to sit for 30 minutes straight.
I'm gonna get a snack and maybe
go to the bathroom.
I'll stay here, but I'm gonna think
about products I might like to purchase.
I don't have that.
You're pregnant.
We're gonna have to have a baby.
All our financial plans are ruined.
We're doomed. Doomed, I tells you!
- Bart, let your father tell the story.
- Yeah.
- Okay, but I know funny.
- Anyhoo...
We're doomed!
- Homer, you had a head.
- Check.
And your bottom was a little bigger.
You've worked hard
at the bowling alley.
- Why don't you ask for a raise.
- Yeah, a raise.
I've never been good enough
at any job to deserve one.
But I'm damn good at this one.
That's it.
I'm gonna march
right up to Al and say:
Steve. I mean, Al,
I think I deserve a raise.
You're a hard worker.
I'd like to give you a raise.
But the alley just ain't doing enough
business to pay that kind of money.
How about if I triple the business?
Then could I get a raise?
Well, yeah, but...
Of course.
Bowling. Bowling here.
Come bowl now. Get your bowling.
Who's ready? Bowling.
Mom, make Dad tell the story right.
That's what really happened.
My marketing plan attracted a record
number of police and fire officials...
...but few stayed to bowl. I failed.
Quitting my dream job
was the hardest thing I've ever done.
You did a great job, Homer.
I'm really gonna miss you.
Place has never been cleaner.
And the way you kept the young people
away, that was beautiful.
Oh, yeah. Thanks for that.
Anyway, we all pitched in, and we
got you this little going-away thing.
This was the happiest time of my life.
I'll never forget you guys.
Especially you, Joey.
- See you around, Mr. Homer.
- Don't worry, Joey.
We'll make it to California someday.
Sure, we will, Mr. Homer.
Sure, we will.
It's gonna be sad around here
without you, Homer.
- Yeah.
- Sure is.
- Boy, this is depressing.
- I know what'd cheer us up. Bowling.
Look at this, I got a ball here.
I needed more money to support
my growing family.
And there was only one place in town
that a man like me could make it.
Acid rain again.
Yes? Are you a new applicant?
- I quit, and I came to get my job back.
- Through there.
So come crawling back, eh?
Seems like the classy thing to do
would be not to call attention to it.
- Thanks for giving me my old job back.
- I'm afraid it's not that simple.
As punishment for your desertion...
...it's company policy
to give you the plague.
Sir, that's the "plaque."
Yes, the special
de-motivational plaque...
...to break what's left of your spirit.
Because, you see,
you're here forever.
"Don't forget: You're here forever."
I've never been so miserable
in all my life.
But I can't take it out
on Marge and the kids.
I've gotta carry the burden
all by myself.
- Hi, honey. How are you?
- Well, actually...
Oh, I can't go on with this charade.
I hate my job. I hate my life.
Since I found out about this baby,
there's been only bad luck.
My contractions started an hour ago.
Just in one ear and out the other
with you, isn't it?
It's wonderful. It's magical. Oh, boy.
Here it comes, another mouth.
One more push should do it.
Marvelous.
Congratulations, Mr. Simpson.
You have a beautiful, healthy baby.
Okay.
Homie, I think someone
is saying hello.
Hello.
It's a boy. And what a boy!
That's the umbilical cord. It's a girl.
A girl. Oh, Marge,
we have a wonderful baby girl.
Not just a girl. The most beautiful
baby girl in the whole world.
Come on, Marge,
show a little enthusiasm.
So you loved her right from the start.
Absolutely.
- Then why no pictures?
- Oh, there are pictures.
I keep them where I need
the most cheering up.
www.tvsubtitles.net