Two Dozen and One Greyhounds
Welcome to the 6:00 news,
in our brand-new studio.
Looking good, Springfield.
In today's news, a 2-ton rhino
escaped from the Springfield Zoo.
But zoo officials were quick to act...
...and Petunia, as she is known,
is safely back in captivity.
In other news, a 3-ton rhino...
...that escaped from the zoo last week
is still at large.
All right, who broke my vase?
Who took my tests off the refrigerator
and tore them up?
Who spread garbage all over
Flanders' yard before I got a chance to?
Oh, please.
This is senseless destruction...
...with none of my usual
social commentary.
If it wasn't you, then who was it?
I'm sure these things didn't destroy
themselves, now, did they?
Did they?
I guess Bart's not to blame.
He's lucky too...
...because it's spanking season, and
I got a hankering for some spankering.
I don't know why you're
so energetic today...
...but prepare to be worn out.
What's wrong, boy? Getting tired?
I think there's really something wrong
with Santa's Little Helper.
He was up barking all night and dug up
the back yard worse than ever.
- My bongo drums!
- My strobe light!
My Best of Ray Stevens,
featuring "The Streak," album.
So it was the dog
that buried all our stuff.
Yes, the dog.
Oh, my God! He's got
the precious cable-TV cable!
Always use fresh macaroni.
If the box rattles, throw it away.
Your cable TV
is experiencing difficulties.
Please do not panic.
Resist the temptation to read
or talk to loved ones.
Do not attempt sexual relations...
...as years of TV radiation have left
your genitals withered and useless.
Well, I'll be damned.
Excuse me. We're having
a problem with our dog.
I'll tell you what I'm telling
everyone else.
I'm sorry if your dog went blind, but your
gripe is with Hartz Mountain, not me.
No. No, our dog is out of control.
He's wild, destructive and has little
or no respect for authority.
Let me try a canine-human mind meld.
It's an incredibly rare psychic power
possessed only by me...
...and three other clerks at this store.
Okay.
I'm bored. I'm restless.
Need change in life...
...like imported leather leash...
...blue contact lenses...
...200-volt-shock training collar.
Well, problem solved.
- Homer, hold on to the wheel!
- You got it.
Hey!
Don't worry. We'll catch him
or run him over trying.
He's headed to the greyhound
racing track where we found him.
Don't worry, when they find out
he doesn't have money...
...they'll throw him out.
Believe me, I know.
This place is so big.
Do you think we should split up
and look for him, Homie?
- Homie?
- Two bucks to win on number eight.
And have you seen my beloved dog?
Give me the ticket.
We can't lose.
Look at the name of the dog I bet on.
"She's the Fastest."
I don't think that means, necessarily...
And they're off. She's the Fastest
jumps out to an insurmountable lead.
You're lucky you got looks, Marge.
Around the far turn,
it's She's the Fastest.
Followed by Always Comes in Second
and I'm Number Three.
Yes! Come on, you little horse!
And they're in the home stretch. It's...
Wait! Another dog is on the track.
- Santa's Little Helper!
- The mystery dog...
...gaining fast on the outside.
Of course, he could never win this race.
Or could he?
What's Santa's Little Helper
doing to that dog?
Looks like he's trying to jump over her,
but he can't quite make it.
Come on, boy! You can do it!
Ladies and gentlemen, this is the end.
This is the end of dog racing.
I think they're in love.
So that's what's been wrong
with the little fella.
He misses casual sex.
- Can we keep Santa's girlfriend, Mom?
- Please?
- But she's not our dog.
- She's yours now.
Once they fall in love,
they lose their racing spirit.
Won't you miss her loyalty
and companionship?
Lady, you're all right.
Okay, you can go out and play.
But no more you-know-what
in front of the house, all right?
Hey! What did I just say?
Take it. It fell on the floor.
Hey, boy, you wanna play fetch?
Me and Santa's Little Helper
used to be a team.
But he never wants to play anymore
since his bitch moved in.
- Don't ever say that word again.
- Well, that's what she is. I looked it up.
Well, I'm going to write the dictionary
people and have that checked.
Feels like a mistake to me.
Hey, look. A really small dog
just fell out of Santa's girlfriend.
Oh, my God! She's having babies!
Oh, I'm sorry, girl.
I thought you were just getting fat.
- Look, it's twins!
- No, it's two sets of twins.
- Two sets of twins and a triplet.
- Homer.
Homer, find a place
for all these little miracles.
Oh, my. I've never seen
anything like this.
How many more can there be?
Twenty-two.
Twenty-three.
Twenty-four.
Twenty-five.
Oh, Homie, aren't they adorable?
Yes. We waited many years...
...but the good Lord has finally
blessed us with a real family.
Look at Branford II. Isn't that cute?
He thinks he's one of the Models Inc.
Get that cat out of the way!
My socks.
Mom, why do I have to wear
a flea collar?
Oh, it's just easier this way.
This time...
This house stinks.
Are you just putting new newspapers
over the old ones?
Do you have a better idea?
Now, I know we love the puppies
very much...
...but I think they're getting
to be a problem.
Yeah, they ate all my socks.
I have to wear Lisa's to school today.
- How do you explain the culottes, boy?
- I have to coordinate, don't I?
We've been thinking about
giving the puppies away.
- No!
- Mainly your mother.
Is that what we do in this family?
When someone becomes an
inconvenience, we just get rid of them?
Hello? Is anybody there?
All right, we'll give the dogs
one more chance.
As long as the puppies don't do
anything else wrong, they stay.
On a completely unrelated topic...
...I'm having a very, very important
dinner party tonight.
Splendid. Who's coming?
Reverend Lovejoy,
your old Army drill sergeant...
...and the regional director of the IRS.
Oh, just lovely, Marge.
The whole town will hear
what a perfect evening this was.
- How nothing at all went wrong.
- Simpson.
This evening has gone so flawlessly,
I'm gonna forget...
...that you were mistakenly
let out of the Army early.
I'm so impressed
by this problem-free evening...
...that there's no need for that audit.
- A toast to the Simpsons.
And to the delectable turkey...
...that's walking around the table!
Dear Lord, it's a demon bird.
Simpson! See you at reveille,
0500 tomorrow.
See you at the IRS.
See you in hell.
From heaven.
Well, we sure could use a pooch
to guard the flock at the Flanderosa.
It'd be nice to have some companionship
when Mother goes out on dates.
We could use a new pet
over at the home...
...seeing how we accidentally
killed that smart-mouthed bird.
They don't like being broken up.
We've got to be realistic, kids.
Who's gonna have a big enough heart
to take care of 25 puppies?
And I know the little fellas would love
romping around my many acres...
...chasing my many cars...
...drinking from my many toilets.
- Who wouldn't?
Mom, don't give the puppies to him.
He'll be mean to them.
She's right, Homer. There's
something about his face I don't trust.
I'm sorry, Mr. Burns...
...but you can't have these dogs.
Am I fired?
Oh, of course not.
They're your pets.
You can do as you wish.
Good day, everyone.
- My, he certainly took that well.
- A little too well, if you ask me.
I'm sure he's plotting some
brilliant scheme to get those puppies.
There you go. There you go. You too.
Honestly, sir, you don't put the effort
into your schemes that you used to.
Don't worry, folks,
we'll find your wallet.
Dogs. Chief, you're getting
powdered sugar all over my floor.
No, I'm not. No, I'm not.
I'm dusting for prints.
We don't have to wait for cops.
Who can track them better
than their mom and dad?
Let's go find your babies.
Dinner's on, dogs.
I'm sorry, kids. I don't think we're
ever gonna find your greyhounds.
Maybe Mr. Burns will sell you
one of the 25 he got last night.
Who knows what horrible things he's
doing to those innocent little puppies.
There. Now, wasn't that heavenly?
And don't you feel better too?
He's giving them a bath.
There you are.
There you go, little fella. And you.
Smithers, look. He's standing up.
I've never seen anything so adorable.
You know who it reminds me of?
- Benji?
- No.
- Lassie?
- No, no.
- A person. You know who I mean.
- Snoop Doggy Dogg?
- Bob Barker? David Brenner?
- No, no.
The person who's always
standing and walking.
- Rory Calhoun?
- That's it!
You stay with me.
You're the pick of the litter.
Maybe we were wrong about Burns
on this one.
Are you sure you wanna
go through with this, sir?
You do have a very full wardrobe
as it is.
Yes. But not completely full.
For, you see:
Some men hunt for sport
Others hunt for food
The only thing I'm hunting for
Is an outfit that looks good
See my vest
Made from real gorilla chest
Feel this sweater, there's no better
Than authentic Irish setter
See this hat
'Twas my cat
My evening wear, vampire bat
These white slippers
Are albino African endangered rhino
Grizzly-bear underwear
Turtles ' necks, I've got my share
Beret of poodle
On my noodle it shall rest
Try my red-robin suit
It comes one breast or two
See my vest
Like my loafers?
Former gophers
It was that or skin my chauffeurs
But a greyhound-fur tuxedo
Would be best
- So let's prepare these dogs
- Kill two for matching clogs
See my vest
Oh, please, won 't you see my vest?
- I really like the vest.
- I gathered, yeah.
He's gonna make a tuxedo
out of our puppies.
- Bart.
- Sorry. You gotta admit, it's catchy.
Come on, Smithers. Let's go
finish the little flea circuses off.
Except for little Monty, of course.
We gotta get the dogs out of there.
- Hush, puppies.
- We gotta get you out of here.
I know. The window.
- No. What are you doing?
- Dogs always land on their feet.
- That's cats.
- No, it's dogs. I'll prove it.
Best two out of three.
Bart, look. A laundry chute.
Okay, guys. Let's move.
Come on, come on.
I've got an idea.
Sorry, Monty,
but you're too big for this ride.
- Quick, let's get the...
- Going somewhere?
That's impossible.
How did you get here first?
Oh, there'll be plenty of time
for explanations later.
Right now, I'll be taking
my puppies back.
But they're ours.
You stole them from us.
Here's a phone.
Call somebody who cares.
Give me that.
Now, if you'll excuse us, children...
...the pups have a date
with a fashion knife.
There. Now you don't know
which one's little Monty.
If you don't want him to be part of your
tuxedo, you'll let the other dogs go too.
Nice try.
Come on, little Monty. Stand up.
Come on, stand up. Do your trick.
No. Don't. Stay down, Monty.
- Stay down. Stay down, boy.
- No. Don't get up. Good boy.
Excellent.
Now it's simply a matter
of bending down...
...and picking up the one and only...
This can't be happening.
They're all standing.
I can't tell them apart.
All right, you win.
- I'll have to kill them all.
- No!
But they're so wretchedly adorable.
Twenty-five little Rory Calhouns.
I can't do it.
But I can kill you.
No, I can't kill you either.
Look at you, standing there
on your hind legs...
...like a couple of Rory Calhouns.
Mr. Burns, I hope you've realized the folly
of killing innocent animals for fashion.
I have, I have. I swear, I'll never wear
any clothing made from an animal...
...that can do an amusing trick.
Another victory for Montgomery Burns '
champion greyhounds.
Twenty-five dogs,
25 world champions...
...which so far have earned
their owner over $ 10 million.
I'll bet whoever gave him those dogs
is kicking themselves now.
Homer! For the love of God, no!
Marge, you know that batting
this light bulb is the only thing...
...that cheers me up after giving away
those million-dollar greyhounds.
www.tvsubtitles.net