Who Shot Mr. Burns? (Part One)
Is there nothing so intoxicating
as the school hallway at early morn?
The school normally
doesn't smell so rank.
Washbasin fresh. That funk must be
coming from one of the classrooms.
Poor fellow.
Crushed by his own water bottle.
Willie, sometime over the holiday
weekend, the beloved grade-four gerbil...
...Superdude, lost his life.
I need you to air out the classroom
and give Superdude a proper burial.
You're lucky you're getting
a decent burial.
Me own father
got thrown in the bog.
What in the name of
Saint Ephesiocritus...?
What reeks?
- Smells like one of van Houten's.
- It does not.
Miss Hoover, the floor is shaking.
Ralph, remember the time
you thought the...?
Now, before we adjourn, I have one last
matter of utmost importance.
I need to send this parcel with the profit
projections to Pete Porter in Pasadena.
And it absolutely, positively,
has to be there overnight.
- Pete Porter. Pass it on.
- Pasadena. Promptly.
Package parcel processing.
Perk up. Package of plant profit
projection for Pete Porter in Pasadena.
- Priority?
- Precisely.
Here's your package, Mr. Burns.
My name is the return address,
you senseless dunderpate.
Smithers, who is this nincompoop?
I've worked here for 10 years and
my boss doesn't even know my name.
Well, that's gonna change right now.
My name is Homer J. Simp...
...son.
- Sounded large when I ordered it.
I can't make hide nor hair
of these metric booby traps.
My Lord. Such destruction.
Superintendent Chalmers.
How are you going?
Why is it when I heard the word
"school" and the word "exploded"...
...I thought of the word "Skinner"?!
Congratulations, gentlemen.
Your custodian struck oil.
You're standing on top of the richest
elementary school in the state.
We also found this.
Thank you. Superdude.
A nonprofit organization with oil?
I won't allow it.
An oil well doesn't belong
in the hands of...
...Betsy Bleeding-heart
and Maynard G. Muskie-vote.
Sir, have you had enough
exercise for this morning?
No.
Let's do another 20 miles.
I want that oil well.
I've got a monopoly to maintain.
I own the electric company, waterworks,
plus the hotel on Baltic Avenue.
That hotel's a dump and
your monopoly's pathetic.
The oil well is not for sale, particularly to
a black-hearted scoundrel like yourself.
I see.
Then I'll just have to attack you.
I must have that oil.
Smithers. Smithers,
help me subdue this beast.
Sorry, sir. This was all I could find.
Take that. And that.
Please don't waste those.
I'm happy for the school.
Sounds like this money is gonna
provide new opportunities.
Big deal. They didn't approve my idea.
Said it was unfeasible.
It is unfeasible
to resurrect the dead, Bart.
And even if the Three Stooges were
alive, I doubt they'd hang out with you.
I guess they'd wanna be with
their families or something, huh?
Oh, I hate my job.
What's the point when your boss
doesn't even remember your name?
- I have an idea.
- What? What's your idea?
When my father was trying
to catch my mother's eye...
...he sent her a box of candy
with his photo.
- After that, she never forgot him.
- That's all well and good.
But it's not really your idea,
is it, now, Marge?
That's it. Frimble about with
your widgets and doobobs.
It will all be a monument to futility
when my plan comes to fruition.
Sir.
What I'm about to say violates
every sycophantic urge in my body...
...but I wish you'd reconsider.
This isn't a rival company...
...it's a school. They won't stand for it.
- Pishposh.
It will be like taking
candy from a baby.
Say, that sounds like a "larf."
Let's try it right now.
There's candy right here. Why
don't we eat this instead of stealing.
Oh, very well.
- Oh, look. There's a photo in here.
- Oh, yes.
That's little Maggie Simpson, the baby
who found my teddy bear Bobo.
And there's that Simpson mutt,
my former guard dog.
And that's Bart Simpson. He was my
heir for a brief period, you know.
Yes, sir. I remember.
Anything left?
Only the sour quince log, sir.
Dispose of it.
And send a thank-you note to
Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie Simpson.
Today, Springfield Elementary
embarks on a new era of...
...unbridled spending where petrodollars
fuel our wildest educational fantasies.
These young minds will enjoy every
academic advantage...
...till they enter Springfield High School,
which has no oil well.
- We got an air hockey table.
- Fine. Now, to switch on our oil pump...
...for the very first time, here's our
top student, Lisa Simpson.
Nerd!
There's no pressure.
- Someone else has tapped this well.
- Ay caramba!
Soon that mighty apparatus will
burst forth with its precious fluid.
Almost sexual, isn't it, Smithers?
Oil ho!
Huzzah!
Holy Christmas!
Your dog's condition has been
upgraded from stable to frisky.
He's free to go. His leg should
be good as new in a few months.
In the meantime,
he'll have to use the wheel-about.
I'll get even with whoever did this
to you, boy. I swear it.
I almost forgot. Wouldn't want
you gnawing on those casts, eh, boy?
We've got no legal recourse against
Mr. Burns' slant-drilling operation.
The oil belongs to whoever
pumped it first.
What about the expensive stuff
we wanted? Can we still have it?
No.
Blast it!
To pay for the construction, operation
and demolition of the derrick...
...we have to cut nonessential programs.
Music...
- What?!
- And maintenance.
I'll kill that Mr. Burns!
And wound that Mr. Smithers.
Out of my way.
Oh, no. That's awful, Mr. Puente.
What?
He owns the nuclear power plant.
Yeah, I'd like to settle his hash too.
Dad, how can you work
for a man like Mr. Burns?
He's not all bad. He did send me
this nice thank-you card.
"Marge, Bart, Lisa and Maggie."
Dad, this doesn't have your name on it.
Kids, would you
step outside for a second?
Dear Lord. That's the loudest
profanity I've ever heard.
These fumes aren't as fun as beer.
Sure, I'm all dizzy and nauseous...
...but where's the inflated sense
of self-esteem?
Hey, if you guys are getting loaded off
them fumes, I'll have to charge you.
Man alive!
There are men alive in here.
I'm detecting over
20 different toxins in the air.
Everybody out. As long as
Burns is pumping oil, this bar is closed.
Damn Burns.
Let me just get one thing.
Me too. Now, there's the
inflated sense of self-esteem.
Earthquake!
- Nurse!
- Nurse! Nurse!
Well, sir, you've
vanquished all your enemies.
The elementary school, local tavern,
the old-age home. You must be proud.
No, not while my greatest nemesis still
provides our customers...
...with free light, heat and energy.
I call this enemy... the sun.
Since the beginning of time,
man has yearned to destroy the sun.
I will do the next best thing:
Block it out.
- Good God!
- Imagine it, Smithers.
Electrical lights and heaters
running all day long.
But, sir, every plant
and tree will die.
Owls will deafen us with incessant
hooting. The sundial will be useless.
I don't want any part of this project.
It's unconscionably fiendish.
I won't suffer your insubordination.
There has been a shocking decline in the
quality and quantity of your toadying.
And you will fall into line. Now!
No. No, Monty, I won't.
Not until you step back
from the brink of insanity.
I'll do no such thing. You're fired.
Take that, Bowl-a-rama.
Take that, convenience mart.
Take that, nuclear power pla...
Oh, fiddlesticks.
I must say, Mr. Burns is being
awfully inconsiderate. Selfish, even.
Burns needs some serious
"boostafazoo." Right, Dad?
Dad. Homer.
Sorry, Grampa. It's just, for a second,
it looked like Dad had melted.
Well, get used to it,
because I'm living here now.
I ain't going back to the home until they
fish my bed out of that sinkhole.
Strained carrots for Maggie.
Strained carrots for Grampa.
I want a bib too.
Smithers, who is that ignoramus?
Smithers, who is that lollygagger?
Who is that blubber-pot?
Who is that bafflewit?
Lummox. Puddinghead.
Mooncalf. Limpnoodle.
Goldbricker. Drizzlepuss...
- Stop it. Stop it. Stop it!
- Look out!
What?
Just a minute.
Who the devil are you?
- Homer Simpson.
- What? What are you talking about?
- Make sense, man.
- I can't understand a word you're saying.
- My name is Homer Simpson.
Oh, you're a dead man, Burns.
Oh, you're dead. You're dead, Burns!
- Hey, the lamp's running away.
- That's my dog, man.
So long, lamp. Now, stop loafing
and help your Grampa unpack.
That's my old Smith & Wesson.
If you're gonna play with it,
be careful. It's loaded.
Bart, put that down!
Guns are dangerous. And I won't
have them in this house.
How can you have a house
without a gun?
What if a bear came through the door?
I'm going to bury it in the yard
where little hands can't get to it.
You should've fired into the air.
She would've run off.
People, take it easy.
We're all upset about Mr. Burns'
plan to block out our sun.
It is time for decisive action.
I have here a polite but firm letter
to Mr. Burns' underlings...
...who, with some cajoling,
will pass it along to him...
...or at least
give him the gist of it.
Sir, a lot of people
are stroking guns.
It has been brought to my attention
a number of you are stroking guns.
Therefore I'll step aside
and open up the floor.
Mr. Burns was the closest thing
I ever had to a friend.
But he fired me.
And now I spend my days drinking cheap
Scotch and watching Comedy Central.
- Oh, dear God.
- I lost my bar. - I lost his bar.
He robbed the school of music.
- He robbed it of financial security.
- He robbed the school of Tito.
- He can't remember my name!
- He's causing us all to yell!
Look what he did to my best friend.
No, my dog.
Those wheels are squeaking a bit.
Perhaps I could sell him a little oil.
You twisted old monster!
I've decided to protect myself...
...ever since I was attacked in my office
by an unidentified assailant.
Burns, your scurvy schemes will earn ye
a one-way passage to the boneyard.
I'd like to hear from Sideshow Mel.
I'll see that Mr. Burns suffers the infernal
machinations of hell's grim tyrant.
- Yeah.
- Oh, you all talk big.
But who here
has the guts to stop me?
Very well. One last question.
Have you ever seen
the sun set at 3 p. M?
Once, when I was
sailing around the Arctic...
Shut up, you. Take one last look
at the sun, Springfield.
Hey, hey!
I've been in Reno for six weeks.
Did I miss anything?
What the...?
Eternal darkness.
Well, that's just great.
Listen, someone's
got to get that Mr. Burns.
Where's a gun-toting lowlife
when you need one?
Sorry, I was in the can.
Perpetual twilight. Bathed in
the glow of Burns brand electricity.
Hello, lamppost. What you knowing?
I've come to watch
your power flowing.
That's odd. Mr. Smithers
left his jacket behind.
That's odd. Principal Skinner
left his mother behind.
That's odd. Where's Homer? And Bart?
And Lisa? And Grampa?
After all these years, things are
finally starting to go my way.
I feel like celebrating.
Oh, it's you.
What are you so happy about?
I see. I think you'd better drop it.
I said, drop it!
Get your hands off.
Where is everybody?
Hey, man. Are you okay?
Won't... dignify that... with a response.
Mr. Burns has been shot.
Just a minute.
This isn't Mr. Burns at all.
It's a mask.
Oh, wait, it is Burns.
His wrinkly skin looks like a mask.
I don't think we'll ever know who
did this. Everyone in town's a suspect.
Well, I couldn't possibly
solve this mystery.
Can you?
Yeah, I'll give it a shot.
I mean, you know, it's my job, right?
www.tvsubtitles.net