Homer Badman
Damn FDA.
Why can't it all be marshmallow?
Bart, don't put the non-marshmallow
pieces back in the box.
They go in the trash.
You like sweets, kids?
I know a place that's sweeter
than sweetness itself.
In this sweet place,
earthly doughnuts are sour as poison.
You'd spit them out, you would.
I'm talking about
the Candy Industry Trade Show.
How did you get tickets?
They hid them in every
millionth Krusty Klump Bar...
...and Krusty Klump Bar
with almonds.
Hey. Hey.
I have asked you nicely
not to mangle my merchandise.
You leave me no choice
but to ask you nicely again.
- Can I come to the candy show? Can I?
- No, me. Take me, me, me.
Sorry, kids.
But this the one event
I want my darling wife by my side.
Oh, well, thank you, Homer.
But take one of the kids.
Marge, they can't carry enough candy.
They have puny little muscles.
Not big, ropy ones like you.
- You go, Mom. For the greater good.
- For the greater good.
Homer, are all
these pockets necessary?
They wouldn't be if you would
sit in a hollowed-out wheelchair.
Well, that's the babysitter. No one
in town will sit for you two anymore.
I had to choose between a grad student
at the university or a scary-looking hobo.
Please, the hobo.
Please, the hobo. The hobo.
Hi. I'm Ashley Grant.
Ashley Grant. You gave a talk
on women's issues at my school...
...on how we don't have to
be second-class citizens.
Mom, how can you leave us
with this maniac?
Hurry. If we're early,
we can get a picture...
...with the two surviving Musketeers.
There's also a baby
somewhere upstairs.
So you're one of those
"don't-call-me-a-chick" chicks, huh?
Sorry about
my unenlightened brother.
He will make
the next few hours a living hell.
Oh, I don't know.
See this, Bart?
Disemboweler IV.
The game where condemned criminals
dig at each other with rusty hooks.
Do a little housework
and you can play for five minutes.
No way.
- Yes.
- See, Lisa? Male's aren't hard to tame.
They all follow their video cartridges.
Mr. Goodbar to the front desk.
The front desk
is looking for Mr. Goodbar.
I feel like a kid
in some kind of a store.
Brilliant.
Exquisite.
You'll do well. Give me those.
Well, as you can see,
I have created a lemon ball so sour...
...it can only be safely contained
in a magnetic field.
The candy, known as 77X42...
- Where the hell is the candy?
- I don't know.
You're gonna have to put some sugar
on that celery or get out, ma'am.
Gummi bears. Gummi calves' heads.
Gummi jawbreakers.
- What's that?
- That is the rarest gummi of them all.
The gummi Venus de Milo,
carved by gummi artisans...
...who work exclusively
in the medium of gummi.
Will you two stop saying
"gummi" so much?
Must have rare gummi.
Distract the salesman.
No. I won't make a spectacle
out of myself any further.
How did they get there?
Now, this is going to take all my skill.
- Halt! Halt!
- Run, Marge. Save the booty.
After him. He has the gummi.
See you in hell, candy boy!
Lis, I found a big caramel deposit
on her back.
I'm coming.
Wait a minute. Wait.
Where's my gummi de Milo?
Okay, don't panic. She can't
have gotten far. She has no arms.
I'm sure it'll turn up.
Take the babysitter home now.
She's been in the car for 20 minutes.
Relax, Marge.
There's plenty for her to do in there.
See? She's having the time of her life.
So a graduate student, huh?
How come you can go to the moon,
but can't make my shoes smell good?
- I'm sorry?
- Nobody's blaming you.
Could you take the wheel
for a second?
- I have to scratch in two places at once.
- Just drop me off here.
Precious Venus.
Thank you.
Hey, kids.
Lots of candy left for breakfast.
Why don't we give it
to some needy children then?
The candy conventioneers
tracked us down.
There he is. There's the man
that sexually harassed me.
For a minute there I thought
I was in big trouble. It's just a...
Two, four, six, eight
Homer's crime was very great
"Great" meaning "large or immense"
We use it in the pejorative sense
Marge, I swear I didn't touch her.
You know how bashful I am.
I can't even say the word "titmouse"
without giggling like a schoolgirl.
At any rate, I believe you.
I think you should go outside
and straighten this out.
Some of their chants
are very catchy and memorable.
- You grabbed me in the car.
- Oh, that? No.
I was grabbing a gummi Venus de Milo
that got stuck to your pants.
Yeah, right.
That's the oldest excuse in the book.
Come on. I'm a decent guy.
Why would anybody
wanna touch a girl's butt?
That's where cooties come from.
I don't understand.
What is she saying you did?
Lisa, remember that postcard
Grampa sent us from Florida...
...of that alligator
biting that woman's bottom?
Oh, yeah. That was brilliant.
That's right.
We all thought it was hilarious.
But it turns out we were wrong.
That alligator was
sexually harassing that woman.
And the dog in the Coppertone ad?
Same deal?
Well, that's kind of a gray area.
- We know you're innocent, Dad.
- Thanks, kids.
They seem to be building some
sort of a shantytown.
Do your worst, protestors.
You can't stop me from living my life.
- No respect for women. No peace.
- Try to push the right buttons now.
We ain't crazy about
nuclear power either!
You people aren't allowed in here.
It's okay. They're with me.
They're ruining my whole life.
Marge, please,
this is where I need you the most.
I'm counting on you to do something
or say something to make it all better.
- Okay. Go.
- Homer...
I talked to the indignation coordinator
out on the lawn today.
I said you were a decent man.
She wouldn't listen.
Besides standing by you and
supporting you, there's nothing I can do.
You mean, I'm on my own?
I've never been on my own. Oh, no.
On own. On own.
I need help. Oh, God, help me.
Help me, God!
- Hello?
- Hello, Homer, this is God...
...frey Jones from
the TV magazine show Rock Bottom.
We're aware of your problems,
and, Mr. Simpson, we want to help.
I saw that report you did on Sasquatch.
It was fair and even-handed.
I'll do it.
Somebody had to take
the babysitter home.
Then I noticed she was sitting on the
gummi Venus, so I grabbed it off her.
Oh, just thinking about
that sweet, sweet candy...
I just wish I had
another one right now.
- But the most important thing is...
- That was great, Mr. Simpson.
- We got everything we need.
- Okay.
Say, can you introduce me
to the Sasquatch?
I like his style.
Here comes the bouncing ball
of justice.
Tonight on Rock Bottom:
We go undercover at a sex farm
for sex hookers.
I keep telling you,
I just grow sorghum here.
- And where are the hookers?
- Around back.
But first, she was a university honors
student who devoted her life to kids.
Until the night a grossly overweight
pervert named Homer Simpson...
...gave her a crash course
in depravity.
"Babysitter and the Beast."
Oh, crap.
Somebody had to take
the babysitter home.
Then I noticed she was sitting
on her sweet can...
I grabbed her sweet can...
Oh, just thinking about her can...
I just wish I had
her sweet, sweet, sweet can.
So, Mr. Simpson,
you admit you grabbed her can.
What do you have to say
in your defense?
Mr. Simpson, your silence
will only incriminate you further.
No, Mr. Simpson, don’t take your anger
out on me. Get back. Get back!
- Mr. Simpson, no!
- Dramatization: May not have happened.
Marge, kids,
everything's gonna be just fine.
Now go upstairs and pack your bags.
We're gonna start a new life
under the sea.
Under the sea
There'll be no accusations
Just friendly crustaceans
Under the sea
That's your solution to everything,
to move under the sea. It won't happen.
Not with that attitude.
Look, maybe this whole thing
will blow over.
It didn't blow over, Marge.
Nothing ever blows over for me.
Simpson scandal update.
Homer sleeps nude in an oxygen tent
he believes gives him sexual powers.
Hey, that's a half-truth.
Today on Ben:
Mothers and runaway daughters reunited
by their hatred of Homer Simpson.
And here's your host, Gentle Ben.
I just have one thing to say.
Let's have less Homer Simpsons
and more money for public schools.
Ben, I have a question.
No, Ben. No.
And now we return to
Fox Night at the Movies.
Homer S: Portrait of an Ass-Grabber.
Starring Dennis Franz.
Portrait. Sounds classy.
Doesn't it?
No, Mr. Simpson.
A cat is a living creature.
I don’t care.
Now I'm gonna grab me
something sweet.
No, Mr. Simpson.
That's sexual harassment.
If you keep it up, I'll yell so loud,
the whole country will hear.
With a man in the White House?
Not likely.
This is hour 57 of our live,
round-the-clock coverage...
...outside the Simpson estate.
Remember to tune in tonight at 8:00
for highlights of today's vigil...
...including when
the garbage man came...
...and when Marge Simpson
put the cat out.
Possibly because it was harassed.
We don’t know.
There's no way to see
into the Simpson home...
...without some kind of infrared,
heat-sensitive camera.
So let's turn it on.
Now, this technology is new to me...
...but I'm pretty sure
that's Homer Simpson in the oven...
...rotating slowly. His body temperature
has risen to over 400 degrees.
He's literally stewing
in his own juices.
Now here are some results
from our phone-in poll.
Ninety-five percent of the people
believe Homer Simpson is guilty.
Of course,
this is just a television poll...
...which is not legally binding,
unless Proposition 304 passes.
And we all pray it will.
I don't have a friend in the world.
- Let us through.
- We're Homer's true friends.
Oh, really?
- Come on, let us through, you vultures.
- Oh, Marge. It's a miracle.
How can you judge this man...
...without talking to the people
who know him best?
We got the real dirt on Homer Simpson,
and the bidding starts at 10 G's.
- I bid 10 G's.
- Ten-five G's.
I need a hug.
How come you guys hesitated?
Sorry, Dad.
We do believe in you. We really do.
It's just hard not to listen to TV.
It's spent so much more time
raising us than you.
Maybe TV is right.
TV's always right.
Are you hugging the TV?
- No.
And the number one reference
that I am running into the ground is:
Homer Simpson.
Is Homer Simpson.
I like it better when they're
making fun of people who aren't me.
I know. Evening at the Improv.
They never talk about anything
beyond the 1980s.
I think about weird stuff.
Like, what would happen if E. T.
And Mr. T had a baby?
Well, you'd get Mr. E. T.,
wouldn't you?
And, you know, I think he'd sound
a little something like this:
"I pity the fool
who doesn't phone home."
I wouldn't wanna be
Mr. T right now.
Homer. Homer, the kids have a
great idea how you can clear your name.
The media's making you a monster
because they don't care about truth.
All they care about is entertainment.
You need a forum where they don't
know the meaning of entertainment:
Public access television.
- But those shows all look so crummy.
- Well, we could dress it up a bit.
We can bring a fern,
and a folding chair from the garage...
...and the most decorative thing of all,
the truth.
There are only 49 stars on that flag.
I'll be deep in the cold, cold ground
before I recognize Missouri.
Now it's time for
The Innocence Report...
...with Homer Simpson.
Hello. I am Homer Simpson.
Or, as some of you wags
have dubbed me, "Father Goose."
You know, everybody believed
the worst about me right away.
Nobody cares that I didn't do it.
But I didn't.
Okay, look, I've done
some bad things in my life.
But harassing women
is not one of them.
Like one time, we were having this race
with this stupid, old-timey bicycle...
...with the big wheel in front.
So I figure, "We'll see about that."
So I get this big chunk
of cinderblock, and I...
Oh, gotta go.
Innocent.
Dad, you did it. I am so proud of you.
The switchboards are lighting up.
Two calls. That's our best ever.
Hello? No, Janice doesn't live here.
Hello? Yes, I am interested
in long-distance savings.
Very interested.
Marge, this is so depressing.
My only hope
is this homemade Prozac.
Needs more ice cream.
So you don't like
the old-time bikes, huh?
Homer, I love amateur video.
And your show
is the most amateur video I ever saw.
My hobby is secretly
videotaping couples in cars.
I didn't come forward
because in this country...
...it makes you look like a pervert.
But every single
Scottish person does it!
Oh, baby. Oh, yeah. Oh, baby.
Oh, no. That's Mayor Quimby.
Here we go.
Precious Venus.
Thank you.
Dad, this clears you completely.
You know, the courts might not
work anymore...
...but as long as everybody
is videotaping everyone else...
...justice will be done.
See?
Homer, I thought you were an animal.
But your daughter said
you were a decent man.
- I guess she was right.
- You're both right.
In our mad pursuit of a scoop...
...we members of the press
sometimes make mistakes.
Rock Bottom would like to make
the following corrections:
Wow, V8 juice
isn't one-eighth gasoline.
- And Ted Koppel is a robot.
- There's you, Dad.
Tomorrow on Rock Bottom.
He's a foreigner who takes perverted
videos of you when you least suspect it.
He's "Rowdy Roddy Peeper".
Oh, that man is sick.
Groundskeeper Willie
saved you, Homer.
But listen to the music. He's evil.
Hasn't this experience taught you
you can't believe everything you hear?
Marge, my friend,
I haven't learned a thing.
Let's never fight again.
www.tvsubtitles.net